<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics</id>
  <title>pdspolitics TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-08-10T22:59:28+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/pdspolitics.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from pdspolitics</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7263520364867767594</id>
    <title>The government just investigated itself for a crime it didn’t know it actually committed. #FBI  #US  #Politics  #Spy</title>
    <updated>2023-08-06T20:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content>The government just investigated itself for a crime it didn’t know it actually committed. #FBI  #US  #Politics  #Spy</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7263520364867767594" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-06T20:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7264712670190816555</id>
    <title>According to former President Trump’s own lawyer, he only “asked” for the election to be overturned, he didn’t actually do it. #Trump   Trump’s attempts to overturn the 2020 election weren’t criminal because he didn’t DIRECT Mike Pence to throw out Biden’</title>
    <updated>2023-08-07T23:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content>According to former President Trump’s own lawyer, he only “asked” for the election to be overturned, he didn’t actually do it. #Trump   Trump’s attempts to overturn the 2020 election weren’t criminal because he didn’t DIRECT Mike Pence to throw out Biden’s legitimate win, he just ASKED him nicely! That’s what Trump’s lawyer John Lauro argued during an interview with CNN last night, seemingly previewing what Trump’s defense will be in the new federal case against him. With Lauro claiming that Trump's attempts to get Pence to toss the slate of electors and pause the certification of the election amounted to free speech protected under the First Amendment: “Asking is aspirational. Asking is not action. It’s core free speech. The press should be defending free speech.” #Politics  #US  #Election</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7264712670190816555" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-07T23:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7265068326794186026</id>
    <title>Democracy is on the line in Ohio, and there’s just a few hours left to vote. #Ohio  #Election  #Vote  #Politics  Ohio voters are heading to the polls for a special election today where democracy itself is on the line. The very surface-level TLDR is basica</title>
    <updated>2023-08-08T21:39:01+00:00</updated>
    <content>Democracy is on the line in Ohio, and there’s just a few hours left to vote. #Ohio  #Election  #Vote  #Politics  Ohio voters are heading to the polls for a special election today where democracy itself is on the line. The very surface-level TLDR is basically that the special election is being held for people to vote on Issue 1 — a measure that will make it harder to pass constitutional amendments by ballot initiative. The measure achieves this in a few ways, but the most significant is that it would raise the number of votes required to approve a constitutional amendment from 50% to a 60% supermajority. So, in other words, 59% of voters can want an amendment, and a minority can undermine the democratic will of that huge majority. And if that sounds like minority rule, it’s because it’s literally minority rule.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7265068326794186026" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-08T21:39:01+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7265436544914165038</id>
    <title>Voters in Ohio overwhelmingly rejected Issue 1, which threatened to change democracy in the state forever #Ohio  #ohioelection  #Vote  #Politics</title>
    <updated>2023-08-09T23:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content>Voters in Ohio overwhelmingly rejected Issue 1, which threatened to change democracy in the state forever #Ohio  #ohioelection  #Vote  #Politics</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7265436544914165038" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-09T23:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7265831640109239594</id>
    <title>ProPublica Finds Clarence Thomas Accepted Even More Gifts #ClarenceThomas  That includes: “At least 38 destination vacations, including a previously unreported voyage on a yacht around the Bahamas; 26 private jet flights, plus an additional eight by helic</title>
    <updated>2023-08-10T22:59:28+00:00</updated>
    <content>ProPublica Finds Clarence Thomas Accepted Even More Gifts #ClarenceThomas  That includes: “At least 38 destination vacations, including a previously unreported voyage on a yacht around the Bahamas; 26 private jet flights, plus an additional eight by helicopter; a dozen VIP passes to professional and college sporting events, typically perched in the skybox; two stays at luxury resorts in Florida and Jamaica; and one standing invitation to an uber-exclusive golf club overlooking the Atlantic coast.” But the report explicitly states that even THAT “it is almost certainly an undercount.” #political  #US  #Propublica</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7265831640109239594" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-10T22:59:28+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
