<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics</id>
  <title>pdspolitics TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-06-28T20:00:00+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/pdspolitics.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from pdspolitics</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7247941854233152810</id>
    <title>Republicans censured Adam Schiff in the U.S. House and Democrats went into open revolt. #Politics  The GOP made the very major move of voting to censure Democrat Adam Schiff for his actions in the investigation into Trump’s alleged ties with Russia while </title>
    <updated>2023-06-23T20:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content>Republicans censured Adam Schiff in the U.S. House and Democrats went into open revolt. #Politics  The GOP made the very major move of voting to censure Democrat Adam Schiff for his actions in the investigation into Trump’s alleged ties with Russia while he was the Chair of the House Intelligence Committee. Normally, a censure is just a very strong and formal condemnation that doesn’t carry any tangible consequences, but this resolution also directed the Ethics Committee to open an investigation into Schiff’s behavior.  Beyond that, the censure itself is also very significant because this is very rare. In the entire history of the House, the chamber has only voted to censure its members two dozen times — and in the past 4 decades, only 2 representatives have been censured. So it makes sense that this was very divisive, with the measure passing by a narrow margin of 213-209 with all Democrats voting against and 6 Republicans voting present. And, very notably here, it only passed after another resolution to censure Schiff failed last week when 20 Republicans killed it because of a provision that would have also fined Schiff $16 million. #US  #AdamSchiff  #House</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7247941854233152810" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-06-23T20:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7247639092211551534</id>
    <title>ProPublica has discovered that Supreme Court Judge Samuel Alito failed to disclose luxury gifts from a Republican mega donor who he later heard cases for. #SupremeCourt  But this story doesn’t stop there. Alito declined ProPublica’s request for comment wh</title>
    <updated>2023-06-24T20:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content>ProPublica has discovered that Supreme Court Judge Samuel Alito failed to disclose luxury gifts from a Republican mega donor who he later heard cases for. #SupremeCourt  But this story doesn’t stop there. Alito declined ProPublica’s request for comment when the outlet sent him a detailed list of questions. But he DID respond to the allegations in a totally bizarre Wall Street Journal op-ep titled: “ProPublica Misleads Its Readers.” And I really can’t understate how weird this is for a few reasons. Right, first of all, as Slate explains: “It is rare (and may in fact be unprecedented) for a sitting court justice to attack a media outlet in print—or to engage in any kind of published advocacy at all.” But beyond that, maybe the weirdest part of all is that this op-ed was published several hours BEFORE the ProPublica report even came. #US  #Politics  #SCOTUS</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7247639092211551534" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-06-24T20:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7247924644685073707</id>
    <title>MTG &amp; Lauren Boebert just took their feud over who gets to impeach Biden to a whole new level on the House floor. #US  #MTG  #Politics  #LaurenBoebert</title>
    <updated>2023-06-25T20:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content>MTG &amp; Lauren Boebert just took their feud over who gets to impeach Biden to a whole new level on the House floor. #US  #MTG  #Politics  #LaurenBoebert</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7247924644685073707" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-06-25T20:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7249491436075371818</id>
    <title>CNN just published audio of Trump talking about taking classified documents after he left the White House #Trump  #TrumpTapes  #US  #Politics</title>
    <updated>2023-06-27T23:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content>CNN just published audio of Trump talking about taking classified documents after he left the White House #Trump  #TrumpTapes  #US  #Politics</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7249491436075371818" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-06-27T23:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7249771117815123243</id>
    <title>Three Supreme Court justices just voted to “upend democracy,” but they were stopped by the rest of the court. #SupremeCourt  The high court struck down an INCREDIBLY consequential and controversial case in a 6-3 ruling. The case in question was called Moo</title>
    <updated>2023-06-28T20:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content>Three Supreme Court justices just voted to “upend democracy,” but they were stopped by the rest of the court. #SupremeCourt  The high court struck down an INCREDIBLY consequential and controversial case in a 6-3 ruling. The case in question was called Moore v. Harper, and we actually did a deep dive on it a little while ago which I’ll link to down below. But the very top-level TLDR is that centers around Republican gerrymandering in North Carolina. North Carolina Republicans took the matter to the Supreme Court after multiple Congressional maps they drew were rejected because of gerrymandering.  But this wasn’t a typical gerrymandering case: the Republican’s argument rested entirely on a totally untested, fringe theory touted by Trump and other far-right extremists in their effort to overturn the 2020 election called Independent State Legislature theory. The basis behind ISL theory is that the Constitution gives state legislatures pretty much the exclusive power to set election rules and congressional maps. But not only is that authority singular, nothing can stop them — there can be no intervention from state courts, governors, or voters. I mean, we’re talking about a case where North Carolina literally argued that legislatures would even violate their own state Constitutions! #US  #Politics  #MooreVHarper</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7249771117815123243" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-06-28T20:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
