<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics</id>
  <title>pdspolitics TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-07-21T23:00:00+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/pdspolitics.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from pdspolitics</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7257571475715116331</id>
    <title>It looks like Trump is about to be federally indicted AGAIN. #DonaldTrump   The former president said in a post on Truth Social that he received a letter from special counsel Jack Smith this weekend informing him that he’s a target of a federal criminal i</title>
    <updated>2023-07-19T20:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content>It looks like Trump is about to be federally indicted AGAIN. #DonaldTrump   The former president said in a post on Truth Social that he received a letter from special counsel Jack Smith this weekend informing him that he’s a target of a federal criminal investigation into efforts to overturn the 2020 election. With Trump writing calling Smith “deranged” and claiming the special counsel gave him “a very short 4 days to report to the Grand Jury, which almost always means an Arrest and Indictment.” And, I mean, he’s not wrong there… when someone gets a letter from the DOJ telling them they are the target of a probe, it is usually a really good sign they are about to be indicted. Right, this is actually something we talked about before when it was first reported that Trump had been informed he was a target in the Mar-a-Lago documents probe. But, for some quick catch-up here, “target” is actually a technical term that the DOJ defines as a person “to whom the prosecutor or the grand jury has substantial evidence linking him or her to the commission of a crime.” With DOJ specifically encouraging prosecutors to send so-called “target letters” in cases where people are likely to be indicted so they get the opportunity to testify before the grand jury in their probe. And, very notably, Trump was in fact indicted on federal charges about a week after it was reported he had gotten a target letter for the Mar-a-Lago inquiry. So, in other words, it seems likely that Trump is going to be indicted in the Jan. 6 probe in a matter of days or weeks. #US  #Politics  #JackSmith</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7257571475715116331" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-19T20:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7257649131999612206</id>
    <title>Michigan just brought the FIRST-ever criminal charges against fake electors that tried to overturn the 2020 election. #Politics  Yesterday, Michigan Attorney General Dana Nessel charged 16 Republicans who falsely claimed to be the presidential electors in</title>
    <updated>2023-07-19T23:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content>Michigan just brought the FIRST-ever criminal charges against fake electors that tried to overturn the 2020 election. #Politics  Yesterday, Michigan Attorney General Dana Nessel charged 16 Republicans who falsely claimed to be the presidential electors in 2020 in an effort to get Trump elected in the state. And the charges here are hefty, with Nessel slapping all 16 with eight criminal counts including forgery, conspiracy to commit forgery, and election law forgery —  Some of which carry sentences of up to 14 years in prison. Specifically, court documents released after the charges were announced detail how the 16 Republicans met and filled out paperwork claiming they were Michigan’s official electors and that Trump had won the election. This despite the fact that Biden had actually won by 150,000 votes, courts had already thrown out lawsuits that claimed Trump had won, and leaders in the legislature had made it clear they would not challenge the results further. #US  #Trump  #Michigan</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7257649131999612206" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-19T23:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7257934613669055786</id>
    <title>Reports indicate that police are using Big Brother tactics to track people crossing state lines to seek gender-affirming and reproductive care #Politics  Big Brother has gone too far! That is what a group of more than three dozen lawmakers argued in a let</title>
    <updated>2023-07-20T20:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content>Reports indicate that police are using Big Brother tactics to track people crossing state lines to seek gender-affirming and reproductive care #Politics  Big Brother has gone too far! That is what a group of more than three dozen lawmakers argued in a letter urging the Biden administration to change federal laws that allow law enforcement to access sensitive medical data without a warrant. #US  #Biden  #BigBrother</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7257934613669055786" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-20T20:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7258308019056872750</id>
    <title>Wesleyan University says it will end legacy admissions following SCOTUS overturning affirmative action. #Wesleyan  Should college applicants be given a boost in admissions because a member of their family went to the same school? That’s a question many ar</title>
    <updated>2023-07-21T20:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content>Wesleyan University says it will end legacy admissions following SCOTUS overturning affirmative action. #Wesleyan  Should college applicants be given a boost in admissions because a member of their family went to the same school? That’s a question many are asking after the Supreme Court overturned Affirmative Action. So-called legacy admissions have been criticized for years now for favoring rich, white applicants over people of color. But that practice has come under even more attack since the Supreme Court decided that schools can’t consider race in admissions. And it seems like, increasingly, more and more people agree that legacy admissions are unfair. Right, top politicians on both sides of the aisle — including President Biden himself — have come out against this practice. And polls have consistently shown that the public agrees. And it seems like some schools are actually taking that to heart. Right, the reason we’re talking about this today is because the esteemed liberal arts school Wesleyan University announced that it would be ending legacy admissions. With this following in the footsteps of other selective schools that have recently made the same move including Amherst, Johns Hopkins, and Carnegie Mellon. #AffirmativeAction  #College  #Politics</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7258308019056872750" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-21T20:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7258307419556629806</id>
    <title>Democrats say Republicans in Alabama are so determined to undermine Black voters that they’re now defying the Supreme Court. #Politics  Right, last month, the conservative high court made an absolutely shocking 5-4 decision to uphold a lower court ruling </title>
    <updated>2023-07-21T23:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content>Democrats say Republicans in Alabama are so determined to undermine Black voters that they’re now defying the Supreme Court. #Politics  Right, last month, the conservative high court made an absolutely shocking 5-4 decision to uphold a lower court ruling that tossed Alabama’s Congressional map on the grounds that it discriminated against Black voters and violated the Voting Rights Act. This because, despite the fact that nearly a third of voters in the state are Black, the GOP had drawn its Congressional map so just one of the state’s 7 districts had a Black majority.  And, of course, as part of that decision, the Supreme Court directed Alabama to comply with a federal court order to re-draw the map so at least TWO districts had at least close to a majority of Black voters. But apparently, that’s too complicated for the tiny brains of the Alabama GOP. Because Republicans in both the State House and Senate passed two different maps this week — and NEITHER sets up another district Black residents make up a majority or near-majority of voters. This notably despite the fact that Democrats literally drew a map that would make another Black-majority district, but Republicans shot it down in favor of their own versions. #US  #Vote  #Politics</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7258307419556629806" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-21T23:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
