<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics</id>
  <title>pdspolitics TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-08-02T22:38:05+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/pdspolitics.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from pdspolitics</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7260916509801811243</id>
    <title>A Texas A&amp;M professor nearly lost her job after she criticized the state government. #Texas  This professor nearly lost her job because she criticized the government. Right, back in March, Joy Alonzo, a clinical assistant professor of pharmacy, gave a gue</title>
    <updated>2023-07-28T20:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content>A Texas A&amp;M professor nearly lost her job after she criticized the state government. #Texas  This professor nearly lost her job because she criticized the government. Right, back in March, Joy Alonzo, a clinical assistant professor of pharmacy, gave a guest lecture at the University of Texas Medical Branch, or UTMB. And at some point during or immediately after the lecture, she made a comment many understood as critical of Texas Lieutenant Governor Dan Patrick. So a first-year medical student filed a complaint against Alonzo for allegedly disparaging Patrick. Now while we can’t say for sure who filed that complaint, we do know one of the first-year students attending the lecture was the daughter of the person who ultimately prompted an investigation against Alonzo. With that being Dawn Buckingham, the Texas land commissioner who also happens to be a graduate of UTMB’s medical school and has close ties to Patrick. Right, she served alongside him for six years in the state Senate and got elected to her current post with his backing. And reportedly Buckingham called A&amp;M’s vice chancellor for governmental relations, as well as the lieutenant governor himself, about Alonzo. Within hours Patrick’s office was discussing the matter with John Sharp, chancellor of the Texas A&amp;M system. With Sharp reportedly sending a text to Patrick saying: “Joy Alonzo has been placed on administrative leave pending investigation re firing her. [should] be finished by end of week.” Meanwhile, UTMB leaders sent an email to the students who attended Alonzo's lecture. Stating that the professor's comments about the lieutenant governor didn't reflect the opinion of the university. #TexasA&amp;M  #Politics  #US</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7260916509801811243" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-28T20:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7260922565093494062</id>
    <title>Trucking Lobbyists Are Blocking Crash Survivors from $$$ #Cars  #Trucks  #Crash  #Politics</title>
    <updated>2023-07-29T20:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content>Trucking Lobbyists Are Blocking Crash Survivors from $$$ #Cars  #Trucks  #Crash  #Politics</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7260922565093494062" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-29T20:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7262096674040859946</id>
    <title>Texas is ripping libraries out of schools and turning them into “discipline centers.” #Texas  A judge in Arkansas temporarily blocked a law that would have made it a crime for librarians and booksellers to give minors “harmful” materials. And so last mont</title>
    <updated>2023-07-31T23:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content>Texas is ripping libraries out of schools and turning them into “discipline centers.” #Texas  A judge in Arkansas temporarily blocked a law that would have made it a crime for librarians and booksellers to give minors “harmful” materials. And so last month, a group of booksellers and libraries filed a lawsuit, arguing that elements of the new law were unconstitutional. With the groups also claiming that the law presented them with an impossible situation. And the judge agreed, issuing a preliminary injunction where he argued the law would: “permit, if not encourage, library committees and local governmental bodies to make censorship decisions based on content or viewpoint, which would violate the First Amendment.” Right, and this is just one state of many where conservative makers are trying to ban and restrict access to books. And some places are finding really unique ways to do this. Right, recently, Texas’ largest public school district in the state — Houston Independent School District — announced that it is eliminating school librarians at 28 schools, And converting the libraries into discipline centers for kids with behavior problems. And this isn’t just a few schools — the move will apply to 28 different schools, with the district saying an additional 57 schools will be assessed on a case-by-case basis. #BookTok  #BookBan  #Politics</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7262096674040859946" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-31T23:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7262436715678240043</id>
    <title>Trump Allegedly Pays Legal Battles with $$$ from Small Donors #Trump  Trump’s political action committee has spent more than $40 million on legal expenses for him and others JUST in the first half of 2023. That is what people familiar with the matter firs</title>
    <updated>2023-08-01T20:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content>Trump Allegedly Pays Legal Battles with $$$ from Small Donors #Trump  Trump’s political action committee has spent more than $40 million on legal expenses for him and others JUST in the first half of 2023. That is what people familiar with the matter first told The Washington Post, though sources have since relayed the same information to other outlets. According to the sources, Trump’s PAC, Save America, is expected to report the expenses in a legal spending in a filing today. Though as of recording, the disclosure has not officially been filed. And the legal costs just for the first half of the year are more than DOUBLE the $16 million the group spent on legal fees for ALL of 2022. Now, as far as who is receiving this legal aid, Trump advisers told The Post that the PAC is helping pay for “almost anyone drawn into the investigations who requests help from the former president and his advisers.” And, very notably here, most of the money the PAC raises comes “from small-dollar contributions by Trump supporters across the country,” But sources also say that the legal financing has raised questions from prosecutors about possible conflicts of interest between Trump and witnesses. And beyond that, The Post has also previously reported that the fundraising and creation by the Save America PAC is under investigation — though it hasn’t been accused of any wrongdoing yet. With some arguing that this is just a concerted effort to “drain” money from Trump and his allies “so he has far less to spend in 2024 than Democrats.”But others hit back on that, including big names like Tomi Lahren. #Politics  #US  #TomiLahren</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7262436715678240043" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-01T20:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7262857344755731758</id>
    <title>Former President Trump has been indicted on charges of trying to overturn the 2020 Presidential Election results. #DonaldTrump  #Politics  #US  #Indictment</title>
    <updated>2023-08-02T22:38:05+00:00</updated>
    <content>Former President Trump has been indicted on charges of trying to overturn the 2020 Presidential Election results. #DonaldTrump  #Politics  #US  #Indictment</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7262857344755731758" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-02T22:38:05+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
