<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics</id>
  <title>pdspolitics TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-07-28T20:00:00+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/pdspolitics.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from pdspolitics</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7259788259289566510</id>
    <title>Republicans in the House are proposing tax credits for unborn fetuses #Politics  #US  #Money</title>
    <updated>2023-07-25T20:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content>Republicans in the House are proposing tax credits for unborn fetuses #Politics  #US  #Money</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7259788259289566510" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-25T20:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7259877020321041707</id>
    <title>Biden’s Justice Department is suing Texas and Gov. Greg Abbott over its controversial Rio Grande buoy barrier at the US-Mexico border. #Texas  #Politics  #US  #RioGrande</title>
    <updated>2023-07-25T23:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content>Biden’s Justice Department is suing Texas and Gov. Greg Abbott over its controversial Rio Grande buoy barrier at the US-Mexico border. #Texas  #Politics  #US  #RioGrande</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7259877020321041707" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-25T23:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7260238636204051754</id>
    <title>A whistleblower just told Congress that the U.S. has captured “non-human” pilots operating UFOs #UFO  The House Oversight Committee is holding a public hearing today as part of an effort to convince the Biden Administration to release more information abo</title>
    <updated>2023-07-26T23:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content>A whistleblower just told Congress that the U.S. has captured “non-human” pilots operating UFOs #UFO  The House Oversight Committee is holding a public hearing today as part of an effort to convince the Biden Administration to release more information about UFOs. One of the most viral clips circulating social media right now is this one where whistleblower David Grusch is being questioned by Rep. Nancy Mace about if he believes the U.S. government has made contact with extraterrestrials. #UAP  #Aliens  #Congress</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7260238636204051754" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-26T23:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7260631191269723434</id>
    <title>Hunter Biden’s Plea Deal Falls Apart #HunterBiden  #FoxNews #political  #US</title>
    <updated>2023-07-27T23:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content>Hunter Biden’s Plea Deal Falls Apart #HunterBiden  #FoxNews #political  #US</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7260631191269723434" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-27T23:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7260916509801811243</id>
    <title>A Texas A&amp;M professor nearly lost her job after she criticized the state government. #Texas  This professor nearly lost her job because she criticized the government. Right, back in March, Joy Alonzo, a clinical assistant professor of pharmacy, gave a gue</title>
    <updated>2023-07-28T20:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content>A Texas A&amp;M professor nearly lost her job after she criticized the state government. #Texas  This professor nearly lost her job because she criticized the government. Right, back in March, Joy Alonzo, a clinical assistant professor of pharmacy, gave a guest lecture at the University of Texas Medical Branch, or UTMB. And at some point during or immediately after the lecture, she made a comment many understood as critical of Texas Lieutenant Governor Dan Patrick. So a first-year medical student filed a complaint against Alonzo for allegedly disparaging Patrick. Now while we can’t say for sure who filed that complaint, we do know one of the first-year students attending the lecture was the daughter of the person who ultimately prompted an investigation against Alonzo. With that being Dawn Buckingham, the Texas land commissioner who also happens to be a graduate of UTMB’s medical school and has close ties to Patrick. Right, she served alongside him for six years in the state Senate and got elected to her current post with his backing. And reportedly Buckingham called A&amp;M’s vice chancellor for governmental relations, as well as the lieutenant governor himself, about Alonzo. Within hours Patrick’s office was discussing the matter with John Sharp, chancellor of the Texas A&amp;M system. With Sharp reportedly sending a text to Patrick saying: “Joy Alonzo has been placed on administrative leave pending investigation re firing her. [should] be finished by end of week.” Meanwhile, UTMB leaders sent an email to the students who attended Alonzo's lecture. Stating that the professor's comments about the lieutenant governor didn't reflect the opinion of the university. #TexasA&amp;M  #Politics  #US</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7260916509801811243" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-28T20:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
