<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics</id>
  <title>pdspolitics TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-08-04T23:00:00+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/pdspolitics.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from pdspolitics</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7262096674040859946</id>
    <title>Texas is ripping libraries out of schools and turning them into “discipline centers.” #Texas  A judge in Arkansas temporarily blocked a law that would have made it a crime for librarians and booksellers to give minors “harmful” materials. And so last mont</title>
    <updated>2023-07-31T23:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content>Texas is ripping libraries out of schools and turning them into “discipline centers.” #Texas  A judge in Arkansas temporarily blocked a law that would have made it a crime for librarians and booksellers to give minors “harmful” materials. And so last month, a group of booksellers and libraries filed a lawsuit, arguing that elements of the new law were unconstitutional. With the groups also claiming that the law presented them with an impossible situation. And the judge agreed, issuing a preliminary injunction where he argued the law would: “permit, if not encourage, library committees and local governmental bodies to make censorship decisions based on content or viewpoint, which would violate the First Amendment.” Right, and this is just one state of many where conservative makers are trying to ban and restrict access to books. And some places are finding really unique ways to do this. Right, recently, Texas’ largest public school district in the state — Houston Independent School District — announced that it is eliminating school librarians at 28 schools, And converting the libraries into discipline centers for kids with behavior problems. And this isn’t just a few schools — the move will apply to 28 different schools, with the district saying an additional 57 schools will be assessed on a case-by-case basis. #BookTok  #BookBan  #Politics</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7262096674040859946" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-31T23:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7262436715678240043</id>
    <title>Trump Allegedly Pays Legal Battles with $$$ from Small Donors #Trump  Trump’s political action committee has spent more than $40 million on legal expenses for him and others JUST in the first half of 2023. That is what people familiar with the matter firs</title>
    <updated>2023-08-01T20:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content>Trump Allegedly Pays Legal Battles with $$$ from Small Donors #Trump  Trump’s political action committee has spent more than $40 million on legal expenses for him and others JUST in the first half of 2023. That is what people familiar with the matter first told The Washington Post, though sources have since relayed the same information to other outlets. According to the sources, Trump’s PAC, Save America, is expected to report the expenses in a legal spending in a filing today. Though as of recording, the disclosure has not officially been filed. And the legal costs just for the first half of the year are more than DOUBLE the $16 million the group spent on legal fees for ALL of 2022. Now, as far as who is receiving this legal aid, Trump advisers told The Post that the PAC is helping pay for “almost anyone drawn into the investigations who requests help from the former president and his advisers.” And, very notably here, most of the money the PAC raises comes “from small-dollar contributions by Trump supporters across the country,” But sources also say that the legal financing has raised questions from prosecutors about possible conflicts of interest between Trump and witnesses. And beyond that, The Post has also previously reported that the fundraising and creation by the Save America PAC is under investigation — though it hasn’t been accused of any wrongdoing yet. With some arguing that this is just a concerted effort to “drain” money from Trump and his allies “so he has far less to spend in 2024 than Democrats.”But others hit back on that, including big names like Tomi Lahren. #Politics  #US  #TomiLahren</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7262436715678240043" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-01T20:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7262857344755731758</id>
    <title>Former President Trump has been indicted on charges of trying to overturn the 2020 Presidential Election results. #DonaldTrump  #Politics  #US  #Indictment</title>
    <updated>2023-08-02T22:38:05+00:00</updated>
    <content>Former President Trump has been indicted on charges of trying to overturn the 2020 Presidential Election results. #DonaldTrump  #Politics  #US  #Indictment</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7262857344755731758" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-02T22:38:05+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7263522866317167918</id>
    <title>Bodies have now been found in Texas’ buoy barrier meant to prevent migrants crossing from from the Mexican border #Texas  #Mexico  #Politics  #US</title>
    <updated>2023-08-04T20:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content>Bodies have now been found in Texas’ buoy barrier meant to prevent migrants crossing from from the Mexican border #Texas  #Mexico  #Politics  #US</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7263522866317167918" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-04T20:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7263511978063433006</id>
    <title>China &amp; Russia used Microsoft to hack the US government, and Microsoft might have known it had serious flaws the whole time. #Microsoft  Microsoft is under heavy scrutiny after both China and Russia managed to use vulnerabilities in their products to hack</title>
    <updated>2023-08-04T23:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content>China &amp; Russia used Microsoft to hack the US government, and Microsoft might have known it had serious flaws the whole time. #Microsoft  Microsoft is under heavy scrutiny after both China and Russia managed to use vulnerabilities in their products to hack the United States government. The most recent hack was announced by Microsoft yesterday, and involved Russian hackers linked to their foreign intelligence service using Microsoft 365 accounts to trick Microsoft Teams users. Using their compromised 365 accounts, the hackers set up official-looking technical support-themed domains and sent Teams messages to a ton of people directing them to the fake websites. Once there they’d be asked to login and grant approval on their Microsoft multi-factor authentication app. But in reality, it was the hackers who needed that authentication code to get access to the target's account. Once in, they had full access and used it to access sensitive information at various global organizations and even US government agencies.#Tech  #Politics  #US</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7263511978063433006" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-04T23:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
