<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics</id>
  <title>pdspolitics TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-07-26T20:00:00+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/pdspolitics.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from pdspolitics</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7258309834175434027</id>
    <title>Millions of U.S. military emails with very sensitive contents have been sent to the country Mali — a big ally of Russia and employer of the Wagner group, all because of a simple typo… #Russia  The Pentagon confirmed that instead of using the military’s do</title>
    <updated>2023-07-22T20:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content>Millions of U.S. military emails with very sensitive contents have been sent to the country Mali — a big ally of Russia and employer of the Wagner group, all because of a simple typo… #Russia  The Pentagon confirmed that instead of using the military’s domain for emails which is “.MIL” (M-I-L), people are incorrectly typing “.ML” (ML) — which is the domain for Mali. Now, notably, according to reports:  “None of the missent emails have been marked classified, but many contain highly sensitive information about American military personnel and installations, including base staff lists, medical data, and identity documents.” But still, the Dutch internet entrepreneur who has contracted to manage Mali’s country domain for the last decade told reporters that he first noticed this issue when he first started working on the domain and has tried to repeatedly warn U.S. authorities. #US  #Politics  #Military</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7258309834175434027" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-22T20:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7258317911398305067</id>
    <title>A Small Handful of Court Cases Could Decide Control of the House in 2024 #Politics  Control of the House in 2024 could be decided by a few court cases. Right, according to Axios, cases involving gerrymandering in Alabama, Louisiana, New York, North Caroli</title>
    <updated>2023-07-23T20:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content>A Small Handful of Court Cases Could Decide Control of the House in 2024 #Politics  Control of the House in 2024 could be decided by a few court cases. Right, according to Axios, cases involving gerrymandering in Alabama, Louisiana, New York, North Carolina, and Ohio “will play an outsized role in determining which party holds the House majority next year.” In Alabama, more districts that are more likely to swing blue will likely be added after the Supreme Court made a very surprising decision last month where they ruled the state had racially gerrymandered its districts and needed to redraw them. With Axios also not that the high court’s decision there “is also expected to overturn Louisiana's map and could reverberate in several other Southern states.” Meanwhile, just last week, an Appeals Court in New York sided with Democrats and ordered the state’s map to be redrawn. And while Republicans have vowed to appeal the case to the state’s highest court — which did previously strike down Democrats’ map — it is now composed of judges that are more liberal. Right, and that decision especially will be key here because New York alone could determine the majority. With Axios explaining that the GOP “can’t afford to lose more than four House seats in next year’s election,” but adding: “Republicans in 2022 won six congressional districts in New York State that President Biden carried, and even small tweaks to the map could make competitive districts unwinnable for Republicans.” But, at the same time, Republicans are also expected to gain three seats in the House in North Carolina. This after the State Supreme Court overturned its OWN past ruling making partisan gerrymandering illegal. #House  #US  #2024</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7258317911398305067" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-23T20:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7259788259289566510</id>
    <title>Republicans in the House are proposing tax credits for unborn fetuses #Politics  #US  #Money</title>
    <updated>2023-07-25T20:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content>Republicans in the House are proposing tax credits for unborn fetuses #Politics  #US  #Money</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7259788259289566510" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-25T20:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7259877020321041707</id>
    <title>Biden’s Justice Department is suing Texas and Gov. Greg Abbott over its controversial Rio Grande buoy barrier at the US-Mexico border. #Texas  #Politics  #US  #RioGrande</title>
    <updated>2023-07-25T23:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content>Biden’s Justice Department is suing Texas and Gov. Greg Abbott over its controversial Rio Grande buoy barrier at the US-Mexico border. #Texas  #Politics  #US  #RioGrande</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7259877020321041707" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-25T23:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7260158027020504366</id>
    <title>Kevin McCarthy is now floating the idea of impeaching President Biden over the family’s business dealings. #JoeBiden  While speaking on Sean Hannity’s show last night, the House Speaker discussed House Republican’s investigation into the business dealings</title>
    <updated>2023-07-26T20:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content>Kevin McCarthy is now floating the idea of impeaching President Biden over the family’s business dealings. #JoeBiden  While speaking on Sean Hannity’s show last night, the House Speaker discussed House Republican’s investigation into the business dealings of Biden’s family members — and in particular, Hunter Biden. Right, for a while now, Republicans have been investigating several unproven claims of financial misconduct. This including claims from two IRS whistleblowers who said the DOJ improperly intervened in the probe into Hunter Biden’s taxes by making it too lenient. As well as an uncorroborated FBI document they claim shows that Biden’s family received payments from foreign companies. Those investigations haven’t gained much traction — probably because all the claims Republicans have made are… still totally unsubstantiated. But despite that, McCarthy has now seriously escalated the situation, discussing various parts of the investigations and telling Hannity: “If you are sitting in our position today, we would know none of this if Republicans had not taken the majority. We only followed where the information has taken us. But, Hannity, this is rising to the level of impeachment inquiry, which provides Congress the strongest power to get the rest of the knowledge and information needed. Because this president has also used something we have not seen since Richard Nixon: used the weaponization of government to benefit his family and deny Congress the ability to have the oversight.” Now, to use the technical political term: them’s fightin’ words. #KevinMcCarthy  #Fox  #Politics</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7260158027020504366" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-26T20:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
