<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics</id>
  <title>pdspolitics TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-06-27T23:00:00+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/pdspolitics.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from pdspolitics</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7247541349052878122</id>
    <title>Utah’s book ban unintentionally caused the Bible to get banned in schools, too. #Bible   It was only a matter of time before book bans reached the best selling book of all time: The Holy Bible. Right, last year Utah passed a law allowing parents to reques</title>
    <updated>2023-06-22T20:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content>Utah’s book ban unintentionally caused the Bible to get banned in schools, too. #Bible   It was only a matter of time before book bans reached the best selling book of all time: The Holy Bible. Right, last year Utah passed a law allowing parents to request the removal of books containing “indecent material” from schools. But in December, one anonymous parent complained to the Davis school district, north of Salt Lake City, saying, “If the books that have been banned so far are any indication for way lesser offenses, this should be a slam dunk.So a committee reviewed the complaint and found that even though the Bible didn’t violate the law, it was nevertheless inappropriate for elementary and middle school students. So it had the book removed from all those libraries in the district, and oh boy did people lose it. With 70 people appealing the decision, and hundreds protesting both the district and the state capital for letting this happen. And even the Republican lawmaker who sponsored the book ban bill, Ken Ivory, jumping in to protest his own law. With him now arguing the review committee needs to be overseen by elected officials to make sure standards are applied properly. But last night the appeals committee voted unanimously to put the Bible back on school shelves. #Utah  #BookTok  #Politics</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7247541349052878122" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-06-22T20:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7247941854233152810</id>
    <title>Republicans censured Adam Schiff in the U.S. House and Democrats went into open revolt. #Politics  The GOP made the very major move of voting to censure Democrat Adam Schiff for his actions in the investigation into Trump’s alleged ties with Russia while </title>
    <updated>2023-06-23T20:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content>Republicans censured Adam Schiff in the U.S. House and Democrats went into open revolt. #Politics  The GOP made the very major move of voting to censure Democrat Adam Schiff for his actions in the investigation into Trump’s alleged ties with Russia while he was the Chair of the House Intelligence Committee. Normally, a censure is just a very strong and formal condemnation that doesn’t carry any tangible consequences, but this resolution also directed the Ethics Committee to open an investigation into Schiff’s behavior.  Beyond that, the censure itself is also very significant because this is very rare. In the entire history of the House, the chamber has only voted to censure its members two dozen times — and in the past 4 decades, only 2 representatives have been censured. So it makes sense that this was very divisive, with the measure passing by a narrow margin of 213-209 with all Democrats voting against and 6 Republicans voting present. And, very notably here, it only passed after another resolution to censure Schiff failed last week when 20 Republicans killed it because of a provision that would have also fined Schiff $16 million. #US  #AdamSchiff  #House</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7247941854233152810" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-06-23T20:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7247639092211551534</id>
    <title>ProPublica has discovered that Supreme Court Judge Samuel Alito failed to disclose luxury gifts from a Republican mega donor who he later heard cases for. #SupremeCourt  But this story doesn’t stop there. Alito declined ProPublica’s request for comment wh</title>
    <updated>2023-06-24T20:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content>ProPublica has discovered that Supreme Court Judge Samuel Alito failed to disclose luxury gifts from a Republican mega donor who he later heard cases for. #SupremeCourt  But this story doesn’t stop there. Alito declined ProPublica’s request for comment when the outlet sent him a detailed list of questions. But he DID respond to the allegations in a totally bizarre Wall Street Journal op-ep titled: “ProPublica Misleads Its Readers.” And I really can’t understate how weird this is for a few reasons. Right, first of all, as Slate explains: “It is rare (and may in fact be unprecedented) for a sitting court justice to attack a media outlet in print—or to engage in any kind of published advocacy at all.” But beyond that, maybe the weirdest part of all is that this op-ed was published several hours BEFORE the ProPublica report even came. #US  #Politics  #SCOTUS</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7247639092211551534" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-06-24T20:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7247924644685073707</id>
    <title>MTG &amp; Lauren Boebert just took their feud over who gets to impeach Biden to a whole new level on the House floor. #US  #MTG  #Politics  #LaurenBoebert</title>
    <updated>2023-06-25T20:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content>MTG &amp; Lauren Boebert just took their feud over who gets to impeach Biden to a whole new level on the House floor. #US  #MTG  #Politics  #LaurenBoebert</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7247924644685073707" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-06-25T20:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7249491436075371818</id>
    <title>CNN just published audio of Trump talking about taking classified documents after he left the White House #Trump  #TrumpTapes  #US  #Politics</title>
    <updated>2023-06-27T23:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content>CNN just published audio of Trump talking about taking classified documents after he left the White House #Trump  #TrumpTapes  #US  #Politics</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7249491436075371818" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-06-27T23:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
