<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics</id>
  <title>pdspolitics TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-07-23T20:00:00+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/pdspolitics.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from pdspolitics</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7257934613669055786</id>
    <title>Reports indicate that police are using Big Brother tactics to track people crossing state lines to seek gender-affirming and reproductive care #Politics  Big Brother has gone too far! That is what a group of more than three dozen lawmakers argued in a let</title>
    <updated>2023-07-20T20:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content>Reports indicate that police are using Big Brother tactics to track people crossing state lines to seek gender-affirming and reproductive care #Politics  Big Brother has gone too far! That is what a group of more than three dozen lawmakers argued in a letter urging the Biden administration to change federal laws that allow law enforcement to access sensitive medical data without a warrant. #US  #Biden  #BigBrother</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7257934613669055786" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-20T20:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7258308019056872750</id>
    <title>Wesleyan University says it will end legacy admissions following SCOTUS overturning affirmative action. #Wesleyan  Should college applicants be given a boost in admissions because a member of their family went to the same school? That’s a question many ar</title>
    <updated>2023-07-21T20:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content>Wesleyan University says it will end legacy admissions following SCOTUS overturning affirmative action. #Wesleyan  Should college applicants be given a boost in admissions because a member of their family went to the same school? That’s a question many are asking after the Supreme Court overturned Affirmative Action. So-called legacy admissions have been criticized for years now for favoring rich, white applicants over people of color. But that practice has come under even more attack since the Supreme Court decided that schools can’t consider race in admissions. And it seems like, increasingly, more and more people agree that legacy admissions are unfair. Right, top politicians on both sides of the aisle — including President Biden himself — have come out against this practice. And polls have consistently shown that the public agrees. And it seems like some schools are actually taking that to heart. Right, the reason we’re talking about this today is because the esteemed liberal arts school Wesleyan University announced that it would be ending legacy admissions. With this following in the footsteps of other selective schools that have recently made the same move including Amherst, Johns Hopkins, and Carnegie Mellon. #AffirmativeAction  #College  #Politics</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7258308019056872750" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-21T20:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7258307419556629806</id>
    <title>Democrats say Republicans in Alabama are so determined to undermine Black voters that they’re now defying the Supreme Court. #Politics  Right, last month, the conservative high court made an absolutely shocking 5-4 decision to uphold a lower court ruling </title>
    <updated>2023-07-21T23:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content>Democrats say Republicans in Alabama are so determined to undermine Black voters that they’re now defying the Supreme Court. #Politics  Right, last month, the conservative high court made an absolutely shocking 5-4 decision to uphold a lower court ruling that tossed Alabama’s Congressional map on the grounds that it discriminated against Black voters and violated the Voting Rights Act. This because, despite the fact that nearly a third of voters in the state are Black, the GOP had drawn its Congressional map so just one of the state’s 7 districts had a Black majority.  And, of course, as part of that decision, the Supreme Court directed Alabama to comply with a federal court order to re-draw the map so at least TWO districts had at least close to a majority of Black voters. But apparently, that’s too complicated for the tiny brains of the Alabama GOP. Because Republicans in both the State House and Senate passed two different maps this week — and NEITHER sets up another district Black residents make up a majority or near-majority of voters. This notably despite the fact that Democrats literally drew a map that would make another Black-majority district, but Republicans shot it down in favor of their own versions. #US  #Vote  #Politics</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7258307419556629806" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-21T23:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7258309834175434027</id>
    <title>Millions of U.S. military emails with very sensitive contents have been sent to the country Mali — a big ally of Russia and employer of the Wagner group, all because of a simple typo… #Russia  The Pentagon confirmed that instead of using the military’s do</title>
    <updated>2023-07-22T20:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content>Millions of U.S. military emails with very sensitive contents have been sent to the country Mali — a big ally of Russia and employer of the Wagner group, all because of a simple typo… #Russia  The Pentagon confirmed that instead of using the military’s domain for emails which is “.MIL” (M-I-L), people are incorrectly typing “.ML” (ML) — which is the domain for Mali. Now, notably, according to reports:  “None of the missent emails have been marked classified, but many contain highly sensitive information about American military personnel and installations, including base staff lists, medical data, and identity documents.” But still, the Dutch internet entrepreneur who has contracted to manage Mali’s country domain for the last decade told reporters that he first noticed this issue when he first started working on the domain and has tried to repeatedly warn U.S. authorities. #US  #Politics  #Military</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7258309834175434027" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-22T20:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7258317911398305067</id>
    <title>A Small Handful of Court Cases Could Decide Control of the House in 2024 #Politics  Control of the House in 2024 could be decided by a few court cases. Right, according to Axios, cases involving gerrymandering in Alabama, Louisiana, New York, North Caroli</title>
    <updated>2023-07-23T20:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content>A Small Handful of Court Cases Could Decide Control of the House in 2024 #Politics  Control of the House in 2024 could be decided by a few court cases. Right, according to Axios, cases involving gerrymandering in Alabama, Louisiana, New York, North Carolina, and Ohio “will play an outsized role in determining which party holds the House majority next year.” In Alabama, more districts that are more likely to swing blue will likely be added after the Supreme Court made a very surprising decision last month where they ruled the state had racially gerrymandered its districts and needed to redraw them. With Axios also not that the high court’s decision there “is also expected to overturn Louisiana's map and could reverberate in several other Southern states.” Meanwhile, just last week, an Appeals Court in New York sided with Democrats and ordered the state’s map to be redrawn. And while Republicans have vowed to appeal the case to the state’s highest court — which did previously strike down Democrats’ map — it is now composed of judges that are more liberal. Right, and that decision especially will be key here because New York alone could determine the majority. With Axios explaining that the GOP “can’t afford to lose more than four House seats in next year’s election,” but adding: “Republicans in 2022 won six congressional districts in New York State that President Biden carried, and even small tweaks to the map could make competitive districts unwinnable for Republicans.” But, at the same time, Republicans are also expected to gain three seats in the House in North Carolina. This after the State Supreme Court overturned its OWN past ruling making partisan gerrymandering illegal. #House  #US  #2024</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@pdspolitics/video/7258317911398305067" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-23T20:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
