<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-08-01T23:57:03+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7261691797804502314</id>
    <title>Ukraine Using North Korean Rockets To Hit Russia #ukraine #korea  Ukraine is using North Korean rockets to hit Russia. They say that a friendly nation seized them from a Russian ship and gave them to Ukraine. The friendly nation is suspected to either be </title>
    <updated>2023-07-30T19:13:12+00:00</updated>
    <content>Ukraine Using North Korean Rockets To Hit Russia #ukraine #korea  Ukraine is using North Korean rockets to hit Russia. They say that a friendly nation seized them from a Russian ship and gave them to Ukraine. The friendly nation is suspected to either be the United States or South Korea. However, Ukrainians don’t like using the rockets because they have a high dud rate because they’re North Korean and nearly 40 years old. But ammo is ammo.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7261691797804502314" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-30T19:13:12+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7261995787427826990</id>
    <title>France Puts Niger On Notice #france #niger  Protesters in Niger are attacking the French embassy. France has condemned the violence and pledged to react strongly to any attack on its nationals or interests. Since the coup, France has cut off all aid to th</title>
    <updated>2023-07-31T14:52:56+00:00</updated>
    <content>France Puts Niger On Notice #france #niger  Protesters in Niger are attacking the French embassy. France has condemned the violence and pledged to react strongly to any attack on its nationals or interests. Since the coup, France has cut off all aid to the country until the President is reinstated.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7261995787427826990" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-31T14:52:56+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7262079526224547114</id>
    <title>Is Elon Helping Russia Invade Ukraine? #ukraine #russia  Elon Musk may have just helped Russia’s invasion of Ukraine. Musk has explicitly intervened and refused to let Starlink be activated in occupied territories so Ukraine could conduct drone strikes in</title>
    <updated>2023-07-31T20:17:42+00:00</updated>
    <content>Is Elon Helping Russia Invade Ukraine? #ukraine #russia  Elon Musk may have just helped Russia’s invasion of Ukraine. Musk has explicitly intervened and refused to let Starlink be activated in occupied territories so Ukraine could conduct drone strikes in places like Crimea. Musk was concerned that such strikes would escalate the war and loss of life, even though not allowing such strikes just meant more dead Ukrainians and that ultimately such a decision was not his to make. This led to the US having to pay for specific access and control of certain Starlink systems so that Musk could get over himself and quit intervening in the war. #elonmusk #usa </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7262079526224547114" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-31T20:17:42+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7262458406756306218</id>
    <title>On The Verge Of World War: Africa #usa #france  We’re on the verge of World War: Africa. The Economic Community of West African States says that Niger has 5 days to reinstate the President or that they’ll take military force to reinstate him. With Nigeria</title>
    <updated>2023-08-01T20:48:00+00:00</updated>
    <content>On The Verge Of World War: Africa #usa #france  We’re on the verge of World War: Africa. The Economic Community of West African States says that Niger has 5 days to reinstate the President or that they’ll take military force to reinstate him. With Nigeria’s military saying that if they’re called upon to reinstate the President, they will. Saying “we will defend democracy” The US says they support ECOWAS’s attempts to reverse the military takeover. But Burkina Faso and Mali, the two neighboring juntas, say they will join the war on the side of the junta. France has begun a military evacuation of its citizens and any European who wants to leave. The U.S. has around 2,000 soldiers in the country meant to train the Nigerian military but they have suspended that mission. It’s unclear if the US and French support for the coalition will be kinetic, intelligence, or just diplomatic support. There are 5 days left on the war ultimatum</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7262458406756306218" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-01T20:48:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7262507133529345326</id>
    <title>Another Wave Of Drones Hit Moscow #ukraine #russia  Another round of drones have hit Moscow. At least one drone hit the IQ Quarter again where Russia’s digital ministry is located. The attacks closed one of Moscow’s four airports. Russia claims that Ukrai</title>
    <updated>2023-08-01T23:57:03+00:00</updated>
    <content>Another Wave Of Drones Hit Moscow #ukraine #russia  Another round of drones have hit Moscow. At least one drone hit the IQ Quarter again where Russia’s digital ministry is located. The attacks closed one of Moscow’s four airports. Russia claims that Ukraine also used naval drones to try to attack their warships but that they stopped them. It’s unclear if this is true because all they do is lie. Zelensky said earlier this week that the war is coming to Russia, a process he said was “inevitable, natural and absolutely fair.” It’s believed that the drones are being launched from the inside of Russia despite having an alleged range of 1000 kilometers. The lack of air raid sirens in Moscow has puzzled many with some wondering if the refusal to use them is to downplay the drone attacks. It does seem to at least be partially explained by Russia being potentially unable to see the drones on radar until it’s too late. However, the drones are being filmed on their flight to Moscow by civilians so one would think that visual confirmation would be enough to at least trigger the sirens. These strikes are part of Ukraine’s objective to make it clear to Russians that war is closer than they think &amp; that they can attack Moscow in hopes of causing domestic problems for Putin. Many residents of Moscow are complaining on Russian social media about the drone strikes, saying it gives them anxiety. Well at least Russians now know how their government has made Ukrainians feel every night for a year and a half.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7262507133529345326" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-01T23:57:03+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
