<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-07-22T19:38:41+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7258004349727657259</id>
    <title>North Korea Says It’ll Nuke USA #usa #korea  North Korea says that the US and South Korea have met the threshold to be hit with a nuclear strike after a U.S. nuclear submarine visited South Korea today. The US and North Korea have had better months. Just </title>
    <updated>2023-07-20T20:43:53+00:00</updated>
    <content>North Korea Says It’ll Nuke USA #usa #korea  North Korea says that the US and South Korea have met the threshold to be hit with a nuclear strike after a U.S. nuclear submarine visited South Korea today. The US and North Korea have had better months. Just this month, North Korea has threatened to shoot down US spy craft and has tested more missiles. And earlier this week a U.S. soldier ran into the country. The U.S. must not have crossed the threshold that hard given that we haven’t been nuked yet.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7258004349727657259" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-20T20:43:53+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7258393488629222698</id>
    <title>US Readies For War With Iran #usa #america  The United States is preparing for an imminent standoff with Iran. In the past two years, Iran has attacked or seized nearly 20 merchant vessels in the Persian gulf. And after it attacked 3 vessels earlier this </title>
    <updated>2023-07-21T21:54:01+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Readies For War With Iran #usa #america  The United States is preparing for an imminent standoff with Iran. In the past two years, Iran has attacked or seized nearly 20 merchant vessels in the Persian gulf. And after it attacked 3 vessels earlier this month, one of which was a US vessel, the US lost patience and deployed F-16s, F-35s, F-22s, and destroyers to the gulf. And now the US is sending an additional 2,000 marines and 3 more warships to the region. The US has been clear, don’t infringe on international shipping lanes and Iran simply doesn't care. In 1987, Iran was sinking Kuwait’s oil tankers. The US Navy began escorting Kuwait’s tankers when an Iranian mine hit a US missile ship. The US destroyed half of Iran’s navy overnight in response. And yet, 40 years later - Iran is still using the half of the Navy that wasn’t sunk to harass shipping lanes. American patience is running out especially now that Iran has detained a fourth US citizen. The message from US Central Command has been clear: we won’t hesitate to protect the flow of international commerce. In addition to a strong statement, the US has been flying A-10s over the Strait of Hormuz all week. Will Iran back down or are we gonna have another event on our hands?</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7258393488629222698" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-21T21:54:01+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7258636890633506090</id>
    <title>Poland And Belarus Are Ready To Fight #poland #russia  Poland has moved its troops to the border of Belarus due to the deployment of Wagner in the country. They’ve called the joint exercises of Belarus and Wagner a provocation. Germany says it’s prepared </title>
    <updated>2023-07-22T13:38:51+00:00</updated>
    <content>Poland And Belarus Are Ready To Fight #poland #russia  Poland has moved its troops to the border of Belarus due to the deployment of Wagner in the country. They’ve called the joint exercises of Belarus and Wagner a provocation. Germany says it’s prepared to defend Poland against Belarussian aggression. And Russia says that preparing to defend against Belarus is preparing to defend against Russia. And that they will respond to this with all means at their disposal. Putin himself said today that Poland was a gift from Stalin and that Poland has forgotten about that. Adding that Poland dreams of conquering Belarus and Ukraine.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7258636890633506090" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-22T13:38:51+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7258692381627780394</id>
    <title>Russia Buzzes Another US Plane #usa #russia  Russia has buzzed yet another US plane. Earlier this week Russia flew dangerously close to a manned US spy plane over Syria and endangered the lives of 4 Americans. This comes as Russia is attempting to break a</title>
    <updated>2023-07-22T17:13:58+00:00</updated>
    <content>Russia Buzzes Another US Plane #usa #russia  Russia has buzzed yet another US plane. Earlier this week Russia flew dangerously close to a manned US spy plane over Syria and endangered the lives of 4 Americans. This comes as Russia is attempting to break a record of harassment, after they’ve harassed the US’s drones, planes, and troops over 5 times this month by dropping fuel on them, buzzing them, and dropping flares on them. The US has urged Russia to cut it out, saying that Russia should act like a professional air force so we can resume our focus on the enduring defeat of.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7258692381627780394" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-22T17:13:58+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7258729696563596586</id>
    <title>Ukraine To Sink All Ships Going To Russia #ukraine #russia  Ukraine is now threatening a tit-for-tat against Russia after Russia threatened to sink civilian vessels traveling to Ukraine. With Ukraine now saying that all ships heading to Russia will be con</title>
    <updated>2023-07-22T19:38:41+00:00</updated>
    <content>Ukraine To Sink All Ships Going To Russia #ukraine #russia  Ukraine is now threatening a tit-for-tat against Russia after Russia threatened to sink civilian vessels traveling to Ukraine. With Ukraine now saying that all ships heading to Russia will be considered to be carrying military cargo with all corresponding risks. This comes after Russia blew up over 60,000 tons of grain meant for China in a Ukrainian port. Russia’s goal is to scare ships from going to Ukrainian ports and now Ukraine is doing the same to Russia. What a fun time to be a fisherman in the Black Sea</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7258729696563596586" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-22T19:38:41+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
