<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-11-10T20:25:17+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7298497621595917598</id>
    <title>Israel Conducts Space Combat In A Global First #usa #israel  Israel shot down a missile in space in what is the first recorded instance of space combat. With the Telegraph reporting that the missile was fired by Yemen’s Houthis, where it traveled out of t</title>
    <updated>2023-11-06T23:38:31+00:00</updated>
    <content>Israel Conducts Space Combat In A Global First #usa #israel  Israel shot down a missile in space in what is the first recorded instance of space combat. With the Telegraph reporting that the missile was fired by Yemen’s Houthis, where it traveled out of the earth’s atmosphere and was intercepted by Israel’s Arrow. Israel has suspended a cabinet minister after he suggested nuking Gaza. Iran says that the US will be hit hard if it doesn’t implement a ceasefire in Gaza. Iranian proxies have continued to attack US bases. They’ve launched at least 40 attacks on America in the past 20 days with at least 45 US troops being injured according to NBC News. The US has conducted at least two airstrikes in response and is now calling on the Iraqi government to stop Iran’s proxies from further attacks. The King of Jordan says they worked with Israel to airdrop medical supplies to a hospital in Gaza. Israel says that its ground invasion has split Gaza in half and the IDF says that it expects to enter Gaza City within the next 48 hours. In an interview, a senior Hamas leader called North Korea an ally and suggested that one day they could intervene in the conflict. This comes after AP identified Hamas using North Korean supplied weapons in the October 7th attack. France has had more than a thousand anti-Semitic incidents since October 7th according to the French interior minister. Turkish police used tear gas and water cannons to stop pro-Palestinian protesters from storming an Air Force base that houses US troops according to Reuters. </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7298497621595917598" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-11-06T23:38:31+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7298876078452395294</id>
    <title>Israel To Occupy Gaza Indefinitely #usa #israel  Israel says it will occupy Gaza indefinitely after the war. Israel hasn’t occupied Gaza since 2005. In an interview, Netanyahu said he’s open to little pauses in the war to facilitate the delivery of aid or</title>
    <updated>2023-11-08T00:07:02+00:00</updated>
    <content>Israel To Occupy Gaza Indefinitely #usa #israel  Israel says it will occupy Gaza indefinitely after the war. Israel hasn’t occupied Gaza since 2005. In an interview, Netanyahu said he’s open to little pauses in the war to facilitate the delivery of aid or to release hostages. But he ruled out a ceasefire without the release of the hostages. Hezbollah and Israel continue to exchange fire. With Hezbollah’s leader saying in an interview with NBC News that they continue to do this to alleviate pressure on Gaza. He added that those in the Axis of Resistance believe America is the mastermind, so they strike America to send a message to stop. The Axis of Resistance is Iran’s alliance of terrorists. This includes Hamas, Hezbollah, the PIJ, and about 30 other Syrian and Iraqi militias. Hezbollah’s leader also said that they would kill an Israeli civilian for every Lebanese civilian that Israel kills but when he was asked if that meant Hezbollah would be deliberately targeting civilians he said “What we will do you will see in the press, God willing. You can start counting and you will see whether or not our calculations are correct or not.” Despite all this talk though, Hezbollah has yet to enter the war despite saying they would if Israel conducted a ground invasion into Gaza. There have now been 40 attacks in the past 3 weeks on US forces in the Middle East after two attacks last night, according to the Pentagon. However, there haven’t been any injuries or damage to bases since October 26th.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7298876078452395294" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-11-08T00:07:02+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7299167817536916767</id>
    <title>Houthis Shot Down US Drone? Maybe? #usa #america  The Houthis in Yemen claim that they shot down an American drone over their territorial waters. The drone was allegedly a MQ-9 Reaper Drone and they claim it was carrying out hostilities, monitoring and sp</title>
    <updated>2023-11-08T18:59:23+00:00</updated>
    <content>Houthis Shot Down US Drone? Maybe? #usa #america  The Houthis in Yemen claim that they shot down an American drone over their territorial waters. The drone was allegedly a MQ-9 Reaper Drone and they claim it was carrying out hostilities, monitoring and spying activities. They haven’t provided any evidence for this claim and the US says as of right now, it’s not aware of any downed drones.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7299167817536916767" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-11-08T18:59:23+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7299567877344988447</id>
    <title>US Is Under Attack And It’s Striking Back #usa #america  The US is under attack and it’s striking back. Yesterday, the US struck back at Iran again after their proxies attacked US bases 46 times in 23 days. Two F-15 fighter jets conducted an airstrike on </title>
    <updated>2023-11-09T20:51:41+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Is Under Attack And It’s Striking Back #usa #america  The US is under attack and it’s striking back. Yesterday, the US struck back at Iran again after their proxies attacked US bases 46 times in 23 days. Two F-15 fighter jets conducted an airstrike on a weapons storage facility in Syria. The facility was used by Iran’s IRGC. With Biden adding that he’ll do it again if they strike the US again. Since the self-defense operation, there have been 4 more reported attacks on US forces, with 3 more Americans injured in those attacks according to US officials. Also US officials have confirmed to several outlets that the Houthis did shoot down a US drone over the Red Sea. The US says it was in international airspace when it was shot down. The Houthis have also released footage of what they claim is their shoot down of the drone. US Command is assessing the situation.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7299567877344988447" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-11-09T20:51:41+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7299932147178130718</id>
    <title>Australia &amp; China Have Absolutely Ridiculous Meeting #australia #usa  China and Australia had a meeting and their leaders were rizzing each other up. Xi told the Australian prime minister that Tasmanian devils were cute, and Albanese responded by saying t</title>
    <updated>2023-11-10T20:25:17+00:00</updated>
    <content>Australia &amp; China Have Absolutely Ridiculous Meeting #australia #usa  China and Australia had a meeting and their leaders were rizzing each other up. Xi told the Australian prime minister that Tasmanian devils were cute, and Albanese responded by saying that they weren’t as cute as Pandas. And Xi apparently said that not all Pandas are cute, citing the Kung Fu Panda movies. The two also reportedly debated wine and its quality. With Xi saying that he visited New Zealand and that the wine was good, and Albanese says he asserted that the best red wine comes from Australia. Albanese said the exchange was very warm. I heard they also sat next to each other in the booth. But so far there has been no word on if a second date will be happening.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7299932147178130718" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-11-10T20:25:17+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
