<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-07-27T21:22:40+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7259915875946450219</id>
    <title>Russian Brain Drain Boosts Neighboring Economies Big Time #russia #ukraine </title>
    <updated>2023-07-26T00:21:34+00:00</updated>
    <content>Russian Brain Drain Boosts Neighboring Economies Big Time #russia #ukraine </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7259915875946450219" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-26T00:21:34+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7260185946157567275</id>
    <title>America Has Alien Bodies?! #usa #ufo  A former intelligence officer testified in front of the United States Congress today that the US is in possession of alien bodies and UFOs. The officer claims that non-human technologies have injured humans and that t</title>
    <updated>2023-07-26T17:49:36+00:00</updated>
    <content>America Has Alien Bodies?! #usa #ufo  A former intelligence officer testified in front of the United States Congress today that the US is in possession of alien bodies and UFOs. The officer claims that non-human technologies have injured humans and that the US government became aware of Aliens in the 1930s. He also says he’s seen a video of a UFO being shot down and that the US government has a program to retrieve crashed UFOs and to reverse engineer them. He refused to say publicly if the US has communicated with aliens. He said that since coming forward about UFOs, he’s had to fear for his life. The officer also alleges that the US government is conducting a disinformation campaign targeted towards Americans about UFOs. Extraordinary claims require extraordinary amounts of evidence.. And he’s provided nothing.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7260185946157567275" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-26T17:49:36+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7260241792690392366</id>
    <title>Large Red Square Hovered Over Air Force Base #usa #america  A US Navy pilot testified in front of Congress today that in 2003 a large red square hovered over an Air Force Base which hovered for approximately 45 seconds before disappearing. The red square </title>
    <updated>2023-07-26T21:26:18+00:00</updated>
    <content>Large Red Square Hovered Over Air Force Base #usa #america  A US Navy pilot testified in front of Congress today that in 2003 a large red square hovered over an Air Force Base which hovered for approximately 45 seconds before disappearing. The red square was supposedly the size of a football field. He said that UFOs are commonly a black square or a black cube inside of a clear sphere. He also said that he’s talked to two navy pilots who nearly hit a dark gray black cube inside of a clear sphere with no wings</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7260241792690392366" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-26T21:26:18+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7260588859367394602</id>
    <title>Russia Attacks 6th US Drone #usa #russia  For the 6th time this month and the 2nd time in 24 hours, a Russian jet has attacked a U.S. drone. The Russian jet fired flares at the drone which struck the main body of the drone, severely damaging it. Russia cl</title>
    <updated>2023-07-27T19:53:07+00:00</updated>
    <content>Russia Attacks 6th US Drone #usa #russia  For the 6th time this month and the 2nd time in 24 hours, a Russian jet has attacked a U.S. drone. The Russian jet fired flares at the drone which struck the main body of the drone, severely damaging it. Russia claims the drone was being highly provocative. And the US statement is the same as last time which is essentially “Russia needs to grow up”. Commanders reportedly exchanged angry threats over the deconfliction hotline afterwards. The U.S. has now deployed even more F-35s to the region as their patience begins to run thin.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7260588859367394602" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-27T19:53:07+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7260611914802236714</id>
    <title>Ireland Says They Wouldn’t Care If Putin Died #ireland #russia  Ireland says that they wouldn’t offer condolences to Russia if Putin died and that they wouldn’t send a delegation to go to his funeral. This is like the global politics version of this</title>
    <updated>2023-07-27T21:22:40+00:00</updated>
    <content>Ireland Says They Wouldn’t Care If Putin Died #ireland #russia  Ireland says that they wouldn’t offer condolences to Russia if Putin died and that they wouldn’t send a delegation to go to his funeral. This is like the global politics version of this</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7260611914802236714" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-27T21:22:40+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
