<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-11-15T14:15:29+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7299567877344988447</id>
    <title>US Is Under Attack And It’s Striking Back #usa #america  The US is under attack and it’s striking back. Yesterday, the US struck back at Iran again after their proxies attacked US bases 46 times in 23 days. Two F-15 fighter jets conducted an airstrike on </title>
    <updated>2023-11-09T20:51:41+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Is Under Attack And It’s Striking Back #usa #america  The US is under attack and it’s striking back. Yesterday, the US struck back at Iran again after their proxies attacked US bases 46 times in 23 days. Two F-15 fighter jets conducted an airstrike on a weapons storage facility in Syria. The facility was used by Iran’s IRGC. With Biden adding that he’ll do it again if they strike the US again. Since the self-defense operation, there have been 4 more reported attacks on US forces, with 3 more Americans injured in those attacks according to US officials. Also US officials have confirmed to several outlets that the Houthis did shoot down a US drone over the Red Sea. The US says it was in international airspace when it was shot down. The Houthis have also released footage of what they claim is their shoot down of the drone. US Command is assessing the situation.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7299567877344988447" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-11-09T20:51:41+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7299932147178130718</id>
    <title>Australia &amp; China Have Absolutely Ridiculous Meeting #australia #usa  China and Australia had a meeting and their leaders were rizzing each other up. Xi told the Australian prime minister that Tasmanian devils were cute, and Albanese responded by saying t</title>
    <updated>2023-11-10T20:25:17+00:00</updated>
    <content>Australia &amp; China Have Absolutely Ridiculous Meeting #australia #usa  China and Australia had a meeting and their leaders were rizzing each other up. Xi told the Australian prime minister that Tasmanian devils were cute, and Albanese responded by saying that they weren’t as cute as Pandas. And Xi apparently said that not all Pandas are cute, citing the Kung Fu Panda movies. The two also reportedly debated wine and its quality. With Xi saying that he visited New Zealand and that the wine was good, and Albanese says he asserted that the best red wine comes from Australia. Albanese said the exchange was very warm. I heard they also sat next to each other in the booth. But so far there has been no word on if a second date will be happening.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7299932147178130718" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-11-10T20:25:17+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7301079848355630367</id>
    <title>US Upset With Israel As It Strikes Back At Iran &amp; Warns Hezbollah #usa #israel  The US is at least mildly pissed at Israel according to Axios. Yesterday the Pentagon’s chief called his Israeli counterpart to issue a warning about trying to provoke a war w</title>
    <updated>2023-11-13T22:38:54+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Upset With Israel As It Strikes Back At Iran &amp; Warns Hezbollah #usa #israel  The US is at least mildly pissed at Israel according to Axios. Yesterday the Pentagon’s chief called his Israeli counterpart to issue a warning about trying to provoke a war with Hezbollah because the US believes that this will cause a regional war that will draw the US and several other countries into the conflict. Israel flatly denies that this conversation happened but Axios says their sources in both countries claim the call was very direct and frank. The US conducted another round of airstrikes in Eastern Syria on bases used by Iranian proxies and the http://IRGC.US Forces have been attacked 4 times by Iranian proxies since the airstrikes yesterday. There have now been at least 50 attacks on US forces since October 17th according to the Pentagon. The New York Times reported that President Biden has rejected more aggressive bombing options proposed by the Pentagon in hopes of not escalating into a war with Iran. With some now saying his hands are looking to be increasingly tied after today’s attacks. The Biden administration sent an advisor to Lebanon last week to deliver a warning to Hezbollah via Lebanon's parliament according to VOA. The warning was to not escalate the conflict. The advisor reportedly returned to America with the impression that Hezbollah wasn’t interested in an actual war, Axios alleges. Despite this, Israel and Hezbollah keep climbing the escalation ladder with each other, hoping one will give up. The White House was reportedly alarmed by two incidents that looked like they could escalate the conflict. If the Fish continues to plagiarize us, he will be struck down.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7301079848355630367" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-11-13T22:38:54+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7301388553676655903</id>
    <title>Bernie Sanders Breaks Up Fight In US Senate #usa #america  Sen. Markwayne Mullin (R-OK) challenges Teamsters leader Sean O’Brien to a physical fight, standing up midway through a Senate HELP Committee hearing. Chair Bernie Sanders (I-VT) repeatedly attemp</title>
    <updated>2023-11-14T18:36:59+00:00</updated>
    <content>Bernie Sanders Breaks Up Fight In US Senate #usa #america  Sen. Markwayne Mullin (R-OK) challenges Teamsters leader Sean O’Brien to a physical fight, standing up midway through a Senate HELP Committee hearing. Chair Bernie Sanders (I-VT) repeatedly attempts to break them up: “You’re a United States senator.” Mullin and O’Brien, the leader of the major union International Brotherhood of Teamsters, have a history of combative moments — Mullin, a hard-right conservative, has repeatedly challenged O’Brien to physical fights.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7301388553676655903" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-11-14T18:36:59+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7301692282800000286</id>
    <title>Senator Challenges Witness To Charity Boxing Match #usa #america  A congressional hearing devolved into an angry confrontation between a senator and a witness on Tuesday after Republican Sen. Markwayne Mullin of Oklahoma challenged Sean O’Brien, the presi</title>
    <updated>2023-11-15T14:15:29+00:00</updated>
    <content>Senator Challenges Witness To Charity Boxing Match #usa #america  A congressional hearing devolved into an angry confrontation between a senator and a witness on Tuesday after Republican Sen. Markwayne Mullin of Oklahoma challenged Sean O’Brien, the president of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters, to “stand your butt up” and settle longstanding differences right there in the room. Vermont Sen. Bernie Sanders, the chairman of the Senate panel that was holding the hearing, yelled at Mullin to sit down after he challenged O’Brien to a fight. Mullin had stood up from his seat at the dais and appeared to start taking his ring off. “This is the time, this is the place,” Mullin told O’Brien after reading a series of critical tweets O’Brien had sent about him in the past. “If you want to run your mouth, we can be two consenting adults. We can finish it here.” The two men never came face to face in the hearing room. But they hurled insults at each other for around six minutes as Sanders repeatedly banged his gavel and tried to cut them off. Sanders, a longtime union ally, pleaded with them to focus on the economic issues that were the focus of the Senate Health, Education, Labor and Pensions Committee hearing, which Sanders was holding to review how unions help working families.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7301692282800000286" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-11-15T14:15:29+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
