<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-10-09T17:36:14+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7287310028124491050</id>
    <title>Israel Says It’s Going To Change Gaza Forever #usa #israel  Israel has cut all power to Gaza as it begins its operation.More than 250 Israelis have reportedly been killed and over 1,500 have been wounded, both numbers are expected to grow drastically. Pal</title>
    <updated>2023-10-07T20:04:56+00:00</updated>
    <content>Israel Says It’s Going To Change Gaza Forever #usa #israel  Israel has cut all power to Gaza as it begins its operation.More than 250 Israelis have reportedly been killed and over 1,500 have been wounded, both numbers are expected to grow drastically. Palestine says at least 232 people have been killed in Israel’s retaliation. With Israel saying it’s going to change the face of reality in Gaza for the next 50 years. Adding “what was, will be no more”. Palestine has reportedly asked France to intervene to stop what it calls “Israeli aggression” - France has declined. A 12 year old and a 16 year old are reportedly among the hostages Hamas took back into Gaza. Massive rocket barrages are repeatedly being launched at Tel Aviv from Gaza and there are several reports of civilians being hit. There are reports that the Iron Dome seems to not be operating correctly or is perhaps overwhelmed. Israel has reportedly bombed the home of the leader of Hamas. Hamas says it’s expanding the war to the West Bank. President Biden in a national address said the United States stands with Israel and will ensure that they have what they need.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7287310028124491050" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-07T20:04:56+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7287626904465657130</id>
    <title>Israel To Turn Gaza “To Rubble” #usa #israel  Israel has called on all Palestinian civilians to immediately leave Gaza before it turns it into rubble. Israel is beginning a naval bombardment of Gaza while it conducts a massive airstrike campaign. Israeli </title>
    <updated>2023-10-08T16:34:42+00:00</updated>
    <content>Israel To Turn Gaza “To Rubble” #usa #israel  Israel has called on all Palestinian civilians to immediately leave Gaza before it turns it into rubble. Israel is beginning a naval bombardment of Gaza while it conducts a massive airstrike campaign. Israeli tanks have reportedly been moved to the border and are reportedly considering destroying Gaza’s water supply as well as cutting it off from Egypt so supplies can’t come in. At least 600 Israelis were killed in yesterday’s terror attack, this number is expected to grow into the thousands. This is the largest number of Jews murdered in a single day since the Holocaust. Also over 2,000 Israelis are injured. At least 370 Palestines have been killed in Israel’s retaliation with another 2,200 injured. There are also reports of several Americans dead and dozens have reportedly been taken hostage. Local media is reporting that the amount of death in the cities being liberated from Hamas is unbearable. There are horrifying stories coming out of the country. Twenty police officers were reportedly massacred in a police station by Hamas, at least a dozen people were killed at a nature party, and Hamas also surrounded a rave in the desert where they began massacring at least 250 people. At that Rave, Hamas kidnapped and then murdered a 22 year old German peace activist before parading her dead body through the streets. Her credit card was also used in Gaza after she was killed. To say German media is ‘foaming at the mouth mad’ would be an understatement. Also one of the people kidnapped by Hamas was a holocaust survivor.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7287626904465657130" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-08T16:34:42+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7287825716190694702</id>
    <title>Israel To “Level” Gaza #usa #israel  Israel has called on all Palestinian civilians to immediately leave Gaza before it turns it into rubble. Israel is beginning a naval bombardment of Gaza while it conducts a massive airstrike campaign. Israeli tanks hav</title>
    <updated>2023-10-09T05:26:04+00:00</updated>
    <content>Israel To “Level” Gaza #usa #israel  Israel has called on all Palestinian civilians to immediately leave Gaza before it turns it into rubble. Israel is beginning a naval bombardment of Gaza while it conducts a massive airstrike campaign. Israeli tanks have reportedly been moved to the border and are reportedly considering destroying Gaza’s water supply as well as cutting it off from Egypt so supplies can’t come in. At least 600 Israelis were killed in yesterday’s terror attack, this number is expected to grow into the thousands. This is the largest number of Jews murdered in a single day since the Holocaust. Also over 2,000 Israelis are injured. At least 370 Palestines have been killed in Israel’s retaliation with another 2,200 injured. There are also reports of several Americans dead and dozens have reportedly been taken hostage. Local media is reporting that the amount of death in the cities being liberated from Hamas is unbearable. There are horrifying stories coming out of the country. Twenty police officers were reportedly massacred in a police station by Hamas, at least a dozen people were killed at a nature party, and Hamas also surrounded a rave in the desert where they began massacring at least 250 people. At that Rave, Hamas kidnapped and then murdered a 22 year old German peace activist before parading her dead body through the streets. Her credit card was also used in Gaza after she was killed. To say German media is ‘foaming at the mouth mad’ would be an understatement. Also one of the people kidnapped by Hamas was a holocaust survivor.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7287825716190694702" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-09T05:26:04+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7287836874511682862</id>
    <title>US Will Defend Israel #usa #israel  Iran helped plan Saturday’s terrorist attack on Israel and gave the green light for the attack, they’re also believed to have paid for it. The US says Hamas and Iran likely committed these terrorist attacks to destroy t</title>
    <updated>2023-10-09T06:09:25+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Will Defend Israel #usa #israel  Iran helped plan Saturday’s terrorist attack on Israel and gave the green light for the attack, they’re also believed to have paid for it. The US says Hamas and Iran likely committed these terrorist attacks to destroy the prospect of Palestinian statehood and normalization between Israel and Saudi Arabia. In response to the terror attacks on Israel, the United States has deployed the USS Gerald Ford aircraft carrier, four destroyers, and a guided missile cruiser off the coast of Israel. They have also moved additional F-35s, F-15s, F-16s, and A-10s to the region to support Israel. This was done to send a message to Iran and Hezbollah that they will defend Israel if they invade. Hamas has reportedly warned the United States about the consequences of doing this and says the presence of a US aircraft carrier doesn’t scare them. More than 700 Israelis were killed in the attacks, again this number is expected to grow. France has reportedly called on Hamas to release their hostages immediately while Saudi has condemned the killing of innocent civilians by Hamas.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7287836874511682862" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-09T06:09:25+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7288013889499942186</id>
    <title>Israel To Begin Total Siege Of Gaza #usa #israel  Israel has announced the total siege of Gaza. Saying “there will be no electricity, no food, no fuel. We are fighting human animals and we will act accordingly.” They’ve also reportedly cut off Gaza’s wate</title>
    <updated>2023-10-09T17:36:14+00:00</updated>
    <content>Israel To Begin Total Siege Of Gaza #usa #israel  Israel has announced the total siege of Gaza. Saying “there will be no electricity, no food, no fuel. We are fighting human animals and we will act accordingly.” They’ve also reportedly cut off Gaza’s water supply. Adding that “this is a war for our existence and we will do things never seen before”. Israel has reportedly told the United States that it will conduct a ground invasion of Gaza, and they have so far mobilized over 300,000 soldiers. Gaza is currently under very intense bombing, with Israel hitting over a hundred targets an hour. The bombing is only expected to increase in intensity. There are reports of entire city blocks being destroyed. At least 1,000 Israelis have been killed as of recording in Hamas’ terror attacks. And at least 9 Americans were reportedly killed in the attacks as well, with several more still held hostage. At least 560 Palestinians have died in Israel’s return strikes with an additional 2,900 wounded. There are reports of clashing between Israel and the P-I-J on their border with Lebanon. Israel is reportedly cooperating with the US military for this operation, with Israel saying that if there are attempts by Iranian proxies to act, it may lead to an attack from America  The EU has suspended all aid payments to Palestine. Saying that the scale of terror and brutality against Israel and its people is a turning point.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7288013889499942186" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-09T17:36:14+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
