<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-10-07T15:44:53+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7286191953404841259</id>
    <title>Israel &amp; Saudi Arabia Mad At US For Trying To Protect Palestine #usa #israel #saudiarabia  Israel and Saudi Arabia are reportedly frustrated with the United States over its insistence on Palestine. The US and Saudi are negotiating a defense pact that in o</title>
    <updated>2023-10-04T19:46:22+00:00</updated>
    <content>Israel &amp; Saudi Arabia Mad At US For Trying To Protect Palestine #usa #israel #saudiarabia  Israel and Saudi Arabia are reportedly frustrated with the United States over its insistence on Palestine. The US and Saudi are negotiating a defense pact that in order to go through requires Israel and Saudi to normalize relations with each other; but the US requires that Palestine be given a pathway to statehood in that normalization deal. This has made the two other countries rather annoyed. Saudi wants a NATO-like pledge from the US to defend the Kingdom but the US isn’t so sure given Saudi’s rampant history of human rights abuses &amp; 9/11. The US would rather just make Saudi a Major Non-NATO ally instead.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7286191953404841259" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-04T19:46:22+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7286535008242748715</id>
    <title>US F-16 Shoots Down Turkish Drone #usa #turkey  A US Fighter Jet just shot down a Turkish drone in Syria after it was deemed a threat to US forces today in a very rare NATO-on-NATO clash. Turkey denies that it was their drone but the US says it was an arm</title>
    <updated>2023-10-05T17:57:50+00:00</updated>
    <content>US F-16 Shoots Down Turkish Drone #usa #turkey  A US Fighter Jet just shot down a Turkish drone in Syria after it was deemed a threat to US forces today in a very rare NATO-on-NATO clash. Turkey denies that it was their drone but the US says it was an armed Turkish drone, and that it was aware of that before it acted. The drone came too close to US Forces who were conducting operations in the area and the US acted in self-defense after Turkey failed to answer their calls.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7286535008242748715" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-05T17:57:50+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7286593689713954090</id>
    <title>Turkey Unfazed By America’s Warning #usa #america  Turkey says its unfazed by the US shooting down its drone, and will continue its bombings of Kurdish infrastructure in Iraq and Syria. Turkey was conducting airstrikes a half kilometer away from US forces</title>
    <updated>2023-10-05T21:45:12+00:00</updated>
    <content>Turkey Unfazed By America’s Warning #usa #america  Turkey says its unfazed by the US shooting down its drone, and will continue its bombings of Kurdish infrastructure in Iraq and Syria. Turkey was conducting airstrikes a half kilometer away from US forces in a US restricted zone when the US acted in self-defense and shot down their drone. The US says it was a regrettable incident but some analysts say.. Look it’s not everyday the US shoots down a NATO drone, so they’re also sending a message to Turkey to quit. But Turkey is clearly not receiving that message. However, the US and Turkey seem to have worked it out with the Pentagon saying that the Turkish drone wasn’t being threatening, it was just where it shouldn’t have been. Adding that Turkey is one of America’s favorite allies.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7286593689713954090" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-05T21:45:12+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7286937417293040938</id>
    <title>Turkey Calls US “Tremendously Stupid” #usa #turkey  Turkey says it won’t bow to threats after the US shot down its drone. They also called the US partnership with the Kurds “tremendously stupid”. Turkey said that it strongly told America to stop working w</title>
    <updated>2023-10-06T19:59:05+00:00</updated>
    <content>Turkey Calls US “Tremendously Stupid” #usa #turkey  Turkey says it won’t bow to threats after the US shot down its drone. They also called the US partnership with the Kurds “tremendously stupid”. Turkey said that it strongly told America to stop working with them. Adding that they won’t let the United States get in the way of their counter terror campaign</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7286937417293040938" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-06T19:59:05+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7287242991226441006</id>
    <title>Israel Has Been Invaded, Now At War #israel #usa  Israel has been invaded and is at war. Hamas just launched a massive sneak attack on Israel and has invaded the country via land, air, and sea. The terrorists have reportedly captured and are occupying sev</title>
    <updated>2023-10-07T15:44:53+00:00</updated>
    <content>Israel Has Been Invaded, Now At War #israel #usa  Israel has been invaded and is at war. Hamas just launched a massive sneak attack on Israel and has invaded the country via land, air, and sea. The terrorists have reportedly captured and are occupying several cities in Israel and are reportedly indiscriminately killing civilians in those cities. Israel says at least 100 Israelis have been killed and at least a thousand are injured, these numbers are expected to grow. There are reports that at least 100 Israelis have been kidnapped and are being held as hostages. Some of which have allegedly been brought back to Gaza and Hamas is reportedly threatening to execute them. And reports say that more than 5,000 rockets have been fired at Israel. Hamas claims its captured senior Israel officers, including a former general. This is a very sophisticated attack and the timing is reportedly intentional as today is the 50th anniversary of the Yom Kippur war. Israel has promised a biblical response, adding that Hamas has opened the gates of hell.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7287242991226441006" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-07T15:44:53+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
