<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-09-11T22:48:49+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7275825668666051882</id>
    <title>Romania Notifies NATO Of Russian Attack On Country #romania #usa  Romania has found the Russian drone that they denied hit them. With the Romanian defense minister saying: “If it is confirmed that these elements come from a Russian drone, such a situation</title>
    <updated>2023-09-06T21:19:48+00:00</updated>
    <content>Romania Notifies NATO Of Russian Attack On Country #romania #usa  Romania has found the Russian drone that they denied hit them. With the Romanian defense minister saying: “If it is confirmed that these elements come from a Russian drone, such a situation would be completely inadmissible and a serious violation of the sovereignty and territorial integrity of Romania, a NATO member.” It’s unclear what Romania’s retaliation will be but they did notify NATO today of the attack. Romania could technically invoke NATO’s Article 5 if they want to but are we really gonna do this over a drone hitting an empty field?</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7275825668666051882" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-06T21:19:48+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7276169703960186154</id>
    <title>Man Arrested After Trying To Hamster Wheel To London #usa #london #florida  A Florida man crossing the Atlantic Ocean in a hamster wheel has been arrested after a three day stand off. The man set off from Florida and intended to go to London by running on</title>
    <updated>2023-09-07T19:34:48+00:00</updated>
    <content>Man Arrested After Trying To Hamster Wheel To London #usa #london #florida  A Florida man crossing the Atlantic Ocean in a hamster wheel has been arrested after a three day stand off. The man set off from Florida and intended to go to London by running on the wheel but 70 miles into his journey - the Coast Guard stopped him. Now you’re probably wondering “where in the law does it say it’s illegal to hamster wheel across the ocean”. And look it might not be illegal, but the issue is that our Hero went rogue when the Coast Guard approached his wheel. He was finally arrested after a 3 day standoff and has been charged with obstructing a boarding and violation of a Captain of the Port order. BUT It turns out this is his 4th time attempting this and in 2002, he was arrested trying to illegally enter the US. But the Judge let him off and granted him asylum after he promised to run from LA to New York City to commemorate the second anniversary of 9/11. He was set free on $250,000 bond with the terms that he can’t go into the ocean or board a vessel on the ocean.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7276169703960186154" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-07T19:34:48+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7276187616238718254</id>
    <title>Hong Kong Experiencing Apocalyptic Floods #hongkong #china  Hong Kong is experiencing apocalyptic floods. In just one hour, it rained 6 inches. That’s the most since records began in 1884. Buses are flooding, The subways are flooding, and you could take b</title>
    <updated>2023-09-07T20:44:22+00:00</updated>
    <content>Hong Kong Experiencing Apocalyptic Floods #hongkong #china  Hong Kong is experiencing apocalyptic floods. In just one hour, it rained 6 inches. That’s the most since records began in 1884. Buses are flooding, The subways are flooding, and you could take boats down these streets because they’re being turned into rivers. It’s so bad that cars in the street are being forced to a total stop by the water.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7276187616238718254" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-07T20:44:22+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7277647637254393131</id>
    <title>US Gains New Ally Thanks To Kim Kardashian #usa #kimkardashian  The U.S. just gained a new ally, thanks to Kim Kardashian. Armenia and the U.S. are conducting an unprecedented joint army exercise for the first time. Russia says it’ll be watching closely. </title>
    <updated>2023-09-11T19:10:01+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Gains New Ally Thanks To Kim Kardashian #usa #kimkardashian  The U.S. just gained a new ally, thanks to Kim Kardashian. Armenia and the U.S. are conducting an unprecedented joint army exercise for the first time. Russia says it’ll be watching closely. Armenia is an odd bird. It really has no friends except the US and depending on the day, Iran. And that’s primarily because the Armenian lobby in the US is very influential. With Kim Kardashian being the loudest pro-Armenian voice and her asking President Biden to prevent another Armenian genocide. Armenia’s lack of friends is really because of Russia. After Russia’s invasion of Ukraine, Europe came to depend on Azerbaijan for gas and now that Russia lacks the ability to protect Armenia, it has only emboldened the Azeris on territory grabs. You know it’s bleak when up until today, your only friends were Kim Kardashian and like sometimes Iran.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7277647637254393131" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-11T19:10:01+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7277704037972249902</id>
    <title>Saudi Arabia Has Paid Off Vice News #vice #saudiarabia  Vice News, they were someone you could count on to give you the news that no one else was willing to cover… they have fallen. After striking a deal with a State-run Saudi Arabian media company, Vice </title>
    <updated>2023-09-11T22:48:49+00:00</updated>
    <content>Saudi Arabia Has Paid Off Vice News #vice #saudiarabia  Vice News, they were someone you could count on to give you the news that no one else was willing to cover… they have fallen. After striking a deal with a State-run Saudi Arabian media company, Vice removed their documentary that was critical of the Saudi Crown Prince. The documentary revealed how MBS orchestrates purges, kidnaps Saudi elites and tortured them, and how he killed Jamal Khashoggi. The video they removed was from June of this year but Vice’s ties to Saudi Arabia go way back. In 2018, Vice started making promotional videos for the Kingdom after Saudi gave them $200 million from the sovereign wealth fund. In 2020, they helped organize a Saudi music festival that was paid for by the Saudi government &amp; Vice hid their involvement. In 2021, they opened an office in Riyadh after previously being banned from the country. Now they’re actively seeking producers for their “new media brand” that’s headquartered in the country. Vice claims that they have full control over editorial but that seems to be a flagrant lie. This year, Vice entered into another deal with a Saudi media company and after doing so they reportedly canned a story on how Saudi Arabia was helping families harass and threaten transgender Saudis living overseas.  With the Vice Union saying that just cause the company is bankrupt financially doesn’t mean it should also be morally bankrupt. The icing on the cake here is that in Vice headquarters in London, there is reportedly a map of Saudi Arabia on the wall.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7277704037972249902" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-11T22:48:49+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
