<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-11-29T20:56:32+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7303706080247434526</id>
    <title>US Prepares To Sanction Israel #usa #israel  The US is preparing to sanction Israel. President Biden wrote in an Op-Ed that the US is preparing to issue visa bans against extremist settlers in the West Bank who are attacking and displacing Palestinians. W</title>
    <updated>2023-11-21T00:29:57+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Prepares To Sanction Israel #usa #israel  The US is preparing to sanction Israel. President Biden wrote in an Op-Ed that the US is preparing to issue visa bans against extremist settlers in the West Bank who are attacking and displacing Palestinians. While officials backed up that op-ed and told Politico that they are also preparing sanctions. President Biden also said that the Gaza strip and West Bank should be reunited and be governed under a revitalized Palestinian Authority. The US continues to publicly oppose an Israeli occupation of Gaza after the war is over.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7303706080247434526" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-11-21T00:29:57+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7306216189510896927</id>
    <title>US Navy Captures Pirates #usa #america  The US Navy captured 5 attackers who were engaging in piracy yesterday, US Central command said in a statement. A ship named Central Park which was carrying phosphoric acid issued distress calls that they were under</title>
    <updated>2023-11-27T18:50:43+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Navy Captures Pirates #usa #america  The US Navy captured 5 attackers who were engaging in piracy yesterday, US Central command said in a statement. A ship named Central Park which was carrying phosphoric acid issued distress calls that they were under attack by an unknown entity - according to Central Command. The USS Mason and other allied ships from a counter-piracy task force responded and demanded the release of the vessel, Central Command alleges. According to their version of events, the 5 armed attackers left the ship after the warning - attempting to flee, the Mason chased them resulting in their surrender. The Pentagon says that the 5 attackers were Somali and not Houthis, and that the incident was piracy related. Also alleging that 3 Chinese Navy vessels were in the vicinity but didn’t respond to the 59 distress calls. Not long after, Central Command claims that two ballistic missiles were fired from a Houthi controlled area toward the general location of the Mason. The missiles missed by 11 miles and didn’t need interception, according to Central Command.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7306216189510896927" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-11-27T18:50:43+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7306258991045201183</id>
    <title>India Plotted To Kill American #usa #india  India was allegedly plotting to kill an American citizen in the United States according to U.S. officials. The US claims it thwarted a plot to assassinate a Sikh separatist on American Soil and that it had issue</title>
    <updated>2023-11-27T21:36:38+00:00</updated>
    <content>India Plotted To Kill American #usa #india  India was allegedly plotting to kill an American citizen in the United States according to U.S. officials. The US claims it thwarted a plot to assassinate a Sikh separatist on American Soil and that it had issued a warning to India’s government. The target, according to the Financial Times, was the general counsel for Sikhs for Justice. It’s currently unknown if the US warning to India led the plotters to abandon their plan, or whether the FBI intervened and foiled the scheme already in motion. Federal prosecutors have filed a sealed indictment against one of the perpetrators of the plot according to the Financial Times. The White House says that India expressed surprise and concern when they were warned by the President.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7306258991045201183" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-11-27T21:36:38+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7306700013411831071</id>
    <title>India rescues workers trapped for over a week after breaking through debris #india #rescue  With how the world has been going lately, I know it feels like we never have any good news. But this time I do have some: Officials in India announced that they’ve</title>
    <updated>2023-11-29T02:08:01+00:00</updated>
    <content>India rescues workers trapped for over a week after breaking through debris #india #rescue  With how the world has been going lately, I know it feels like we never have any good news. But this time I do have some: Officials in India announced that they’ve rescued 41 construction workers who were trapped for over a week underground. The 41 men were working on the $1.5 billion Char Dam highway, which is meant to connect four Hindu pilgrimage sites and is one of Prime Minister Narendra Modi’s prized projects. However, while digging through the Himalayas, the tunnel collapsed and trapped the men for 17 days. It’s unclear what exactly caused the collapse, but the mountainous region is well-known for earthquakes, floods, and landslides. The 41 managed to stay alive for so long because rescue crews drilled little passageways into the chamber and pumped in oxygen, water, and food. At the same time, crews were working around the clock to open up a passage big enough to get the men out. They tried various methods, but the one that proved to be the most effective -- despite many snags along the way -- was to just drill through the debris that was blocking the tunnel. Eventually a 3-foot-wide pipe connected the workers to the outside. Initial reports indicated that a wheeled stretcher was sent to them to help them out, But according to the chief minister of the local state, the workers preferred to crawl out on their own. That was a good indication of their health, as the minister added they were all healthy. Crews and locals celebrated each time a man came out of the tunnel, although the rescued workers didn’t get to stay long as they were sent away on ambulances to make sure they were fine. Reportedly, the workers are getting $1,200 for their ordeal. Which isn’t a lot, but at the same time these workers are from India’s poorest states and working a low-paying job. It ends up that the $1,200 is about equal to 6-months of the average salary in the state. So that $1,200 is actually quite a bit for them. (I vote they get more). The real kicker though is that the local chief minister had to ask that “the company that these 41 workers be allowed to go home and spend time with their family for 15 days, 20 days, or 1 month.” So there’s a chance they may only get a little time off for their troubles. But what if that was you? Would you be going back to that tunnel?</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7306700013411831071" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-11-29T02:08:01+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7306990804239764766</id>
    <title>Saudi Offers Iran A Deal They Can’t Refuse #usa #saudiarabia  Saudi Arabia has approached Iran with a deal that they might not be able to refuse. Saudi, according to Bloomberg, has approached Iran with an offer to boost cooperation and investments to its </title>
    <updated>2023-11-29T20:56:32+00:00</updated>
    <content>Saudi Offers Iran A Deal They Can’t Refuse #usa #saudiarabia  Saudi Arabia has approached Iran with a deal that they might not be able to refuse. Saudi, according to Bloomberg, has approached Iran with an offer to boost cooperation and investments to its sanctioned economy if they stop their proxies from turning the Israel-Hamas war into a wider conflict. At the same time though, Saudi Arabia is also pursuing another path with the US. With US Assistant Secretary of State Barbara Leaf saying the US is working with them and their Arab allies to stop Iran from weaponizing the Israel-Hamas war to strengthen its axis of resistance. This is a continuation of Saudi’s two-pronged approach to foreign affairs - they’re trying to deepen ties with Iran and deescalate with them while trying to normalize ties with Israel, achieve a two state solution, and get a defense alliance with the US. Bloomberg writes that it’s unclear how serious Iran is taking Saudi’s offer but that a regional war has been averted so far. Saudi’s main fear is that once this ceasefire ends - Israel will once again ignite the region in anger, making its goal of normalizing with Israel harder to achieve.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7306990804239764766" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-11-29T20:56:32+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
