<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-09-06T18:49:50+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7275106644634176811</id>
    <title>France Bans Muslim Dresses In Schools #france #islam  France says it’ll be uncompromising in its ban on abayas in school. An Abaya is usually a dark cloak worn by Muslim women. The French education minister says “When you walk into a classroom, you should</title>
    <updated>2023-09-04T22:49:33+00:00</updated>
    <content>France Bans Muslim Dresses In Schools #france #islam  France says it’ll be uncompromising in its ban on abayas in school. An Abaya is usually a dark cloak worn by Muslim women. The French education minister says “When you walk into a classroom, you shouldn't be able to identify a student’s religion just by looking at them” Some critics have called it discriminatory because Abayas aren’t inherently religious, they’re just a kind of dress. But Macron says French schools are secular and that teachers must enforce the ban. All religious attire and symbols are banned in French schools. Which is quite the difference from America. Here, our secularism is based on freedom of religion. It’s very individual, it’s part of the “be who you want to be” motto of America. While in France, their secularism is based on freedom from religion. It’s based on this belief that there is a collective freedom from religious institutions. It’s an interesting approach.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7275106644634176811" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-04T22:49:33+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7275435734398405930</id>
    <title>India Is Changing Its Name To Bharat #india #bharat  India may be changing its name! A special session in parliament may rename the country to Bharat. Bharat is already the name most Indians call India so renaming it would be like Germany changing their n</title>
    <updated>2023-09-05T20:06:31+00:00</updated>
    <content>India Is Changing Its Name To Bharat #india #bharat  India may be changing its name! A special session in parliament may rename the country to Bharat. Bharat is already the name most Indians call India so renaming it would be like Germany changing their name to Deutschland or Japan becoming Nippon. It’s common for places to have their own name and a name that everyone else calls them. For instance: China calls America a name that means “The United States of Beauty, Advantage and Endurance” And we call China “China” which is thought to mean “Land of the Qins”.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7275435734398405930" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-05T20:06:31+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7275456711706561838</id>
    <title>Russia Wants Alliance With North Korea &amp; China #russia #korea  South Korea says that Russia has proposed a three way with North Korea and China. Under Russia’s proposal, the three of them would conduct naval exercises together. Last time, Russia and China</title>
    <updated>2023-09-05T21:27:58+00:00</updated>
    <content>Russia Wants Alliance With North Korea &amp; China #russia #korea  South Korea says that Russia has proposed a three way with North Korea and China. Under Russia’s proposal, the three of them would conduct naval exercises together. Last time, Russia and China got together for an exercise, they just did their own thing next to each other and called it a joint exercise which is not what that is. Also North Korea and Russia are currently negotiating an arms deal. 6 years ago, Russia told North Korea that if the U.S. nukes them that they’ll be justified in doing so and will have no one to blame but themselves. Now Russia is making the nuclear threats they denounced and is becoming friends with the hermit kingdom.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7275456711706561838" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-05T21:27:58+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7275506222642695470</id>
    <title>US Places Nuclear Weapons In Britain #usa #uk  The U.S. may return it’s nuclear weapons to British soil for the first time in 15 years. The Air Force has secured funding to build a dormitory to house increased personnel due to a potential nuclear mission.</title>
    <updated>2023-09-06T00:40:05+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Places Nuclear Weapons In Britain #usa #uk  The U.S. may return it’s nuclear weapons to British soil for the first time in 15 years. The Air Force has secured funding to build a dormitory to house increased personnel due to a potential nuclear mission. This comes as the nuclear capable F-35 has been deployed to the UK. And Russia has taken notice with them saying that the return of US nuclear weapons to the UK will be seen as an escalation.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7275506222642695470" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-06T00:40:05+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7275787044721413422</id>
    <title>Passenger Coats Plane In Diarrhea #usa #airplane  A flight from Atlanta to Barcelona was forced to turn around 2 hours into the journey because a passenger had diarrhea all throughout the airplane. Passengers say it dribbled down the aisle and that they t</title>
    <updated>2023-09-06T18:49:50+00:00</updated>
    <content>Passenger Coats Plane In Diarrhea #usa #airplane  A flight from Atlanta to Barcelona was forced to turn around 2 hours into the journey because a passenger had diarrhea all throughout the airplane. Passengers say it dribbled down the aisle and that they tried to cover up the smell with vanilla but it just smelt like vanilla diarrhea. I do feel bad for the diarrhea passenger because not only did you cover the plane in diarrhea but then you had to sit in it for the next 2 hours, and the rest of the plane is mad at you for ruining their vacation. They’re getting off the plane pointing at you saying “that’s the diarrhea guy” and then just when you think the humiliation is over… it’s front page news across the country.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7275787044721413422" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-06T18:49:50+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
