<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-06-28T21:27:50+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7248726082432748846</id>
    <title>Bobby Wagner Just Rizzed Up Baby Gronk. #usa  This video is in full compliance of community guidelines and is an obvious parody. Baby Gronk is like 10 and lives in America, Bobby Wagner is a mercenary group in Russia this is obvuously nonsense. It doesnt </title>
    <updated>2023-06-25T20:39:36+00:00</updated>
    <content>Bobby Wagner Just Rizzed Up Baby Gronk. #usa  This video is in full compliance of community guidelines and is an obvious parody. Baby Gronk is like 10 and lives in America, Bobby Wagner is a mercenary group in Russia this is obvuously nonsense. It doesnt promote criminal activity, it doesnt violate community guidelines. Is it dumb? Yes. Stop removing the video. Please and thank you. </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7248726082432748846" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-06-25T20:39:36+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7249108866133265707</id>
    <title>US Called Russia During Coup #usa #russia  During Saturday’s Coup, the US called Russia. The US reportedly told them that they had nothing to do with the coup and they pushed for Russia to not use its nuclear arsenal. Lavrov added that the US really empha</title>
    <updated>2023-06-26T21:25:00+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Called Russia During Coup #usa #russia  During Saturday’s Coup, the US called Russia. The US reportedly told them that they had nothing to do with the coup and they pushed for Russia to not use its nuclear arsenal. Lavrov added that the US really emphasized that they had had no plans to get involved in the coup and that everything that was happening was an internal affair of Russia and none of their business. But that’s about where the good will ended. Lavrov then lashed out at the US for not telling anyone about the rebellion despite knowing about it. And in fairness, he has a point.. When has Russia ever done the US wrong? And don’t say the 2016 election, Syria, cyber attacks on our power grid, the 3 invasions of Ukraine, continuous nuclear threats to us and our allies, attempts to kill US citizens, Afghanistan, downing our drones by running into them with their planes, trying to shoot down our planes, unleashing a troll farm on US social media sites, blaming us for everything that goes wrong, cheating in the olympics, hacking of us companies</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7249108866133265707" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-06-26T21:25:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7249486072445521198</id>
    <title>US Prepares For Collapse Of Russia #usa #russia #uk  The UK is making plans for Russia if it suddenly collapses. This comes after this weekend’s coup attempt. The US had also prepared plans for a range of scenarios with Russia. When we spoke to officials </title>
    <updated>2023-06-27T21:48:41+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Prepares For Collapse Of Russia #usa #russia #uk  The UK is making plans for Russia if it suddenly collapses. This comes after this weekend’s coup attempt. The US had also prepared plans for a range of scenarios with Russia. When we spoke to officials over the weekend, Western capitals were already starting to make plans if Wagner were to come in possession of nuclear weapons. Officials in Washington are left wondering if they witnessed an aborted coup or a thwarted mutiny. One senior European Diplomat asked “Why did it calm down so quickly, and how come Putin’s puppet Lukashenko got the credit?” Many western officials are skeptical that this is the end, with some believing that Wagner will either challenge Russia’s military from abroad or that Prigo will be killed in Belarus. Also Putin revealed today Russia had paid Wagner 68 billion rubles just this year… damn and I thought my Peloton investment was bad.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7249486072445521198" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-06-27T21:48:41+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7249828198110825770</id>
    <title>The World Loves America #usa #america  America is beloved all over the globe according to a new pew research poll. The results of this poll are stunning. With 93% of Poland having a positive view of the U.S. So does 60% of Italy, 59% of the UK, 57% of Ger</title>
    <updated>2023-06-28T19:56:22+00:00</updated>
    <content>The World Loves America #usa #america  America is beloved all over the globe according to a new pew research poll. The results of this poll are stunning. With 93% of Poland having a positive view of the U.S. So does 60% of Italy, 59% of the UK, 57% of Germany and 52% of France. 51% of Hungarians don’t view the U.S. positively. In Asia, they can’t stop loving us. Over 70% of South Korea and Japan view the U.S. positively. 65% of India and 52% of Australia. In Africa, over 70% of Nigeria and Kenya view the U.S. positively along with 59% of South Africans. And the love continues in the Americas with Brazil, Mexico, and Argentina all having positive views of the U.S. Of the 23 countries surveyed, only one country didn’t like us and that country is terrible.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7249828198110825770" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-06-28T19:56:22+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7249851787761503530</id>
    <title>All Of South Korea Just Got 2 Years Younger! #southkorea #korea  All South Koreans are now a year or two younger as of today. South Korea has adopted the international age system that the rest of the world uses that states that when babies are born, they </title>
    <updated>2023-06-28T21:27:50+00:00</updated>
    <content>All Of South Korea Just Got 2 Years Younger! #southkorea #korea  All South Koreans are now a year or two younger as of today. South Korea has adopted the international age system that the rest of the world uses that states that when babies are born, they are 0 years old. With South Korea’s old age system, when a baby was born they were 1 year old and on every New Year’s Day, they aged 1 year. So if you were born on New Years Eve, you’d be two years old despite only being two days old! What an interesting way to do pension reform. #korean </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7249851787761503530" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-06-28T21:27:50+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
