<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-08-21T16:25:53+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7267985946149408046</id>
    <title>US Soldier Fled To North Korea To Escape Racism In America #usa #korea #america  North Korea says the U.S. soldier, Travis King, who ran into the country did so because of racism in the United States. They say he says he suffered inhuman treatment and rac</title>
    <updated>2023-08-16T18:17:36+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Soldier Fled To North Korea To Escape Racism In America #usa #korea #america  North Korea says the U.S. soldier, Travis King, who ran into the country did so because of racism in the United States. They say he says he suffered inhuman treatment and racial discrimination in the US Army. They also claim he wants to seek refugee in North Korea or in a 3rd country because he’s disillusioned at “unequal American society”. Travis King was being sent back to the United States due to several crimes he had committed in South Korea when he ran into North Korea.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7267985946149408046" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-16T18:17:36+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7268046704086355246</id>
    <title>US Throws France Under The Bus In Niger #usa #france  The US now says that Niger is a partner and they don’t wanna see that partnership go. Adding that they have invested hundreds of millions of dollars into bases there, so it really wants a peaceful reso</title>
    <updated>2023-08-16T22:13:21+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Throws France Under The Bus In Niger #usa #france  The US now says that Niger is a partner and they don’t wanna see that partnership go. Adding that they have invested hundreds of millions of dollars into bases there, so it really wants a peaceful resolution. The US seems to be coming to peace with the Junta because they’re not kicking out the American troops, only the French. So, in essence - the US is throwing France under the bus and leaving them behind. Or as Charles de Gaulle famously said “No nation has friends, only interests”. Bon Voyage.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7268046704086355246" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-16T22:13:21+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7268405461618052394</id>
    <title>US Asks Iran To Stop Giving Drones To Russia #usa #russia  The US has asked Iran to stop selling drones to Russia. Currently the U.S. and Iran are conducting indirect talks in Oman which is an absolutely ridiculous thing. The two governments want to make </title>
    <updated>2023-08-17T21:25:31+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Asks Iran To Stop Giving Drones To Russia #usa #russia  The US has asked Iran to stop selling drones to Russia. Currently the U.S. and Iran are conducting indirect talks in Oman which is an absolutely ridiculous thing. The two governments want to make a deal with each other but they refuse to speak to each other so Omani officials have to go between the two rooms delivering messages between them. Anyways the US asked them to stop supplying drones to Russia and while Iran officially denies that their drones are being used - they told the US that they have asked Moscow to stop but the US wants more concrete steps.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7268405461618052394" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-17T21:25:31+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7269796629912341803</id>
    <title>US Unites Japan and South Korea in Historic Security Pact #usa #japan #korea  A New Friendship has been formed! The US has gotten Japan and South Korea to drop their disputes and agree to a new security pledge that would see all 3 countries defend each ot</title>
    <updated>2023-08-21T15:24:16+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Unites Japan and South Korea in Historic Security Pact #usa #japan #korea  A New Friendship has been formed! The US has gotten Japan and South Korea to drop their disputes and agree to a new security pledge that would see all 3 countries defend each other. South Korea and Japan have famously hated each other since the Second World War, but after meeting at Camp David with President Biden - the two countries will now pursue peace and mutual security as friends not foes. The threats of China and North Korea and the friendship of the United States has brought them together. This comes as America seeks to build Asian NATO.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7269796629912341803" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-21T15:24:16+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7269812524781014314</id>
    <title>Niger Changes Mind On France, Wants Them To Stay #usa #france  Niger’s Junta now says they want France to stay in the country, and just asks that they be less condescending which good luck with that request, that’s just part of being French. They praised </title>
    <updated>2023-08-21T16:25:53+00:00</updated>
    <content>Niger Changes Mind On France, Wants Them To Stay #usa #france  Niger’s Junta now says they want France to stay in the country, and just asks that they be less condescending which good luck with that request, that’s just part of being French. They praised President Biden and his “extremely reasonable position”. They also said that they won’t allow Wagner into the country because they want to stay partners with the US and France. This comes as ECOWAS announced that they will conduct D-Day on Niger. The Junta seems to have drunk its own Kool-Aid by appealing to France and the U.S. Because it’s Nigeria they should be appealing to right now, it’s Nigeria who will be rolling across the border not the US &amp; France. #nigeria </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7269812524781014314" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-21T16:25:53+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
