<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-07-26T21:26:18+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7259767425774816558</id>
    <title>Russia Attacked US Drone #usa #russia  Russia just attacked a U.S. drone. When a U.S. drone was returning home after it completed its mission of defeating, a Russian jet flew within meters of it and deployed flares on it which hit its propeller, severely </title>
    <updated>2023-07-25T14:45:35+00:00</updated>
    <content>Russia Attacked US Drone #usa #russia  Russia just attacked a U.S. drone. When a U.S. drone was returning home after it completed its mission of defeating, a Russian jet flew within meters of it and deployed flares on it which hit its propeller, severely damaging it. The U.S. says this was an attempt to knock the US drone out of the sky. With the U.S. saying “We call upon the Russian forces in Syria to put an immediate end to this reckless, unprovoked, and unprofessional behavior.” Apparently both sides used the deconfliction hotline but reportedly the line has been very heated lately and just been a place for the two of them to verbally argue instead of deconflict.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7259767425774816558" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-25T14:45:35+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7259866793546714410</id>
    <title>Russia Bombs NATO Ship #russia #ukraine  Russia just hit a NATO ship while it was bombing a Ukrainian port. The civilian ship belonged to Romania and it was struck in the Ukrainian port of Reni. The ship was able to complete its voyage despite minor damag</title>
    <updated>2023-07-25T21:11:11+00:00</updated>
    <content>Russia Bombs NATO Ship #russia #ukraine  Russia just hit a NATO ship while it was bombing a Ukrainian port. The civilian ship belonged to Romania and it was struck in the Ukrainian port of Reni. The ship was able to complete its voyage despite minor damage. No Romanian citizens were injured. If Russia continues to bomb Ukrainian ports, they will only raise the risk of NATO involvement.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7259866793546714410" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-25T21:11:11+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7259915875946450219</id>
    <title>Russian Brain Drain Boosts Neighboring Economies Big Time #russia #ukraine </title>
    <updated>2023-07-26T00:21:34+00:00</updated>
    <content>Russian Brain Drain Boosts Neighboring Economies Big Time #russia #ukraine </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7259915875946450219" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-26T00:21:34+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7260185946157567275</id>
    <title>America Has Alien Bodies?! #usa #ufo  A former intelligence officer testified in front of the United States Congress today that the US is in possession of alien bodies and UFOs. The officer claims that non-human technologies have injured humans and that t</title>
    <updated>2023-07-26T17:49:36+00:00</updated>
    <content>America Has Alien Bodies?! #usa #ufo  A former intelligence officer testified in front of the United States Congress today that the US is in possession of alien bodies and UFOs. The officer claims that non-human technologies have injured humans and that the US government became aware of Aliens in the 1930s. He also says he’s seen a video of a UFO being shot down and that the US government has a program to retrieve crashed UFOs and to reverse engineer them. He refused to say publicly if the US has communicated with aliens. He said that since coming forward about UFOs, he’s had to fear for his life. The officer also alleges that the US government is conducting a disinformation campaign targeted towards Americans about UFOs. Extraordinary claims require extraordinary amounts of evidence.. And he’s provided nothing.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7260185946157567275" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-26T17:49:36+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7260241792690392366</id>
    <title>Large Red Square Hovered Over Air Force Base #usa #america  A US Navy pilot testified in front of Congress today that in 2003 a large red square hovered over an Air Force Base which hovered for approximately 45 seconds before disappearing. The red square </title>
    <updated>2023-07-26T21:26:18+00:00</updated>
    <content>Large Red Square Hovered Over Air Force Base #usa #america  A US Navy pilot testified in front of Congress today that in 2003 a large red square hovered over an Air Force Base which hovered for approximately 45 seconds before disappearing. The red square was supposedly the size of a football field. He said that UFOs are commonly a black square or a black cube inside of a clear sphere. He also said that he’s talked to two navy pilots who nearly hit a dark gray black cube inside of a clear sphere with no wings</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7260241792690392366" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-26T21:26:18+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
