<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-10-31T22:22:31+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7293989871083998507</id>
    <title>Iran Attacks United States, Teetering On War #usa #america  The U.S. &amp; Iran are on the verge of war. Since October 17th, the Pentagon says there have been at least 15 drone and rocket attacks on US forces by Iranian proxies. With US officials telling NBC </title>
    <updated>2023-10-25T20:06:16+00:00</updated>
    <content>Iran Attacks United States, Teetering On War #usa #america  The U.S. &amp; Iran are on the verge of war. Since October 17th, the Pentagon says there have been at least 15 drone and rocket attacks on US forces by Iranian proxies. With US officials telling NBC News that more than two dozen U.S. soldiers were wounded in these attacks. Several of these soldiers have reported symptoms of traumatic brain injuries. Today President Biden said “My warning to the Ayatollah was that if they continued to move against our troops we will respond and he should be prepared.” The Marine Corps top general issued a warning yesterday saying “For those that are in the area, if that Marine Expeditionary Unit has to go in, if you target them, someone else will raise your children.” Yesterday the US delivered a stark warning at the UN to Iran and now The White House says they’re sending even MORE forces to the Middle East. US officials say they have intelligence that Iran is encouraging its terror groups to ramp up attacks on the United States according to Reuters. With one U.S. official saying “there are red lights flashing everywhere.”</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7293989871083998507" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-25T20:06:16+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7294704766553296159</id>
    <title>US Strikes Back At Iran #usa #america  The Pentagon says the US military conducted airstrikes on two facilities in eastern Syria used by Iran's troops and its proxy groups. With the New York Times reporting that two F-16s dropped 30 precision guided bombs</title>
    <updated>2023-10-27T18:20:17+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Strikes Back At Iran #usa #america  The Pentagon says the US military conducted airstrikes on two facilities in eastern Syria used by Iran's troops and its proxy groups. With the New York Times reporting that two F-16s dropped 30 precision guided bombs on a weapons storage facility and an ammunition storage facility. AP reports that Iranian troops were present at the facilities during the strikes but a causality assessment hasn’t been done yet. These strikes are in response to at least 19 attacks on US forces in the past week. The US says it doesn't seek a broader conflict, but Iran must stop attacking US troops. Adding any further attacks including any response to these airstrikes will result in the US engaging in self-defense. But earlier this morning, US soldiers shot down a one-way attack drone heading for their base in Iraq according to Fox News. Making that the 20th attack on US forces, and a clear violation of the red line that was laid out by the White House like not even an hour earlier.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7294704766553296159" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-27T18:20:17+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7294737926674582815</id>
    <title>Chinese Jet Almost Hit B-52 Bomber #usa #america  A Chinese fighter jet came within 10 feet of a US B-52 bomber over the South China Sea earlier this week, that’s what you’re seeing on screen right now. The US says the Chinese pilot was “flying at an unco</title>
    <updated>2023-10-27T20:28:55+00:00</updated>
    <content>Chinese Jet Almost Hit B-52 Bomber #usa #america  A Chinese fighter jet came within 10 feet of a US B-52 bomber over the South China Sea earlier this week, that’s what you’re seeing on screen right now. The US says the Chinese pilot was “flying at an uncontrolled excessive speed, flying below, in front of, and within 10 feet of the B-52, putting both aircraft in danger of collision.” In response to this, China released a video showing a US warship doing what they call “close-in harassment” on August 19th, which is what you’re watching right now. China says the US is the real provoker, risk-taker and disrupter. But the US says that China has engaged in risky and aggressive behavior in the skies over 180 times since Fall of 2021. Good lord, which one of them is gonna yell “mom” first?</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7294737926674582815" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-27T20:28:55+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7295884650151546143</id>
    <title>Hamas Wasn’t Expecting America To Join The Battle #usa #israel  Hamas says it didn’t expect such a strong response from the U.S. With a senior member of the group telling the financial times - “An Israeli response? Yes, we expected that but what we’re see</title>
    <updated>2023-10-30T22:38:46+00:00</updated>
    <content>Hamas Wasn’t Expecting America To Join The Battle #usa #israel  Hamas says it didn’t expect such a strong response from the U.S. With a senior member of the group telling the financial times - “An Israeli response? Yes, we expected that but what we’re seeing now is the entrance of the US into the battle, and this we didn’t count on.” This alluding to how the US’ two carriers have restrained Hamas’ allies from fully entering the war with Israel as Hamas expected them to. Jordan has asked the United States to deploy Patriots in its country to bolster its defense. An anti-Semitic mob of hundreds stormed an airport and its tarmac in Russia looking for Jewish people who they claim were on a flight from Tel Aviv. Earlier in the day, the New York Times reports that hundreds gathered outside of a hotel after rumors that it was “filled with Jews”. Russia has blamed Ukraine for its own people forming antisemitic mobs.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7295884650151546143" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-30T22:38:46+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7296251541105675550</id>
    <title>Israel Strikes Refugee Camp #usa #israel  Israel has confirmed that it carried out an airstrike on Gaza’s largest refugee camp to kill a senior Hamas commander. The Wall Street Journal says Doctors estimate scores of civilians were killed in the strike. T</title>
    <updated>2023-10-31T22:22:31+00:00</updated>
    <content>Israel Strikes Refugee Camp #usa #israel  Israel has confirmed that it carried out an airstrike on Gaza’s largest refugee camp to kill a senior Hamas commander. The Wall Street Journal says Doctors estimate scores of civilians were killed in the strike. The IDF was asked by Wolf Blitzer why they would hit the camp if they knew it had  innocent refugees and civilians. And the spokesperson said: “This is the tragedy of war, wolf. We've been saying for days, move south." The Houthis have entered the conflict, according to Reuters. The Houthis, based in Yemen over a thousand miles away from Israel, say they have carried out 3 missile attacks on Israel so far. The first of these attacks was intercepted by the US navy and Saudi Arabia while the 2nd hit Egypt instead of Israel, and initial reports seem to suggest that the third attack hit Jordan by accident today.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7296251541105675550" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-31T22:22:31+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
