<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-10-10T22:15:44+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7288013889499942186</id>
    <title>Israel To Begin Total Siege Of Gaza #usa #israel  Israel has announced the total siege of Gaza. Saying “there will be no electricity, no food, no fuel. We are fighting human animals and we will act accordingly.” They’ve also reportedly cut off Gaza’s wate</title>
    <updated>2023-10-09T17:36:14+00:00</updated>
    <content>Israel To Begin Total Siege Of Gaza #usa #israel  Israel has announced the total siege of Gaza. Saying “there will be no electricity, no food, no fuel. We are fighting human animals and we will act accordingly.” They’ve also reportedly cut off Gaza’s water supply. Adding that “this is a war for our existence and we will do things never seen before”. Israel has reportedly told the United States that it will conduct a ground invasion of Gaza, and they have so far mobilized over 300,000 soldiers. Gaza is currently under very intense bombing, with Israel hitting over a hundred targets an hour. The bombing is only expected to increase in intensity. There are reports of entire city blocks being destroyed. At least 1,000 Israelis have been killed as of recording in Hamas’ terror attacks. And at least 9 Americans were reportedly killed in the attacks as well, with several more still held hostage. At least 560 Palestinians have died in Israel’s return strikes with an additional 2,900 wounded. There are reports of clashing between Israel and the P-I-J on their border with Lebanon. Israel is reportedly cooperating with the US military for this operation, with Israel saying that if there are attempts by Iranian proxies to act, it may lead to an attack from America  The EU has suspended all aid payments to Palestine. Saying that the scale of terror and brutality against Israel and its people is a turning point.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7288013889499942186" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-09T17:36:14+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7288047104843386154</id>
    <title>Hezbollah Threatens America As It Prepares To Defend Israel #usa #israel  Hamas says they will start executing hostages one by one in response to Israeli airstrikes that they aren’t warned about. They say they’ll film the executions and post the videos on</title>
    <updated>2023-10-09T19:45:12+00:00</updated>
    <content>Hezbollah Threatens America As It Prepares To Defend Israel #usa #israel  Hamas says they will start executing hostages one by one in response to Israeli airstrikes that they aren’t warned about. They say they’ll film the executions and post the videos online. There are still several Americans, as well as tens of Chinese and Russian citizens being held hostage. The US has once again repeated its threat that any party that seeks to attack Israel right now will face the US military. Hezbollah has reportedly threatened the United States. Saying that if they intervene directly in the war with Israel there will be no red lines. Warning that all American locations in the Middle East, including military bases, embassies and consulates, will become targets of its attacks. Hezbollah and Israel have been exchanging artillery fire on and off all morning. The UAE has reportedly expressed solidarity with Israel. The White House has reportedly told Senators to prepare their constituents for a long war between Israel and Gaza. Adding that the US will supply both tangible and political support to Israel.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7288047104843386154" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-09T19:45:12+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7288411287485287722</id>
    <title>Hamas Wants Truce, Israel Says You’ll Get The War You Wanted #usa #israel  Hamas is reportedly asking for a truce with Israel but Israel says that Hamas asked for war so they will get war. Both Israel and the US have compared Hamas to ISIS. An unidentifie</title>
    <updated>2023-10-10T19:18:32+00:00</updated>
    <content>Hamas Wants Truce, Israel Says You’ll Get The War You Wanted #usa #israel  Hamas is reportedly asking for a truce with Israel but Israel says that Hamas asked for war so they will get war. Both Israel and the US have compared Hamas to ISIS. An unidentified country struck an Iranian convoy in Iraq and Syria today. The US has reportedly communicated with Lebanon directly to tell them “Hezbollah should stay out of the picture because if there is a war - Lebanon as a country will be damaged and hurt”. Meanwhile, Hezbollah and Israel have continued to shoot at each other all day through various means with each strike being a response to the previous strike. The US has said that Iran should “think twice” about entering the conflict and they believe that Iran is trying to draw them into a global conflict. In addition to all this, The United States, United Kingdom, France, Germany and Italy have issued a joint statement pledging to help Israel defend itself. The UAE has reportedly warned Syria to not intervene and to not allow attacks to happen from their soil.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7288411287485287722" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-10T19:18:32+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7288442118136302894</id>
    <title>Iran &amp; Israel Take The War To Twitter #israel #usa  The US may conduct a special forces operation to free Americans in Gaza. Yemen’s Houthi group reportedly said if the US intervenes, they’ll attack them with missiles. Trigger fingers are turning into twi</title>
    <updated>2023-10-10T21:18:09+00:00</updated>
    <content>Iran &amp; Israel Take The War To Twitter #israel #usa  The US may conduct a special forces operation to free Americans in Gaza. Yemen’s Houthi group reportedly said if the US intervenes, they’ll attack them with missiles. Trigger fingers are turning into twitter fingers. With Iran’s supreme leader tweeting that Israel will face a larger force if they keep doing, what he called, the mass murder of Gaza. Israel tweeted back saying “It’s easy to be brave when you’re hiding behind a keyboard. You and your Hamas friends will regret your barbaric actions very soon.” Egypt says it’ll bring aid to Gaza but Israel says it’ll airstrike all Egyptian aid convoys. Despite these warnings, Egypt has reportedly still ordered the aid convoy to go into Gaza.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7288442118136302894" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-10T21:18:09+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7288456984376954154</id>
    <title>US To Send Another Aircraft Carrier To Israel #usa #israel  Israel is now getting hit by Mortars from Syria in addition to rockets from Lebanon, and Israel is responding with counter-battery fire. So far 1,000 Israelis have been killed with another 3,400 </title>
    <updated>2023-10-10T22:15:44+00:00</updated>
    <content>US To Send Another Aircraft Carrier To Israel #usa #israel  Israel is now getting hit by Mortars from Syria in addition to rockets from Lebanon, and Israel is responding with counter-battery fire. So far 1,000 Israelis have been killed with another 3,400 injured and 900 Palestinians have been killed with another 4,500 injured. Israel is preparing a months-long ground campaign in Gaza according to Egypt. With Egypt also saying that Israel has dismissed their efforts to mediate any kind of de-escalation according to the Times of Israel. With the Times saying it’s believed that Israel wants to destroy Hamas before entertaining a ceasefire. The United States may deploy a 2nd aircraft carrier strike group to Israel according to the Wall Street Post. The USS Gerald Ford has arrived off the coast of Israel and will likely begin operations tonight. And this has made Erdogan very mad at Israel and the United States. He angrily asked today:  “Why is the US aircraft carrier coming to Israel? For what? What will they do? Will they hit Gaza with their warplanes and commit a massacre?”. Jake Sullivan responded saying: "Let me be clear: we did not move the carrier for Hamas. We moved the carrier to send a clear message of deterrence to other parties who may seek to widen the war”.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7288456984376954154" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-10T22:15:44+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
