<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-06-25T20:39:36+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7248221539332623659</id>
    <title>The Russian Civil War Begins #russia #ukraine #usa  The Russian civil war is now in full swing. I’ve done this for 17 years now and this is the most insane thing I’ve ever seen. Putin says he’ll do anything to defend Russia and has ordered the military to</title>
    <updated>2023-06-24T12:02:18+00:00</updated>
    <content>The Russian Civil War Begins #russia #ukraine #usa  The Russian civil war is now in full swing. I’ve done this for 17 years now and this is the most insane thing I’ve ever seen. Putin says he’ll do anything to defend Russia and has ordered the military to wipe out Wagner. The Wagner group says he’s made the wrong choice and that they’re going to topple his regime. Wagner controls at least two cities and Russia is blowing up oil depots in cities that Wagner controls. Russia is also airstriking the Wagner Convoy on Russian highways as they make their way to Moscow. There are reports that Wagner has shot down more helicopters and allegedly fighter jets. Some units of the Russian army have reportedly flipped to Wagner. Wagner is seemingly hell bent on marching on Moscow</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7248221539332623659" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-06-24T12:02:18+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7248257862848269610</id>
    <title>Wagner Makes Mad Dash To Moscow #russia #ukraine #usa  Wagner is making a bolt to Moscow with a convoy of reportedly 400 vehicles. Russia is setting machine gun nests up around Moscow as well as attempting to block all entrances into the city. It appears </title>
    <updated>2023-06-24T14:22:45+00:00</updated>
    <content>Wagner Makes Mad Dash To Moscow #russia #ukraine #usa  Wagner is making a bolt to Moscow with a convoy of reportedly 400 vehicles. Russia is setting machine gun nests up around Moscow as well as attempting to block all entrances into the city. It appears as if we’re heading towards a showdown in Moscow by tonight. Putin has tried to negotiate with Wagner but they’ve rejected his attempts. Wagner is pulling equipment out of Ukraine to use in it’s war against Russia. Putin’s plane has flown out of Moscow but the Kremlin says he’s still in the city.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7248257862848269610" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-06-24T14:22:45+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7248329651632819498</id>
    <title>The Russian Civil War Coup Is Over #russia #ukraine #usa  The Russian civil war Coup attempt is over… maybe? Kind of? Reports are coming out that Wagner has halted their advance to Moscow and will be returning to their bases after Lukashenko of all people</title>
    <updated>2023-06-24T19:01:10+00:00</updated>
    <content>The Russian Civil War Coup Is Over #russia #ukraine #usa  The Russian civil war Coup attempt is over… maybe? Kind of? Reports are coming out that Wagner has halted their advance to Moscow and will be returning to their bases after Lukashenko of all people struck a deal with them. The deal reportedly will see Russia's defense minister and chief general replaced while Wagner’s leader and his fighters will get total legal immunity in exchange for not overthrowing the government. If you’re confused, I can assure you that everyone is. A point of no return was reached today, they shot down 7 aircraft, occupied cities, and humiliated Putin. Russia was blowing up their own bridges and oil depots, and digging trenches in Moscow. Maybe the immediate situation is over but the crisis is just beginning. It’s now very clear how incredibly weak Putin is and you can’t get that cat back in the bag.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7248329651632819498" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-06-24T19:01:10+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7248696266413198634</id>
    <title>The US Knew Of Russian Coup Plot #usa #russia  The U.S. reportedly knew Russia was about to be coup’d two weeks ago after spies uncovered the plot. In fact, Congress had reportedly been briefed on it days before it happened. This demonstrates just how big</title>
    <updated>2023-06-25T18:43:55+00:00</updated>
    <content>The US Knew Of Russian Coup Plot #usa #russia  The U.S. reportedly knew Russia was about to be coup’d two weeks ago after spies uncovered the plot. In fact, Congress had reportedly been briefed on it days before it happened. This demonstrates just how big of an intelligence failure this was for Russia. The leader of Wagner has reportedly been exiled to Belarus and it’s hard to say how long that will last for. It’s still not quite clear to anyone who’s currently in charge of the Russian military or why Wagner stopped when they had it in the bag. But The U.S. believes that we haven’t seen the end of Russian turmoil and that Pandora’s box has been opened.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7248696266413198634" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-06-25T18:43:55+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7248726082432748846</id>
    <title>Bobby Wagner Just Rizzed Up Baby Gronk. #usa  This video is in full compliance of community guidelines and is an obvious parody. Baby Gronk is like 10 and lives in America, Bobby Wagner is a mercenary group in Russia this is obvuously nonsense. It doesnt </title>
    <updated>2023-06-25T20:39:36+00:00</updated>
    <content>Bobby Wagner Just Rizzed Up Baby Gronk. #usa  This video is in full compliance of community guidelines and is an obvious parody. Baby Gronk is like 10 and lives in America, Bobby Wagner is a mercenary group in Russia this is obvuously nonsense. It doesnt promote criminal activity, it doesnt violate community guidelines. Is it dumb? Yes. Stop removing the video. Please and thank you. </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7248726082432748846" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-06-25T20:39:36+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
