<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-09-27T20:21:53+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7282857074013375790</id>
    <title>Russia Rejects Peace, Wants To Settle It On Battlefield #ukraine #russia  Russia has rejected Ukraine’s peace plan because they want to “settle it on the Battlefield” instead. Just this past week, Ukraine struck the Black Sea Headquarters in Crimea - kill</title>
    <updated>2023-09-25T20:05:11+00:00</updated>
    <content>Russia Rejects Peace, Wants To Settle It On Battlefield #ukraine #russia  Russia has rejected Ukraine’s peace plan because they want to “settle it on the Battlefield” instead. Just this past week, Ukraine struck the Black Sea Headquarters in Crimea - killing the commander of the Black Sea Fleet. Meanwhile American tanks have finally arrived in Ukraine with Depleted uranium rounds. And while Ukraine’s counteroffensive has been moving slower than expected, their shaping operation in Crimea has seen great success.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7282857074013375790" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-25T20:05:11+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7283211994537184555</id>
    <title>US Deploys F-16s To Enforce No-Fly Zone #usa #ukraine  The US has deployed F-16s to Romania to enforce the new no fly zone. The No-Fly Zone extends 30 kilometers from Romania’s eastern border and will allow them to shoot down any missiles or drones approa</title>
    <updated>2023-09-26T19:02:33+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Deploys F-16s To Enforce No-Fly Zone #usa #ukraine  The US has deployed F-16s to Romania to enforce the new no fly zone. The No-Fly Zone extends 30 kilometers from Romania’s eastern border and will allow them to shoot down any missiles or drones approaching their borders. This comes after Russia kept hitting Romania when they were attacking Ukraine.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7283211994537184555" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-26T19:02:33+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7283235540193856811</id>
    <title>Canadian Pilot Changes Call Sign To What?! #canada #uk  Yesterday a Canadian fighter jet changed its call sign to “D**K69” while it was flying over the UK. Canada says it’s investigating the name change, adding that it was inappropriate and unapproved. Ca</title>
    <updated>2023-09-26T20:33:53+00:00</updated>
    <content>Canadian Pilot Changes Call Sign To What?! #canada #uk  Yesterday a Canadian fighter jet changed its call sign to “D**K69” while it was flying over the UK. Canada says it’s investigating the name change, adding that it was inappropriate and unapproved. Call signs contain four letters and two numbers. They are assigned to pilots and usually remain unchanged. And this Canadian pilot changed their call sign from BLDE11 to D**K69. They could be facing a stiff punishment.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7283235540193856811" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-26T20:33:53+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7283547924317965614</id>
    <title>China Saved US Soldier From North Korea #usa #korea  The US soldier who ran into North Korea is now in American custody. Sweden and China worked diplomatic channels on behalf of the US to get the soldier released. North Korea then transferred him to China</title>
    <updated>2023-09-27T16:45:59+00:00</updated>
    <content>China Saved US Soldier From North Korea #usa #korea  The US soldier who ran into North Korea is now in American custody. Sweden and China worked diplomatic channels on behalf of the US to get the soldier released. North Korea then transferred him to China who gave him back to the United States. The US has thanked Sweden and China for helping bring Private King home. North Korea deported him for illegally crossing into the country. He must have been messing up the feel good vibes North Korea is so famous for. China Saved US Soldier From North Korea The US soldier who ran into North Korea is now in American custody. Sweden and China worked diplomatic channels on behalf of the US to get the soldier released. North Korea then transferred him to China who gave him back to the United States. The US has thanked Sweden and China for helping bring Private King home. North Korea deported him for illegally crossing into the country. He must have been messing up the feel good vibes North Korea is so famous for.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7283547924317965614" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-27T16:45:59+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7283603550100294954</id>
    <title>Gamer Leaks Classified Document To Win War Thunder Argument #usa #warthunder  For the third time this month, gamers have leaked restricted military documents on the war thunder forums. This time it’s the manual to the Apache helicopter which was supposed </title>
    <updated>2023-09-27T20:21:53+00:00</updated>
    <content>Gamer Leaks Classified Document To Win War Thunder Argument #usa #warthunder  For the third time this month, gamers have leaked restricted military documents on the war thunder forums. This time it’s the manual to the Apache helicopter which was supposed to be for the DoD only. Earlier this month, a user leaked part of the manual to the F-117 Nighthawk’s flight manual. War Thunder’s dedication to realism is its Achilles heal as players often resort to leaking classified documents in order to settle online arguments… which has happened at least 13 times.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7283603550100294954" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-27T20:21:53+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
