<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-09-04T22:49:33+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7273600574636215598</id>
    <title>Russia Demands Norway Pay Them $4.4 Million Because Of Reindeer Damage #norway #russia  Russia is demanding that Norway pay them 4.4 million dollars because 42 reindeer crossed the border into Russia. They say the money is for compensation for the reindee</title>
    <updated>2023-08-31T21:25:20+00:00</updated>
    <content>Russia Demands Norway Pay Them $4.4 Million Because Of Reindeer Damage #norway #russia  Russia is demanding that Norway pay them 4.4 million dollars because 42 reindeer crossed the border into Russia. They say the money is for compensation for the reindeer eating Russian grass. That’s some expensive grass. Supposedly a gate that separated the two countries and kept Reindeer out of Russia broke. So now 40 of the 42 reindeer have been killed in fears that they’ll cross into Russia again. Norway has asked its citizens to keep their reindeer in check. Look, Santa won’t be stopping in Russia this year with these kinds of rules in place.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7273600574636215598" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-31T21:25:20+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7273616892273691950</id>
    <title>French Military Readies To Strike Niger #france #niger  Niger has stripped the French ambassador of their diplomatic immunity and have ordered the police to expel them. They obviously can’t go into the embassy as that would be a major breach of internatio</title>
    <updated>2023-08-31T22:28:35+00:00</updated>
    <content>French Military Readies To Strike Niger #france #niger  Niger has stripped the French ambassador of their diplomatic immunity and have ordered the police to expel them. They obviously can’t go into the embassy as that would be a major breach of international norms, too far for even them. But Police in Niger are now searching all vehicles leaving the embassy. It can not be understated how absolutely ridiculous this is. If they manage to get their hands on the ambassador; France isn’t going to ask for them back, they’re just going to bomb the country into oblivion. Have the people of Niger not suffered enough? The Junta must stop doing this stupid stuff.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7273616892273691950" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-31T22:28:35+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7273992810217442603</id>
    <title>Saudi Arabia Kills Man For Tweets #saudiarabia #saudi  Saudi Arabia has sentenced a man to death for criticizing the Saudi Royal Family on Twitter. The charges against him are “betraying his religion,” “disturbing the security of society,” “conspiring aga</title>
    <updated>2023-09-01T22:47:19+00:00</updated>
    <content>Saudi Arabia Kills Man For Tweets #saudiarabia #saudi  Saudi Arabia has sentenced a man to death for criticizing the Saudi Royal Family on Twitter. The charges against him are “betraying his religion,” “disturbing the security of society,” “conspiring against the government” and “impugning the kingdom and the crown prince”. The man had just 10 followers so he was tweeting to essentially no one. Killing people for tweets is just yet another human rights violation from the champions of crimes against humanity Saudi Arabia also funded 9/11, genocided Yemenis, aided ISIS, and killed Jamal Khashoggi.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7273992810217442603" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-01T22:47:19+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7275007107122941226</id>
    <title>Russia Bombs Romania On Accident #russia #romania #ukraine  Russia hit Romania, a NATO member, with drones in an attack last night according to Ukraine. Romania denies this but Ukraine has released video and pictures of the drones hitting them. However Ro</title>
    <updated>2023-09-04T16:23:20+00:00</updated>
    <content>Russia Bombs Romania On Accident #russia #romania #ukraine  Russia hit Romania, a NATO member, with drones in an attack last night according to Ukraine. Romania denies this but Ukraine has released video and pictures of the drones hitting them. However Romania says that they posed no direct military threat. Russia is playing a risky game. They can’t hit the back side of a barn yet they send explosives en masse. This is at least the 2nd time Russia has bombed a NATO country by accident.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7275007107122941226" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-04T16:23:20+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7275106644634176811</id>
    <title>France Bans Muslim Dresses In Schools #france #islam  France says it’ll be uncompromising in its ban on abayas in school. An Abaya is usually a dark cloak worn by Muslim women. The French education minister says “When you walk into a classroom, you should</title>
    <updated>2023-09-04T22:49:33+00:00</updated>
    <content>France Bans Muslim Dresses In Schools #france #islam  France says it’ll be uncompromising in its ban on abayas in school. An Abaya is usually a dark cloak worn by Muslim women. The French education minister says “When you walk into a classroom, you shouldn't be able to identify a student’s religion just by looking at them” Some critics have called it discriminatory because Abayas aren’t inherently religious, they’re just a kind of dress. But Macron says French schools are secular and that teachers must enforce the ban. All religious attire and symbols are banned in French schools. Which is quite the difference from America. Here, our secularism is based on freedom of religion. It’s very individual, it’s part of the “be who you want to be” motto of America. While in France, their secularism is based on freedom from religion. It’s based on this belief that there is a collective freedom from religious institutions. It’s an interesting approach.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7275106644634176811" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-04T22:49:33+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
