<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-08-22T18:29:15+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7268405461618052394</id>
    <title>US Asks Iran To Stop Giving Drones To Russia #usa #russia  The US has asked Iran to stop selling drones to Russia. Currently the U.S. and Iran are conducting indirect talks in Oman which is an absolutely ridiculous thing. The two governments want to make </title>
    <updated>2023-08-17T21:25:31+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Asks Iran To Stop Giving Drones To Russia #usa #russia  The US has asked Iran to stop selling drones to Russia. Currently the U.S. and Iran are conducting indirect talks in Oman which is an absolutely ridiculous thing. The two governments want to make a deal with each other but they refuse to speak to each other so Omani officials have to go between the two rooms delivering messages between them. Anyways the US asked them to stop supplying drones to Russia and while Iran officially denies that their drones are being used - they told the US that they have asked Moscow to stop but the US wants more concrete steps.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7268405461618052394" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-17T21:25:31+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7269796629912341803</id>
    <title>US Unites Japan and South Korea in Historic Security Pact #usa #japan #korea  A New Friendship has been formed! The US has gotten Japan and South Korea to drop their disputes and agree to a new security pledge that would see all 3 countries defend each ot</title>
    <updated>2023-08-21T15:24:16+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Unites Japan and South Korea in Historic Security Pact #usa #japan #korea  A New Friendship has been formed! The US has gotten Japan and South Korea to drop their disputes and agree to a new security pledge that would see all 3 countries defend each other. South Korea and Japan have famously hated each other since the Second World War, but after meeting at Camp David with President Biden - the two countries will now pursue peace and mutual security as friends not foes. The threats of China and North Korea and the friendship of the United States has brought them together. This comes as America seeks to build Asian NATO.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7269796629912341803" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-21T15:24:16+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7269812524781014314</id>
    <title>Niger Changes Mind On France, Wants Them To Stay #usa #france  Niger’s Junta now says they want France to stay in the country, and just asks that they be less condescending which good luck with that request, that’s just part of being French. They praised </title>
    <updated>2023-08-21T16:25:53+00:00</updated>
    <content>Niger Changes Mind On France, Wants Them To Stay #usa #france  Niger’s Junta now says they want France to stay in the country, and just asks that they be less condescending which good luck with that request, that’s just part of being French. They praised President Biden and his “extremely reasonable position”. They also said that they won’t allow Wagner into the country because they want to stay partners with the US and France. This comes as ECOWAS announced that they will conduct D-Day on Niger. The Junta seems to have drunk its own Kool-Aid by appealing to France and the U.S. Because it’s Nigeria they should be appealing to right now, it’s Nigeria who will be rolling across the border not the US &amp; France. #nigeria </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7269812524781014314" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-21T16:25:53+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7269834304388156714</id>
    <title>Canada Preparing For A Fascist America #usa #canada  Canada says it’s creating a game plan for how to respond and deal with the United States if it takes a far-right authoritarian shift in next year’s Presidential election. They worry that the two Republi</title>
    <updated>2023-08-21T17:50:19+00:00</updated>
    <content>Canada Preparing For A Fascist America #usa #canada  Canada says it’s creating a game plan for how to respond and deal with the United States if it takes a far-right authoritarian shift in next year’s Presidential election. They worry that the two Republican front runners will pull the US out of NATO and all of its other treaties including trade agreements, leaving Canada to fend for itself. They declined to comment on what the plan would look like but Europe and Canada have been strengthening ties since the Trump Presidency due to this explicit scenario. If push comes to shove, they could always build a wall.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7269834304388156714" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-21T17:50:19+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7270215433377254702</id>
    <title>Ukraine Destroys Russian Supersonic Bomber #ukraine #russia  Ukraine has destroyed Russia’s supersonic bomber. Now Russia claims it’s only damaged, but judging by the photo. Looks pretty bad to me. Russia called this a terrorist act but hitting a bomber o</title>
    <updated>2023-08-22T18:29:15+00:00</updated>
    <content>Ukraine Destroys Russian Supersonic Bomber #ukraine #russia  Ukraine has destroyed Russia’s supersonic bomber. Now Russia claims it’s only damaged, but judging by the photo. Looks pretty bad to me. Russia called this a terrorist act but hitting a bomber on a military base is the furthest thing from terrorism. A terrorist act is hitting entire apartment buildings with missiles like this supersonic bomber has done since the beginning of the war.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7270215433377254702" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-22T18:29:15+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
