<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-07-24T21:18:27+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7258692381627780394</id>
    <title>Russia Buzzes Another US Plane #usa #russia  Russia has buzzed yet another US plane. Earlier this week Russia flew dangerously close to a manned US spy plane over Syria and endangered the lives of 4 Americans. This comes as Russia is attempting to break a</title>
    <updated>2023-07-22T17:13:58+00:00</updated>
    <content>Russia Buzzes Another US Plane #usa #russia  Russia has buzzed yet another US plane. Earlier this week Russia flew dangerously close to a manned US spy plane over Syria and endangered the lives of 4 Americans. This comes as Russia is attempting to break a record of harassment, after they’ve harassed the US’s drones, planes, and troops over 5 times this month by dropping fuel on them, buzzing them, and dropping flares on them. The US has urged Russia to cut it out, saying that Russia should act like a professional air force so we can resume our focus on the enduring defeat of.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7258692381627780394" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-22T17:13:58+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7258729696563596586</id>
    <title>Ukraine To Sink All Ships Going To Russia #ukraine #russia  Ukraine is now threatening a tit-for-tat against Russia after Russia threatened to sink civilian vessels traveling to Ukraine. With Ukraine now saying that all ships heading to Russia will be con</title>
    <updated>2023-07-22T19:38:41+00:00</updated>
    <content>Ukraine To Sink All Ships Going To Russia #ukraine #russia  Ukraine is now threatening a tit-for-tat against Russia after Russia threatened to sink civilian vessels traveling to Ukraine. With Ukraine now saying that all ships heading to Russia will be considered to be carrying military cargo with all corresponding risks. This comes after Russia blew up over 60,000 tons of grain meant for China in a Ukrainian port. Russia’s goal is to scare ships from going to Ukrainian ports and now Ukraine is doing the same to Russia. What a fun time to be a fisherman in the Black Sea</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7258729696563596586" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-22T19:38:41+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7259086473260010794</id>
    <title>Wagner Wants To Invade Poland #poland #russia  Wagner wants to invade Poland! Belarus says Wagner is stressing them out because they want to invade Poland and that they’ve been “bugging” them to strike Warsaw. And Belarus says it’s been begging them not t</title>
    <updated>2023-07-23T18:43:12+00:00</updated>
    <content>Wagner Wants To Invade Poland #poland #russia  Wagner wants to invade Poland! Belarus says Wagner is stressing them out because they want to invade Poland and that they’ve been “bugging” them to strike Warsaw. And Belarus says it’s been begging them not to and that they’re having a hard time controlling them. There are few things the extremely capable Polish military would enjoy more than erasing every member of Wagner stupid enough to cross their border.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7259086473260010794" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-23T18:43:12+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7259474763851042091</id>
    <title>UN Trying To Save US Soldier From North Korea #usa #korea  The UN has begun talks with North Korea about Travis King, the U.S. soldier who ran into North Korea. King hasn’t been seen since he ran across the border and was shoved into a van and driven off </title>
    <updated>2023-07-24T19:49:54+00:00</updated>
    <content>UN Trying To Save US Soldier From North Korea #usa #korea  The UN has begun talks with North Korea about Travis King, the U.S. soldier who ran into North Korea. King hasn’t been seen since he ran across the border and was shoved into a van and driven off by North Korean soldiers. The US says they’re not ruling out that he contacted North Korea beforehand but currently they don’t believe he was in prior contact. New reports suggest that there was a 13 hour gap between when he escaped the airport and when he crossed into the North. North Korea has so far refused to talk to the U.S. about the issue.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7259474763851042091" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-24T19:49:54+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7259497585491184938</id>
    <title>China Is Now Supplying Russia In Ukraine #ukraine #russia  China is supplying Russia with enough gear to equip the entire Russian army. China has been supplying Russia with dual use equipment - so things that are civilian but could be used for military pu</title>
    <updated>2023-07-24T21:18:27+00:00</updated>
    <content>China Is Now Supplying Russia In Ukraine #ukraine #russia  China is supplying Russia with enough gear to equip the entire Russian army. China has been supplying Russia with dual use equipment - so things that are civilian but could be used for military purposes. So for example: Russia has imported over 100 million dollars worth of drones from China this year as well as 225 million dollars of Ceramic. This goes right up to the West’s red line.. with both France and the U.S. telling China earlier this month that they rely on the west and that they won’t hesitate to cut them off. While it’s clear that China is not a neutral actor unless they cross the red line of supplying munitions and equipment,. They’re unlikely to face sanctions</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7259497585491184938" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-24T21:18:27+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
