<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-10-19T21:28:26+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7289571920750677291</id>
    <title>Terror Attack Rocks France As Israeli Invasion Is Imminent #usa #israel  Israel has told a hospital in Northern Gaza that they have two hours to evacuate according to doctors without borders. The hospital says this is just not possible. Politico says Isra</title>
    <updated>2023-10-13T22:22:16+00:00</updated>
    <content>Terror Attack Rocks France As Israeli Invasion Is Imminent #usa #israel  Israel has told a hospital in Northern Gaza that they have two hours to evacuate according to doctors without borders. The hospital says this is just not possible. Politico says Israel’s ground invasion is imminent. The US is urging Israel to delay their imminent ground operation until safe passage for Palestinians can be secured. Meanwhile Egypt says Israel’s mass evacuation notice is a serious breach of international humanitarian law but Egypt has also taken “unprecedented measures” to reinforce its border with Gaza to prevent any breaches and is resisting pressure from the US to open a humanitarian corridor for Palestinians according to the Financial Times. Biden says it’s a priority of his to address this humanitarian crisis, and that the overwhelming majority of Palestinians had nothing to do with Hamas and the appalling attacks. France has declared a maximum security alert because a knife attack done by an Islamic terrorist in France has been linked to the events we just discussed. Macron said that the French Police thwarted another attack earlier in the day. Macron said France had been “hit once again by the barbarity of Islamist terrorism.” The UK is drawing up rules to deport foreign students, academics, and workers who commit antisemitic acts or praise Hamas.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7289571920750677291" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-13T22:22:16+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7290684236640685355</id>
    <title>Iran Warns Israel Of Intervention #usa #israel  Iran sent a warning to Israel through the United Nations saying: that if they continue their operation in Gaza, they will intervene in the conflict according to Axios. The US has sent a second aircraft carri</title>
    <updated>2023-10-16T22:18:41+00:00</updated>
    <content>Iran Warns Israel Of Intervention #usa #israel  Iran sent a warning to Israel through the United Nations saying: that if they continue their operation in Gaza, they will intervene in the conflict according to Axios. The US has sent a second aircraft carrier to the region and has selected 2,000 troops to prepare for a potential deployment to support Israel. When asked if the US can support both Ukraine and Israel, President Biden said “We're the United States of America for God's sake. The most powerful nation in the history of the world.” He also called on Hamas to be destroyed but reiterated his support for a Palestinian state. Palestine’s President has condemned Hamas’ attacks and says that Hamas doesn’t represent the Palestinian people but then the remarks were later deleted without explanation. Israel is rushing to deploy a giant laser for the first time in the world according to Channel 14 in Israel. The giant laser is supposed to work as an air defense system. Israel and Hezbollah are continuing to exchange an increasing amount of fire with each other across the border as the situation escalates rapidly.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7290684236640685355" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-16T22:18:41+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7291002229492878638</id>
    <title>US Gets Israel To Allow Aid To Gaza #usa #israel  After 8 hours of negotiations with Israel, the United States has convinced Israel to agree to develop a plan to let humanitarian aid flow into Gaza as well as create areas to keep civilians out of harm's w</title>
    <updated>2023-10-17T18:52:30+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Gets Israel To Allow Aid To Gaza #usa #israel  After 8 hours of negotiations with Israel, the United States has convinced Israel to agree to develop a plan to let humanitarian aid flow into Gaza as well as create areas to keep civilians out of harm's way. The US warned that if Hamas tries to block or seize the aid, the US will prevent it from happening. President Biden will go to Israel tomorrow, where he will be presented with a plan from Israel on how they plan to conduct their operation in a way that minimizes civilian casualties according to the State Department. They will also present him with a briefing on their war strategy. After this, Biden will fly to Jordan where he will meet with the President of Palestine and Egypt, and the King of Jordan. The King of Jordan says that Egypt and Israel will not accept any refugees or support Israel’s operation to take out Hamas but President Biden seems determined to change that. Secretary Blinken has taken 13 trips in the past 72 hours between 8 different Middle Eastern capitals in an effort to prevent an escalation of this war.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7291002229492878638" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-17T18:52:30+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7291398010318163246</id>
    <title>Hospital In Gaza Hit By Rogue Missile #usa #israel  Yesterday a hospital in Gaza was hit by a rogue missile. Visual evidence from Palestinians, an independent assessment from the Pentagon, and overwhelming evidence released by the IDF suggest this was a P</title>
    <updated>2023-10-18T20:28:19+00:00</updated>
    <content>Hospital In Gaza Hit By Rogue Missile #usa #israel  Yesterday a hospital in Gaza was hit by a rogue missile. Visual evidence from Palestinians, an independent assessment from the Pentagon, and overwhelming evidence released by the IDF suggest this was a PIJ rocket that misfired. The US has also collected “high confidence” signals intelligence that this was caused by the PIJ. President Biden also went as far to say that the Department of Defense concluded that it wasn’t Israel based on their own intelligence. The IDF also released an alleged audio recording between two Hamas members discussing the rocket that misfired. Contrary to initial claims, the hospital wasn't completely destroyed. It's still standing and footage from the ground shows that the worst damage was done in the parking lot. The crater in the ground is consistent with militant missiles, not Israeli JDAMs according to most experts. Hamas claims that nearly 500 were killed. But due to the seeming lack of major damage to any of the nearby buildings or independent verification of those numbers, people are starting to doubt that figure. The facts of what actually happened differ from what mainstream media and several other news creators initially reported yesterday because they ran with Hamas’ narrative. With Al-Jazeera, BBC, MSNBC among several others all saying with certainty that Israel had done this. This misinformation resulted in widespread riots and protests outside of US embassies across the Middle East. As well as regional-wide condemnation of Israel, calls to war by Hezbollah and Iran, and drones launched at US bases in Iraq. Today should serve as a day of reflection for the media and news influencers since they almost started a region-wide war yesterday. Taking a second to make sure what you have is correct is more important than being first because someone’s going to get there before you do anyways.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7291398010318163246" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-18T20:28:19+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7291784553260125486</id>
    <title>US Forces Under Assault Across Middle East #usa #israel  The United States has issued a very rare worldwide caution travel alert due to the risk of terror attacks, protests, and violent actions against Americans. Reuters reports that US officials say that</title>
    <updated>2023-10-19T21:28:26+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Forces Under Assault Across Middle East #usa #israel  The United States has issued a very rare worldwide caution travel alert due to the risk of terror attacks, protests, and violent actions against Americans. Reuters reports that US officials say that a Hezebollah linked terror group used drones to attack a US Military base in Syria today causing minor injuries. Meanwhile the Pentagon says a US Navy warship operating in the Northern Red Sea today intercepted 3 cruise missiles and several drones that were fired from the Houthi militant group in Yemen. The Pentagon says the missiles were potentially headed towards Israel which is why they intercepted them, but that they can’t currently confirm that Israel was the target. Channel 13 in Israel is reporting that Israel believes that the missiles were launched at them. And just now Reuters is reporting that two security sources tell them that yet another US base in Iraq has been hit with drones and missiles, this is reportedly the 5th attack on US forces in Iraq and Syria in the past 36 hours. The US has also ordered Americans to leave Lebanon as soon as possible and has changed its travel advisory to “Do Not Travel”.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7291784553260125486" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-19T21:28:26+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
