<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-08-03T17:03:50+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7262772636801895723</id>
    <title>Belarusian Helicopters Cross Into Poland #usa #poland  Two Belarusian helicopters crossed into Poland earlier today violating their airspace during a training exercise. In response, Poland is deploying additional troops and combat helicopters to the borde</title>
    <updated>2023-08-02T17:07:16+00:00</updated>
    <content>Belarusian Helicopters Cross Into Poland #usa #poland  Two Belarusian helicopters crossed into Poland earlier today violating their airspace during a training exercise. In response, Poland is deploying additional troops and combat helicopters to the border with Belarus. This comes after the US said that an attack by Wagner will be considered an attack by Russia. However the US says it’s aware of the threats Wagner is making to Poland but that it’s unaware of any credible threats to Poland.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7262772636801895723" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-02T17:07:16+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7262783774134471978</id>
    <title>US Evacuates Embassy In Niger #usa #nigeria  The U.S. is preparing to evacuate its embassy in Niger but as of right now, its 2K troops are staying put. The junta in Niger has requested the rapid deployment of Wagner to the country. ECOWAS says the militar</title>
    <updated>2023-08-02T17:50:30+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Evacuates Embassy In Niger #usa #nigeria  The U.S. is preparing to evacuate its embassy in Niger but as of right now, its 2K troops are staying put. The junta in Niger has requested the rapid deployment of Wagner to the country. ECOWAS says the military option is the very last option on the table, but that they need to prepare for that eventuality. Nigeria has cut all electricity to the country as Niger plunges into darkness and rolling blackouts. There are 4 days left on the war deadline.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7262783774134471978" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-02T17:50:30+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7262807707504102698</id>
    <title>Reports Of Mass Shooting At US Capitol #usa #america  The U.S. Capitol is on lockdown after reports of a mass shooter in the Senate. All Senate offices have been evacuated by armed police, and now additional buildings are being evacuated. Capitol Police a</title>
    <updated>2023-08-02T19:23:23+00:00</updated>
    <content>Reports Of Mass Shooting At US Capitol #usa #america  The U.S. Capitol is on lockdown after reports of a mass shooter in the Senate. All Senate offices have been evacuated by armed police, and now additional buildings are being evacuated. Capitol Police are asking people remaining to barricade themselves in their offices.A massive police response is currently underway. It should be stressed though that Capitol police have yet to hear gunshots or seen evidence of a shooter.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7262807707504102698" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-02T19:23:23+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7262825176608345386</id>
    <title>Replying to @Philip DeFranco Senate Active Shooter Was Prank Call Capitol Police say that the 911 call about an active shooter may have been a “prank call”. All buildings have been cleared and Capitol Police reportedly sealed off all of the Senate’s under</title>
    <updated>2023-08-02T20:31:10+00:00</updated>
    <content>Replying to @Philip DeFranco Senate Active Shooter Was Prank Call Capitol Police say that the 911 call about an active shooter may have been a “prank call”. All buildings have been cleared and Capitol Police reportedly sealed off all of the Senate’s underground tunnels. No shooter has been located and so far no injuries reported. Police are still searching but this does appear to be a false alarm.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7262825176608345386" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-02T20:31:10+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7263142801657924906</id>
    <title>Coalition To Liberate Niger Grows #niger #usa  Ivory Coast, Senegal, and Benin say they will participate in ECOWAS’s military coalition to restore democracy in Niger. China has told its citizens in the country to prepare for an emergency. America has put </title>
    <updated>2023-08-03T17:03:50+00:00</updated>
    <content>Coalition To Liberate Niger Grows #niger #usa  Ivory Coast, Senegal, and Benin say they will participate in ECOWAS’s military coalition to restore democracy in Niger. China has told its citizens in the country to prepare for an emergency. America has put Niger on its Do Not Travel list and has ordered all non-essential government employees and their families to leave. The US also told the ousted President of Niger that it remains committed to restoring democracy. New reports say that the Junta was in contact with Mali and Burkina Faso before they even took power suggesting that at some level Russia and Wagner have been involved since the very start. We’re now 3 days away from the war deadline with no sign of a diplomatic solution on the horizon. #ivorycoast #benin #senegal #nigeria </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7263142801657924906" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-03T17:03:50+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
