<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-09-07T20:44:22+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7275506222642695470</id>
    <title>US Places Nuclear Weapons In Britain #usa #uk  The U.S. may return it’s nuclear weapons to British soil for the first time in 15 years. The Air Force has secured funding to build a dormitory to house increased personnel due to a potential nuclear mission.</title>
    <updated>2023-09-06T00:40:05+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Places Nuclear Weapons In Britain #usa #uk  The U.S. may return it’s nuclear weapons to British soil for the first time in 15 years. The Air Force has secured funding to build a dormitory to house increased personnel due to a potential nuclear mission. This comes as the nuclear capable F-35 has been deployed to the UK. And Russia has taken notice with them saying that the return of US nuclear weapons to the UK will be seen as an escalation.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7275506222642695470" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-06T00:40:05+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7275787044721413422</id>
    <title>Passenger Coats Plane In Diarrhea #usa #airplane  A flight from Atlanta to Barcelona was forced to turn around 2 hours into the journey because a passenger had diarrhea all throughout the airplane. Passengers say it dribbled down the aisle and that they t</title>
    <updated>2023-09-06T18:49:50+00:00</updated>
    <content>Passenger Coats Plane In Diarrhea #usa #airplane  A flight from Atlanta to Barcelona was forced to turn around 2 hours into the journey because a passenger had diarrhea all throughout the airplane. Passengers say it dribbled down the aisle and that they tried to cover up the smell with vanilla but it just smelt like vanilla diarrhea. I do feel bad for the diarrhea passenger because not only did you cover the plane in diarrhea but then you had to sit in it for the next 2 hours, and the rest of the plane is mad at you for ruining their vacation. They’re getting off the plane pointing at you saying “that’s the diarrhea guy” and then just when you think the humiliation is over… it’s front page news across the country.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7275787044721413422" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-06T18:49:50+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7275825668666051882</id>
    <title>Romania Notifies NATO Of Russian Attack On Country #romania #usa  Romania has found the Russian drone that they denied hit them. With the Romanian defense minister saying: “If it is confirmed that these elements come from a Russian drone, such a situation</title>
    <updated>2023-09-06T21:19:48+00:00</updated>
    <content>Romania Notifies NATO Of Russian Attack On Country #romania #usa  Romania has found the Russian drone that they denied hit them. With the Romanian defense minister saying: “If it is confirmed that these elements come from a Russian drone, such a situation would be completely inadmissible and a serious violation of the sovereignty and territorial integrity of Romania, a NATO member.” It’s unclear what Romania’s retaliation will be but they did notify NATO today of the attack. Romania could technically invoke NATO’s Article 5 if they want to but are we really gonna do this over a drone hitting an empty field?</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7275825668666051882" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-06T21:19:48+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7276169703960186154</id>
    <title>Man Arrested After Trying To Hamster Wheel To London #usa #london #florida  A Florida man crossing the Atlantic Ocean in a hamster wheel has been arrested after a three day stand off. The man set off from Florida and intended to go to London by running on</title>
    <updated>2023-09-07T19:34:48+00:00</updated>
    <content>Man Arrested After Trying To Hamster Wheel To London #usa #london #florida  A Florida man crossing the Atlantic Ocean in a hamster wheel has been arrested after a three day stand off. The man set off from Florida and intended to go to London by running on the wheel but 70 miles into his journey - the Coast Guard stopped him. Now you’re probably wondering “where in the law does it say it’s illegal to hamster wheel across the ocean”. And look it might not be illegal, but the issue is that our Hero went rogue when the Coast Guard approached his wheel. He was finally arrested after a 3 day standoff and has been charged with obstructing a boarding and violation of a Captain of the Port order. BUT It turns out this is his 4th time attempting this and in 2002, he was arrested trying to illegally enter the US. But the Judge let him off and granted him asylum after he promised to run from LA to New York City to commemorate the second anniversary of 9/11. He was set free on $250,000 bond with the terms that he can’t go into the ocean or board a vessel on the ocean.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7276169703960186154" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-07T19:34:48+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7276187616238718254</id>
    <title>Hong Kong Experiencing Apocalyptic Floods #hongkong #china  Hong Kong is experiencing apocalyptic floods. In just one hour, it rained 6 inches. That’s the most since records began in 1884. Buses are flooding, The subways are flooding, and you could take b</title>
    <updated>2023-09-07T20:44:22+00:00</updated>
    <content>Hong Kong Experiencing Apocalyptic Floods #hongkong #china  Hong Kong is experiencing apocalyptic floods. In just one hour, it rained 6 inches. That’s the most since records began in 1884. Buses are flooding, The subways are flooding, and you could take boats down these streets because they’re being turned into rivers. It’s so bad that cars in the street are being forced to a total stop by the water.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7276187616238718254" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-07T20:44:22+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
