<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-10-16T23:50:31+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7289210719046831403</id>
    <title>Israel Strikes Syria In Growing War #usa #israel  Israel struck Syria’s two main airports last night to put them out of service according to Al-Jazeera, which is thought to have been done to stop Iranian assistance. https://x.com/IAFsite/status/1712484101</title>
    <updated>2023-10-12T23:00:36+00:00</updated>
    <content>Israel Strikes Syria In Growing War #usa #israel  Israel struck Syria’s two main airports last night to put them out of service according to Al-Jazeera, which is thought to have been done to stop Iranian assistance. https://x.com/IAFsite/status/1712484101763342772?s=20has also dropped over 6,000 bombs on Gaza since Sunday. The IDF also claims that they have a list of everyone who participated in the terror attack and that the air force will reach every one of them. The UK will send part of the Royal navy to Israel as a show of support and to conduct surveillance flights over israel. The US and Qatar have reached a “quiet understanding” to not give Iran any of the 6 Billion that was unfrozen, according to CBS News. 27 Americans have now been killed in the attacks on Israel, 14 are still missing. Secretary Blinken in Israel today said “This is the equivalent of ten 9/11s” - what he means is population scaling. If what happened in Israel happened in America that would mean 48,000 people dead. France has banned Pro-Palestine protests because they are “likely to generate disturbances to the public order”</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7289210719046831403" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-12T23:00:36+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7289523296746360107</id>
    <title>Israel Gives 24 Hours To Evacuate Gaza #usa #israel  Israel has told the United Nations that they have 24 hours to evacuate Northern Gaza to the south. But The UN says that its impossible to evacuate 1.1 million people in less than 24 hours. And Hamas is </title>
    <updated>2023-10-13T19:13:31+00:00</updated>
    <content>Israel Gives 24 Hours To Evacuate Gaza #usa #israel  Israel has told the United Nations that they have 24 hours to evacuate Northern Gaza to the south. But The UN says that its impossible to evacuate 1.1 million people in less than 24 hours. And Hamas is telling people not to evacuate, saying its propaganda according to Al-Jazeera. Israel is expected to begin its ground invasion of Gaza as soon as this weekend. Iran says that there is a real possibility of more fronts opening against Israel. Human rights Watch has accused Israel of using White Phosphorus while others have accused them of flat out revenge bombing.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7289523296746360107" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-13T19:13:31+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7289571920750677291</id>
    <title>Terror Attack Rocks France As Israeli Invasion Is Imminent #usa #israel  Israel has told a hospital in Northern Gaza that they have two hours to evacuate according to doctors without borders. The hospital says this is just not possible. Politico says Isra</title>
    <updated>2023-10-13T22:22:16+00:00</updated>
    <content>Terror Attack Rocks France As Israeli Invasion Is Imminent #usa #israel  Israel has told a hospital in Northern Gaza that they have two hours to evacuate according to doctors without borders. The hospital says this is just not possible. Politico says Israel’s ground invasion is imminent. The US is urging Israel to delay their imminent ground operation until safe passage for Palestinians can be secured. Meanwhile Egypt says Israel’s mass evacuation notice is a serious breach of international humanitarian law but Egypt has also taken “unprecedented measures” to reinforce its border with Gaza to prevent any breaches and is resisting pressure from the US to open a humanitarian corridor for Palestinians according to the Financial Times. Biden says it’s a priority of his to address this humanitarian crisis, and that the overwhelming majority of Palestinians had nothing to do with Hamas and the appalling attacks. France has declared a maximum security alert because a knife attack done by an Islamic terrorist in France has been linked to the events we just discussed. Macron said that the French Police thwarted another attack earlier in the day. Macron said France had been “hit once again by the barbarity of Islamist terrorism.” The UK is drawing up rules to deport foreign students, academics, and workers who commit antisemitic acts or praise Hamas.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7289571920750677291" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-13T22:22:16+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7290684236640685355</id>
    <title>Iran Warns Israel Of Intervention #usa #israel  Iran sent a warning to Israel through the United Nations saying: that if they continue their operation in Gaza, they will intervene in the conflict according to Axios. The US has sent a second aircraft carri</title>
    <updated>2023-10-16T22:18:41+00:00</updated>
    <content>Iran Warns Israel Of Intervention #usa #israel  Iran sent a warning to Israel through the United Nations saying: that if they continue their operation in Gaza, they will intervene in the conflict according to Axios. The US has sent a second aircraft carrier to the region and has selected 2,000 troops to prepare for a potential deployment to support Israel. When asked if the US can support both Ukraine and Israel, President Biden said “We're the United States of America for God's sake. The most powerful nation in the history of the world.” He also called on Hamas to be destroyed but reiterated his support for a Palestinian state. Palestine’s President has condemned Hamas’ attacks and says that Hamas doesn’t represent the Palestinian people but then the remarks were later deleted without explanation. Israel is rushing to deploy a giant laser for the first time in the world according to Channel 14 in Israel. The giant laser is supposed to work as an air defense system. Israel and Hezbollah are continuing to exchange an increasing amount of fire with each other across the border as the situation escalates rapidly.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7290684236640685355" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-16T22:18:41+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7290707916590550314</id>
    <title>US Warns Iran To Not Escalate With Israel #usa #israel  The US has warned Iran to not escalate the conflict with Israel, this comes as the US has deployed another carrier and is preparing troops for deployment. Israel turned water back on for Gaza after P</title>
    <updated>2023-10-16T23:50:31+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Warns Iran To Not Escalate With Israel #usa #israel  The US has warned Iran to not escalate the conflict with Israel, this comes as the US has deployed another carrier and is preparing troops for deployment. Israel turned water back on for Gaza after President Biden pressured them to do so. Biden is also pushing Israel to demonstrate restraint. Acknowledging that Israel has a right to destroy Hamas but not a right to subject Palestine to collective punishment. He also warned against occupying Gaza. Israel’s ground offensive is still expected, but keeps getting delayed by rain.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7290707916590550314" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-16T23:50:31+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
