<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-09-25T16:45:05+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7281410415370964270</id>
    <title>India Says Quebec Should Be Free #canada #india  India says it should have a referendum on Quebec’s independence from Canada. Also saying that Canada’s reputation is now being a “safe haven for terror”. This comes as India has suspended visa services for </title>
    <updated>2023-09-21T22:31:22+00:00</updated>
    <content>India Says Quebec Should Be Free #canada #india  India says it should have a referendum on Quebec’s independence from Canada. Also saying that Canada’s reputation is now being a “safe haven for terror”. This comes as India has suspended visa services for Canadians and has demanded that Canada reduce the amount of staff in it’s embassy in India. Saying that Canada has interfered in their domestic affairs… which actually kind of seems like admission of guilt. India continues to deny the accusation but Canada has rejected India’s denial and is urging India to cooperate in the investigation.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7281410415370964270" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-21T22:31:22+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7281426848012061994</id>
    <title>America abandons Canada #usa #canada  American has abandoned Canada. India has reportedly reached out to the US to offer to cooperate with Canada if they release the evidence publicly. It’s unclear why India didn’t just tell Canada this directly but it’s </title>
    <updated>2023-09-21T23:35:06+00:00</updated>
    <content>America abandons Canada #usa #canada  American has abandoned Canada. India has reportedly reached out to the US to offer to cooperate with Canada if they release the evidence publicly. It’s unclear why India didn’t just tell Canada this directly but it’s possible that the Indian government is just lying and is assuming the US won’t involve itself. India is having a full scale meltdown and is throwing gasoline on this fire, making themselves look more guilty in the process as Canada continues to wonder why the US and UK, who helped indict India, are staying silent. As one Canadian in our comments put it “America loves this kind of thing. They love to stick up for the little guy &amp; raise hell but not when it comes to us I guess. Maybe China would be a more dependable ally.”</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7281426848012061994" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-21T23:35:06+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7281769554341088555</id>
    <title>Canada Has India Dead To Rights #canada #india #usa  Canada has India dead to rights in the murder of a Canadian citizen. The Canadian government &amp; an unidentified Five Eyes member reportedly amassed tons of intelligence on India including communications </title>
    <updated>2023-09-22T21:44:59+00:00</updated>
    <content>Canada Has India Dead To Rights #canada #india #usa  Canada has India dead to rights in the murder of a Canadian citizen. The Canadian government &amp; an unidentified Five Eyes member reportedly amassed tons of intelligence on India including communications involving Indian officials themselves, including Indian diplomats present in Canada. This reportedly includes texts and recorded calls. Also Canadian officials say that when pressed behind closed doors, no Indian official has denied the bombshell allegation. The US now says that India will not get a free pass after public pressure mounted over the US’ initially staying silent over the row. President Biden reportedly raised the issue with Modi at the G20 which means that the evidence that India murdered a Canadian is rock solid enough for the President of the United States to take action on it.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7281769554341088555" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-22T21:44:59+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7282086898871455022</id>
    <title>US Navy Is Creating UFOs #usa #america  The US Navy may be creating UFOs unintentionally and that is likely why there are increasing sightings. For at least the past two decades, the US Navy has been researching Laser-Plasma and 3 years ago, they patented</title>
    <updated>2023-09-23T18:16:30+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Navy Is Creating UFOs #usa #america  The US Navy may be creating UFOs unintentionally and that is likely why there are increasing sightings. For at least the past two decades, the US Navy has been researching Laser-Plasma and 3 years ago, they patented the technology. It’s supposed to protect stealth aircraft by using bursts of laser plasma to create or project mid-air images, these images will trick incoming missiles into hitting the hologram. These holograms, for lack of a better term, can be picked up in several wavelengths including infrared and can appear as real objects in them. This technology has also been used to create laser-plasma balls that can transmit human speech, whatever that means. Perhaps the Pentagon changing the term from UFO, unidentified flying object, to UAP, unidentified aerial phenomena, is further evidence of this. So it seems like aliens are once again not real but who’s to say.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7282086898871455022" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-23T18:16:30+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7282805487853145386</id>
    <title>India Threatens To Kill Americans #usa #india  The FBI has visited Sikh leaders in the United States to warn them that there have been credible threats against their lives from India. This comes after India murdered a Canadian Sikh leader. Across the Unit</title>
    <updated>2023-09-25T16:45:05+00:00</updated>
    <content>India Threatens To Kill Americans #usa #india  The FBI has visited Sikh leaders in the United States to warn them that there have been credible threats against their lives from India. This comes after India murdered a Canadian Sikh leader. Across the United States, local law enforcement is reportedly reaching out to Sikh communities with warnings regarding potential threats from India. America is India’s largest trade partner and killing an American in the US would undoubtedly result in India’s economy being completely crippled, if not military action. The US says there must be accountability from India.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7282805487853145386" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-25T16:45:05+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
