<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-08-17T21:25:31+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7267280227997437227</id>
    <title>US &amp; France Fighting Over World War Africa #usa #france  The US and France are fighting over World War Africa. France reportedly actively favors and wants to support the military intervention into Niger. While the U.S. actively opposes military interventi</title>
    <updated>2023-08-14T20:39:03+00:00</updated>
    <content>US &amp; France Fighting Over World War Africa #usa #france  The US and France are fighting over World War Africa. France reportedly actively favors and wants to support the military intervention into Niger. While the U.S. actively opposes military intervention and wants to seek diplomatic solutions to the crisis. France believes the US is being “unwise” in their attempts at diplomacy, but the US views the consequences of destabilization as counterproductive to its anti-terror mission. The U.S. currently has a massive drone base in Niger that it uses to combat terrorism across all of Western and Northern Africa.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7267280227997437227" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-14T20:39:03+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7267329367859137838</id>
    <title>North Korea Is Preparing For Offensive War #usa #korea  North Korea says it’s preparing for an offensive war against South Korea. This comes after the defense chief hinted at a preemptive nuclear strike. In response, the US and South Korea will strengthen</title>
    <updated>2023-08-14T23:49:46+00:00</updated>
    <content>North Korea Is Preparing For Offensive War #usa #korea  North Korea says it’s preparing for an offensive war against South Korea. This comes after the defense chief hinted at a preemptive nuclear strike. In response, the US and South Korea will strengthen their defense and surveillance posture. They will also be conducting military exercises later this month. North Korea is expected to make more provocations in response.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7267329367859137838" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-14T23:49:46+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7267663518541876526</id>
    <title>Al-Qaeda Calls For Revenge On Sweden &amp; Denmark #sweden #denmark  Al-Qaeda has called for revenge attacks on Sweden and Denmark. This comes after people in the two countries burned Qurans. With Al-Qaeda saying “Denmark and Sweden are two small, despicable </title>
    <updated>2023-08-15T21:26:27+00:00</updated>
    <content>Al-Qaeda Calls For Revenge On Sweden &amp; Denmark #sweden #denmark  Al-Qaeda has called for revenge attacks on Sweden and Denmark. This comes after people in the two countries burned Qurans. With Al-Qaeda saying “Denmark and Sweden are two small, despicable countries that amount to no more than two small spots on the world map” And then it called upon Muslims to take revenge on them.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7267663518541876526" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-15T21:26:27+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7267985946149408046</id>
    <title>US Soldier Fled To North Korea To Escape Racism In America #usa #korea #america  North Korea says the U.S. soldier, Travis King, who ran into the country did so because of racism in the United States. They say he says he suffered inhuman treatment and rac</title>
    <updated>2023-08-16T18:17:36+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Soldier Fled To North Korea To Escape Racism In America #usa #korea #america  North Korea says the U.S. soldier, Travis King, who ran into the country did so because of racism in the United States. They say he says he suffered inhuman treatment and racial discrimination in the US Army. They also claim he wants to seek refugee in North Korea or in a 3rd country because he’s disillusioned at “unequal American society”. Travis King was being sent back to the United States due to several crimes he had committed in South Korea when he ran into North Korea.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7267985946149408046" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-16T18:17:36+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7268405461618052394</id>
    <title>US Asks Iran To Stop Giving Drones To Russia #usa #russia  The US has asked Iran to stop selling drones to Russia. Currently the U.S. and Iran are conducting indirect talks in Oman which is an absolutely ridiculous thing. The two governments want to make </title>
    <updated>2023-08-17T21:25:31+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Asks Iran To Stop Giving Drones To Russia #usa #russia  The US has asked Iran to stop selling drones to Russia. Currently the U.S. and Iran are conducting indirect talks in Oman which is an absolutely ridiculous thing. The two governments want to make a deal with each other but they refuse to speak to each other so Omani officials have to go between the two rooms delivering messages between them. Anyways the US asked them to stop supplying drones to Russia and while Iran officially denies that their drones are being used - they told the US that they have asked Moscow to stop but the US wants more concrete steps.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7268405461618052394" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-17T21:25:31+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
