<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-07-20T20:02:10+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7257275236784065835</id>
    <title>Russia Threatens South Africa With War #russia #southafrica  Russia has threatened to declare war on South Africa. South Africa has been warning Putin to not physically come to the country next month because they have a legal obligation to arrest him. And</title>
    <updated>2023-07-18T21:34:31+00:00</updated>
    <content>Russia Threatens South Africa With War #russia #southafrica  Russia has threatened to declare war on South Africa. South Africa has been warning Putin to not physically come to the country next month because they have a legal obligation to arrest him. And Putin doesn’t care and he says he’s coming to South Africa no matter what and if they arrest him, it’s war. So now South Africa is asking the international criminal court for permission to not arrest Putin due to the Russian threat of war.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7257275236784065835" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-18T21:34:31+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7257568244893044010</id>
    <title>Russia Backs Down To South Africa #russia #southafrica  Russia has backed down to South Africa. After months of warning Putin not to come to South Africa and him threatening to declare war on the country if they try to arrest him when he visits, he is now</title>
    <updated>2023-07-19T16:31:44+00:00</updated>
    <content>Russia Backs Down To South Africa #russia #southafrica  Russia has backed down to South Africa. After months of warning Putin not to come to South Africa and him threatening to declare war on the country if they try to arrest him when he visits, he is now no longer coming. He desperately wanted to come to the BRICS summit but it seems as though he’ll have to use zoom to speak to his fake alliance.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7257568244893044010" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-19T16:31:44+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7257610229901200682</id>
    <title>Russia To Sink All Ships Heading To Ukraine #russia #ukraine  Russia has announced that they will now be sinking all ships heading to Ukrainian ports. They’re now considering all ships, including those carrying people and wheat, to be potential carriers o</title>
    <updated>2023-07-19T19:14:32+00:00</updated>
    <content>Russia To Sink All Ships Heading To Ukraine #russia #ukraine  Russia has announced that they will now be sinking all ships heading to Ukrainian ports. They’re now considering all ships, including those carrying people and wheat, to be potential carriers of military cargo starting at midnight tonight. Russia added that the countries with their flags on the ships will now be considered part of the war. Ukraine has called for an international escort in the Black Sea. With Ukraine being unable to export wheat due to this, the developing world will face starvation and become victims of Putin’s war.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7257610229901200682" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-19T19:14:32+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7257649692371160363</id>
    <title>This Is Why A US Soldier Defected To North Korea #usa #korea  Travis King, the US soldier, who defected to North Korea was reportedly facing two assault allegations and was fined for damaging a South Korean police car. He still remains in North Korean cus</title>
    <updated>2023-07-19T21:47:44+00:00</updated>
    <content>This Is Why A US Soldier Defected To North Korea #usa #korea  Travis King, the US soldier, who defected to North Korea was reportedly facing two assault allegations and was fined for damaging a South Korean police car. He still remains in North Korean custody and his status is unknown, although the U.S. says it’s committed to getting him back. His mom says she just can’t see her son defecting to North Korea.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7257649692371160363" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-19T21:47:44+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7257993609507556651</id>
    <title>Swedish Embassy Burned Down #sweden #iraq  Protesters stormed the Swedish embassy in Baghdad and set it on fire in response to Quran burnings in Sweden. All because an Iraqi living in Sweden is planning to exercise his freedom of speech by burning another</title>
    <updated>2023-07-20T20:02:10+00:00</updated>
    <content>Swedish Embassy Burned Down #sweden #iraq  Protesters stormed the Swedish embassy in Baghdad and set it on fire in response to Quran burnings in Sweden. All because an Iraqi living in Sweden is planning to exercise his freedom of speech by burning another Quran today and now an Iraqi flag outside of the Iraqi embassy to Sweden. Swedish and Iraqi authorities have exchanged threats with each other over the two sets of protests and both have condemned each other. And Iraq has expelled the Swedish ambassador from the country.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7257993609507556651" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-20T20:02:10+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
