<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-07-21T21:54:01+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7257610229901200682</id>
    <title>Russia To Sink All Ships Heading To Ukraine #russia #ukraine  Russia has announced that they will now be sinking all ships heading to Ukrainian ports. They’re now considering all ships, including those carrying people and wheat, to be potential carriers o</title>
    <updated>2023-07-19T19:14:32+00:00</updated>
    <content>Russia To Sink All Ships Heading To Ukraine #russia #ukraine  Russia has announced that they will now be sinking all ships heading to Ukrainian ports. They’re now considering all ships, including those carrying people and wheat, to be potential carriers of military cargo starting at midnight tonight. Russia added that the countries with their flags on the ships will now be considered part of the war. Ukraine has called for an international escort in the Black Sea. With Ukraine being unable to export wheat due to this, the developing world will face starvation and become victims of Putin’s war.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7257610229901200682" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-19T19:14:32+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7257649692371160363</id>
    <title>This Is Why A US Soldier Defected To North Korea #usa #korea  Travis King, the US soldier, who defected to North Korea was reportedly facing two assault allegations and was fined for damaging a South Korean police car. He still remains in North Korean cus</title>
    <updated>2023-07-19T21:47:44+00:00</updated>
    <content>This Is Why A US Soldier Defected To North Korea #usa #korea  Travis King, the US soldier, who defected to North Korea was reportedly facing two assault allegations and was fined for damaging a South Korean police car. He still remains in North Korean custody and his status is unknown, although the U.S. says it’s committed to getting him back. His mom says she just can’t see her son defecting to North Korea.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7257649692371160363" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-19T21:47:44+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7257993609507556651</id>
    <title>Swedish Embassy Burned Down #sweden #iraq  Protesters stormed the Swedish embassy in Baghdad and set it on fire in response to Quran burnings in Sweden. All because an Iraqi living in Sweden is planning to exercise his freedom of speech by burning another</title>
    <updated>2023-07-20T20:02:10+00:00</updated>
    <content>Swedish Embassy Burned Down #sweden #iraq  Protesters stormed the Swedish embassy in Baghdad and set it on fire in response to Quran burnings in Sweden. All because an Iraqi living in Sweden is planning to exercise his freedom of speech by burning another Quran today and now an Iraqi flag outside of the Iraqi embassy to Sweden. Swedish and Iraqi authorities have exchanged threats with each other over the two sets of protests and both have condemned each other. And Iraq has expelled the Swedish ambassador from the country.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7257993609507556651" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-20T20:02:10+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7258004349727657259</id>
    <title>North Korea Says It’ll Nuke USA #usa #korea  North Korea says that the US and South Korea have met the threshold to be hit with a nuclear strike after a U.S. nuclear submarine visited South Korea today. The US and North Korea have had better months. Just </title>
    <updated>2023-07-20T20:43:53+00:00</updated>
    <content>North Korea Says It’ll Nuke USA #usa #korea  North Korea says that the US and South Korea have met the threshold to be hit with a nuclear strike after a U.S. nuclear submarine visited South Korea today. The US and North Korea have had better months. Just this month, North Korea has threatened to shoot down US spy craft and has tested more missiles. And earlier this week a U.S. soldier ran into the country. The U.S. must not have crossed the threshold that hard given that we haven’t been nuked yet.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7258004349727657259" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-20T20:43:53+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7258393488629222698</id>
    <title>US Readies For War With Iran #usa #america  The United States is preparing for an imminent standoff with Iran. In the past two years, Iran has attacked or seized nearly 20 merchant vessels in the Persian gulf. And after it attacked 3 vessels earlier this </title>
    <updated>2023-07-21T21:54:01+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Readies For War With Iran #usa #america  The United States is preparing for an imminent standoff with Iran. In the past two years, Iran has attacked or seized nearly 20 merchant vessels in the Persian gulf. And after it attacked 3 vessels earlier this month, one of which was a US vessel, the US lost patience and deployed F-16s, F-35s, F-22s, and destroyers to the gulf. And now the US is sending an additional 2,000 marines and 3 more warships to the region. The US has been clear, don’t infringe on international shipping lanes and Iran simply doesn't care. In 1987, Iran was sinking Kuwait’s oil tankers. The US Navy began escorting Kuwait’s tankers when an Iranian mine hit a US missile ship. The US destroyed half of Iran’s navy overnight in response. And yet, 40 years later - Iran is still using the half of the Navy that wasn’t sunk to harass shipping lanes. American patience is running out especially now that Iran has detained a fourth US citizen. The message from US Central Command has been clear: we won’t hesitate to protect the flow of international commerce. In addition to a strong statement, the US has been flying A-10s over the Strait of Hormuz all week. Will Iran back down or are we gonna have another event on our hands?</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7258393488629222698" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-21T21:54:01+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
