<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-10-27T20:28:55+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7291784553260125486</id>
    <title>US Forces Under Assault Across Middle East #usa #israel  The United States has issued a very rare worldwide caution travel alert due to the risk of terror attacks, protests, and violent actions against Americans. Reuters reports that US officials say that</title>
    <updated>2023-10-19T21:28:26+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Forces Under Assault Across Middle East #usa #israel  The United States has issued a very rare worldwide caution travel alert due to the risk of terror attacks, protests, and violent actions against Americans. Reuters reports that US officials say that a Hezebollah linked terror group used drones to attack a US Military base in Syria today causing minor injuries. Meanwhile the Pentagon says a US Navy warship operating in the Northern Red Sea today intercepted 3 cruise missiles and several drones that were fired from the Houthi militant group in Yemen. The Pentagon says the missiles were potentially headed towards Israel which is why they intercepted them, but that they can’t currently confirm that Israel was the target. Channel 13 in Israel is reporting that Israel believes that the missiles were launched at them. And just now Reuters is reporting that two security sources tell them that yet another US base in Iraq has been hit with drones and missiles, this is reportedly the 5th attack on US forces in Iraq and Syria in the past 36 hours. The US has also ordered Americans to leave Lebanon as soon as possible and has changed its travel advisory to “Do Not Travel”.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7291784553260125486" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-19T21:28:26+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7293279484566850862</id>
    <title>US Fears Region-Wide War #usa #israel  The US fears a widening region-wide war, US officials tell Axios. With the Pentagon now putting even more troops on “prepare to deploy orders” This comes as the US has sent two aircraft carriers to the region, surged</title>
    <updated>2023-10-23T22:09:25+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Fears Region-Wide War #usa #israel  The US fears a widening region-wide war, US officials tell Axios. With the Pentagon now putting even more troops on “prepare to deploy orders” This comes as the US has sent two aircraft carriers to the region, surged aircraft to its bases in the Middle East, and added more air defense systems and all weekend, US bases all over the region were attacked by terror groups. The rhetoric coming out of Israel and Iran has been white hot, with the BBC reporting that Iran warned Israel that if they don’t stop striking Gaza - the region will spiral out of control. Israel and Hezbollah are continuing to exchange fire with each other on the northern border. With the New York Times reporting that the United States has told Israel to not conduct a preemptive strike on Hezbollah. With the outlet also saying the US believes that Israel would struggle in a two front war, and that such a war would drag both them and Iran into it.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7293279484566850862" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-23T22:09:25+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7293296117683604782</id>
    <title>US Moves Carrier Closer To Iran #usa #israel  The USS Eisenhower, the 2nd aircraft carrier the US sent to Israel, will now move to the Persian Gulf according to the Pentagon. This puts the US closer to its bases in the region and closer to Iran. The Guard</title>
    <updated>2023-10-23T23:14:01+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Moves Carrier Closer To Iran #usa #israel  The USS Eisenhower, the 2nd aircraft carrier the US sent to Israel, will now move to the Persian Gulf according to the Pentagon. This puts the US closer to its bases in the region and closer to Iran. The Guardian is reporting that ISIS and Al-Qaeda are calling on their followers to attack Israel and the US. In other parts of the world: The Philippines has accused China of intentionally colliding with their ships on a resupply mission. The US has sided with the Philippines and once again reaffirmed their mutual defense treaty. In an exclusive, Rolling Stone is reporting that Trump is planning on pulling the United States out of NATO if he wins the Presidency again. Russia began an offensive in the past two weeks and it’s gone about as well as the initial invasion did. Only advancing a few hundred meters. Ukraine says Russia has lost over 400 vehicles and 6,000 soldiers. How’s the expression go? If at first you don’t succeed, try, try again.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7293296117683604782" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-23T23:14:01+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7294704766553296159</id>
    <title>US Strikes Back At Iran #usa #america  The Pentagon says the US military conducted airstrikes on two facilities in eastern Syria used by Iran's troops and its proxy groups. With the New York Times reporting that two F-16s dropped 30 precision guided bombs</title>
    <updated>2023-10-27T18:20:17+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Strikes Back At Iran #usa #america  The Pentagon says the US military conducted airstrikes on two facilities in eastern Syria used by Iran's troops and its proxy groups. With the New York Times reporting that two F-16s dropped 30 precision guided bombs on a weapons storage facility and an ammunition storage facility. AP reports that Iranian troops were present at the facilities during the strikes but a causality assessment hasn’t been done yet. These strikes are in response to at least 19 attacks on US forces in the past week. The US says it doesn't seek a broader conflict, but Iran must stop attacking US troops. Adding any further attacks including any response to these airstrikes will result in the US engaging in self-defense. But earlier this morning, US soldiers shot down a one-way attack drone heading for their base in Iraq according to Fox News. Making that the 20th attack on US forces, and a clear violation of the red line that was laid out by the White House like not even an hour earlier.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7294704766553296159" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-27T18:20:17+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7294737926674582815</id>
    <title>Chinese Jet Almost Hit B-52 Bomber #usa #america  A Chinese fighter jet came within 10 feet of a US B-52 bomber over the South China Sea earlier this week, that’s what you’re seeing on screen right now. The US says the Chinese pilot was “flying at an unco</title>
    <updated>2023-10-27T20:28:55+00:00</updated>
    <content>Chinese Jet Almost Hit B-52 Bomber #usa #america  A Chinese fighter jet came within 10 feet of a US B-52 bomber over the South China Sea earlier this week, that’s what you’re seeing on screen right now. The US says the Chinese pilot was “flying at an uncontrolled excessive speed, flying below, in front of, and within 10 feet of the B-52, putting both aircraft in danger of collision.” In response to this, China released a video showing a US warship doing what they call “close-in harassment” on August 19th, which is what you’re watching right now. China says the US is the real provoker, risk-taker and disrupter. But the US says that China has engaged in risky and aggressive behavior in the skies over 180 times since Fall of 2021. Good lord, which one of them is gonna yell “mom” first?</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7294737926674582815" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-27T20:28:55+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
