<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-07-30T19:13:12+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7260241792690392366</id>
    <title>Large Red Square Hovered Over Air Force Base #usa #america  A US Navy pilot testified in front of Congress today that in 2003 a large red square hovered over an Air Force Base which hovered for approximately 45 seconds before disappearing. The red square </title>
    <updated>2023-07-26T21:26:18+00:00</updated>
    <content>Large Red Square Hovered Over Air Force Base #usa #america  A US Navy pilot testified in front of Congress today that in 2003 a large red square hovered over an Air Force Base which hovered for approximately 45 seconds before disappearing. The red square was supposedly the size of a football field. He said that UFOs are commonly a black square or a black cube inside of a clear sphere. He also said that he’s talked to two navy pilots who nearly hit a dark gray black cube inside of a clear sphere with no wings</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7260241792690392366" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-26T21:26:18+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7260588859367394602</id>
    <title>Russia Attacks 6th US Drone #usa #russia  For the 6th time this month and the 2nd time in 24 hours, a Russian jet has attacked a U.S. drone. The Russian jet fired flares at the drone which struck the main body of the drone, severely damaging it. Russia cl</title>
    <updated>2023-07-27T19:53:07+00:00</updated>
    <content>Russia Attacks 6th US Drone #usa #russia  For the 6th time this month and the 2nd time in 24 hours, a Russian jet has attacked a U.S. drone. The Russian jet fired flares at the drone which struck the main body of the drone, severely damaging it. Russia claims the drone was being highly provocative. And the US statement is the same as last time which is essentially “Russia needs to grow up”. Commanders reportedly exchanged angry threats over the deconfliction hotline afterwards. The U.S. has now deployed even more F-35s to the region as their patience begins to run thin.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7260588859367394602" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-27T19:53:07+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7260956878946143534</id>
    <title>NATO To Escort Ukrainian Ships?! #usa #ukraine  A US Admiral and former Supreme Allied commander of NATO has suggested the US Navy and NATO escort Ukraine’s ships exporting grain in the Black Sea. He says they would bundle merchant ships into three-to-fiv</title>
    <updated>2023-07-28T19:41:17+00:00</updated>
    <content>NATO To Escort Ukrainian Ships?! #usa #ukraine  A US Admiral and former Supreme Allied commander of NATO has suggested the US Navy and NATO escort Ukraine’s ships exporting grain in the Black Sea. He says they would bundle merchant ships into three-to-five ship convoys, each escorted by a couple of guided-missile warships. He cites how the US Navy did the same thing in the Persian Gulf when Iran was sinking Kuwait’s oil vessels. The justification for this action would be that blockades are illegal and that there is no declared state of war between Ukraine and Russia. It may have worked against Iran, but the serious flaw in this plan is that your average Russian sailor is silly and that Biden is too risk averse for such a plan.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7260956878946143534" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-28T19:41:17+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7261677878058749226</id>
    <title>China Hacked US Power Grid #usa #america  China has planted malware inside of networks controlling power grids, communications systems and water supplies that feed US military bases all around the world. And now the U.S. is hunting for it in a panic under</title>
    <updated>2023-07-30T18:19:09+00:00</updated>
    <content>China Hacked US Power Grid #usa #america  China has planted malware inside of networks controlling power grids, communications systems and water supplies that feed US military bases all around the world. And now the U.S. is hunting for it in a panic under the belief that China could activate the code to disrupt the U.S. military in the event of conflict or when China makes a move on Taiwan. One official called it a “ticking time bomb”. If China were to use the malware, it wouldn’t just affect the bases - it would also affect regular Americans as domestic US bases use the same infrastructure.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7261677878058749226" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-30T18:19:09+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7261691797804502314</id>
    <title>Ukraine Using North Korean Rockets To Hit Russia #ukraine #korea  Ukraine is using North Korean rockets to hit Russia. They say that a friendly nation seized them from a Russian ship and gave them to Ukraine. The friendly nation is suspected to either be </title>
    <updated>2023-07-30T19:13:12+00:00</updated>
    <content>Ukraine Using North Korean Rockets To Hit Russia #ukraine #korea  Ukraine is using North Korean rockets to hit Russia. They say that a friendly nation seized them from a Russian ship and gave them to Ukraine. The friendly nation is suspected to either be the United States or South Korea. However, Ukrainians don’t like using the rockets because they have a high dud rate because they’re North Korean and nearly 40 years old. But ammo is ammo.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7261691797804502314" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-30T19:13:12+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
