<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-09-30T15:30:13+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7283211994537184555</id>
    <title>US Deploys F-16s To Enforce No-Fly Zone #usa #ukraine  The US has deployed F-16s to Romania to enforce the new no fly zone. The No-Fly Zone extends 30 kilometers from Romania’s eastern border and will allow them to shoot down any missiles or drones approa</title>
    <updated>2023-09-26T19:02:33+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Deploys F-16s To Enforce No-Fly Zone #usa #ukraine  The US has deployed F-16s to Romania to enforce the new no fly zone. The No-Fly Zone extends 30 kilometers from Romania’s eastern border and will allow them to shoot down any missiles or drones approaching their borders. This comes after Russia kept hitting Romania when they were attacking Ukraine.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7283211994537184555" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-26T19:02:33+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7283235540193856811</id>
    <title>Canadian Pilot Changes Call Sign To What?! #canada #uk  Yesterday a Canadian fighter jet changed its call sign to “D**K69” while it was flying over the UK. Canada says it’s investigating the name change, adding that it was inappropriate and unapproved. Ca</title>
    <updated>2023-09-26T20:33:53+00:00</updated>
    <content>Canadian Pilot Changes Call Sign To What?! #canada #uk  Yesterday a Canadian fighter jet changed its call sign to “D**K69” while it was flying over the UK. Canada says it’s investigating the name change, adding that it was inappropriate and unapproved. Call signs contain four letters and two numbers. They are assigned to pilots and usually remain unchanged. And this Canadian pilot changed their call sign from BLDE11 to D**K69. They could be facing a stiff punishment.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7283235540193856811" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-26T20:33:53+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7283603550100294954</id>
    <title>Gamer Leaks Classified Document To Win War Thunder Argument #usa #warthunder  For the third time this month, gamers have leaked restricted military documents on the war thunder forums. This time it’s the manual to the Apache helicopter which was supposed </title>
    <updated>2023-09-27T20:21:53+00:00</updated>
    <content>Gamer Leaks Classified Document To Win War Thunder Argument #usa #warthunder  For the third time this month, gamers have leaked restricted military documents on the war thunder forums. This time it’s the manual to the Apache helicopter which was supposed to be for the DoD only. Earlier this month, a user leaked part of the manual to the F-117 Nighthawk’s flight manual. War Thunder’s dedication to realism is its Achilles heal as players often resort to leaking classified documents in order to settle online arguments… which has happened at least 13 times.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7283603550100294954" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-27T20:21:53+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7284352786714856750</id>
    <title>China Takes Pandas Away From US, UK, And Australia #usa #uk #australia  China is taking back all of their pandas. Next year the US, UK, and Australia will lose all of their pandas. The Netherlands and Japan both had their pandas taken this year as well. W</title>
    <updated>2023-09-29T20:49:27+00:00</updated>
    <content>China Takes Pandas Away From US, UK, And Australia #usa #uk #australia  China is taking back all of their pandas. Next year the US, UK, and Australia will lose all of their pandas. The Netherlands and Japan both had their pandas taken this year as well. With China experts saying the reason they’re being like this about this is because it’s China’s way of saying that they don’t like how they’re being treated. And China says that only friendly nations to China can host Pandas which is why Russia gets to keep their pandas. Pandas have played a vital role in the US-China relationship with the Chinese ambassador saying 10 years ago - “there are two Chinese ambassadors to Washington, me and the Panda at the National Zoo”. The US says it holds out hope that the “charismatic megafauna” may one day return.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7284352786714856750" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-29T20:49:27+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7284641615698808106</id>
    <title>Serbia Prepares Invasion of Kosovo &amp; NATO #usa #europe  Serbia could attack NATO and Kosovo soon. The US just delivered an unusually specific warning about a potential Serbian military action into Kosovo. Saying they’re monitoring a larger Serbian deploym</title>
    <updated>2023-09-30T15:30:13+00:00</updated>
    <content>Serbia Prepares Invasion of Kosovo &amp; NATO #usa #europe  Serbia could attack NATO and Kosovo soon. The US just delivered an unusually specific warning about a potential Serbian military action into Kosovo. Saying they’re monitoring a larger Serbian deployment on the border of Kosovo including an “unprecedented forward deployment and staging of artillery, tanks, and service members”. The US called on Serbia to withdraw their forces, and said that it’s destabilizing. When asked if Serbia was going to invade Kosovo, the White House said “we’re looking at it but we can’t say right now”. NATO has deployed more forces to Kosovo in light of this, and Britain has placed more troops under NATO command.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7284641615698808106" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-30T15:30:13+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
