<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-09-01T22:47:19+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7273215368611532078</id>
    <title>China Drops New Map Claiming India, Japan, Vietnam, Malaysia, Philippines, Russia, and Bhutan #russia #philippines #japan  China dropped it’s new map and it’s neighbors are upset. China’s new map shows them claiming part of India. India says the map is ab</title>
    <updated>2023-08-30T20:30:30+00:00</updated>
    <content>China Drops New Map Claiming India, Japan, Vietnam, Malaysia, Philippines, Russia, and Bhutan #russia #philippines #japan  China dropped it’s new map and it’s neighbors are upset. China’s new map shows them claiming part of India. India says the map is absurd and that their claims have no basis. The map also shows them infringing on Malaysia’s maritime border so Malaysia has rejected their unilateral claims. China’s map also claims part of Russia, Japan, Vietnam, Bhutan, Indonesia, Philippines, and all of Taiwan. It may seem silly for these countries to get very upset over what are essentially just lines on a piece of paper. But lines on a map represent people’s identities, their validation, things they’ve fought thousands of years for. It’s never just a line on a piece of paper.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7273215368611532078" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-30T20:30:30+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7273264915857771822</id>
    <title>Russia Says It Has A Right To 1v1 Each &amp; Every NATO Country #russia #usa  Russia says it has a right to war with each and every NATO country. Saying “whether you like it or not, history is on our side and we will bury you”. Russia has lost half of it’s mi</title>
    <updated>2023-08-30T23:42:44+00:00</updated>
    <content>Russia Says It Has A Right To 1v1 Each &amp; Every NATO Country #russia #usa  Russia says it has a right to war with each and every NATO country. Saying “whether you like it or not, history is on our side and we will bury you”. Russia has lost half of it’s military hardware and half a million soldiers and NATO hasn’t even shown up yet. So I say fine. If Russia wants to fight each NATO country individually, then I volunteer Hungary to go first and then Poland gets to go second.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7273264915857771822" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-30T23:42:44+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7273576922783681835</id>
    <title>Police Pull Over Giant Bull Named Howdy Dooty Sitting In Car #usa #america  A car with a giant bull sitting in the passenger seat named Howdy Doody was pulled over by police in Nebraska. The man and Howdy Doody were pulled over after a snitch called the p</title>
    <updated>2023-08-31T19:53:30+00:00</updated>
    <content>Police Pull Over Giant Bull Named Howdy Dooty Sitting In Car #usa #america  A car with a giant bull sitting in the passenger seat named Howdy Doody was pulled over by police in Nebraska. The man and Howdy Doody were pulled over after a snitch called the police about the sight. The police didn’t give him a ticket though, they just gave him some warnings and asked him and Howdy to leave the city. Turns out that Howdy Doody is actually a bit of a celebrity and performs at a lot of parades and fairs in the area.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7273576922783681835" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-31T19:53:30+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7273600574636215598</id>
    <title>Russia Demands Norway Pay Them $4.4 Million Because Of Reindeer Damage #norway #russia  Russia is demanding that Norway pay them 4.4 million dollars because 42 reindeer crossed the border into Russia. They say the money is for compensation for the reindee</title>
    <updated>2023-08-31T21:25:20+00:00</updated>
    <content>Russia Demands Norway Pay Them $4.4 Million Because Of Reindeer Damage #norway #russia  Russia is demanding that Norway pay them 4.4 million dollars because 42 reindeer crossed the border into Russia. They say the money is for compensation for the reindeer eating Russian grass. That’s some expensive grass. Supposedly a gate that separated the two countries and kept Reindeer out of Russia broke. So now 40 of the 42 reindeer have been killed in fears that they’ll cross into Russia again. Norway has asked its citizens to keep their reindeer in check. Look, Santa won’t be stopping in Russia this year with these kinds of rules in place.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7273600574636215598" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-31T21:25:20+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7273992810217442603</id>
    <title>Saudi Arabia Kills Man For Tweets #saudiarabia #saudi  Saudi Arabia has sentenced a man to death for criticizing the Saudi Royal Family on Twitter. The charges against him are “betraying his religion,” “disturbing the security of society,” “conspiring aga</title>
    <updated>2023-09-01T22:47:19+00:00</updated>
    <content>Saudi Arabia Kills Man For Tweets #saudiarabia #saudi  Saudi Arabia has sentenced a man to death for criticizing the Saudi Royal Family on Twitter. The charges against him are “betraying his religion,” “disturbing the security of society,” “conspiring against the government” and “impugning the kingdom and the crown prince”. The man had just 10 followers so he was tweeting to essentially no one. Killing people for tweets is just yet another human rights violation from the champions of crimes against humanity Saudi Arabia also funded 9/11, genocided Yemenis, aided ISIS, and killed Jamal Khashoggi.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7273992810217442603" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-01T22:47:19+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
