<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-09-21T23:35:06+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7281006265705172267</id>
    <title>Biden Met With The Stans #usa #swiftie  Biden met with the stans yesterday, and I’m not talking about the Barbs or the Swifties. Nope, I’m talking about Kazakhstan, Kyrgyzstan, Tajikistan, Turkmenistan, and Uzbekistan. This is the first C5+1 summit in Pre</title>
    <updated>2023-09-20T20:23:02+00:00</updated>
    <content>Biden Met With The Stans #usa #swiftie  Biden met with the stans yesterday, and I’m not talking about the Barbs or the Swifties. Nope, I’m talking about Kazakhstan, Kyrgyzstan, Tajikistan, Turkmenistan, and Uzbekistan. This is the first C5+1 summit in Presidential history. They discussed stronger regional security, connectivity, climate action, and governance. Central Asia asked Washington to not forget about them when they left Afghanistan, and sure enough they didn’t.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7281006265705172267" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-20T20:23:02+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7281038330848922922</id>
    <title>Pakistan Stands Up For Canada Amid Diplomatic Battle With India #canada #india #pakistan  India is warning its citizens traveling to Canada or living in Canada to exercise the utmost caution. They issued this warning in light of what they call “anti-India</title>
    <updated>2023-09-20T22:27:27+00:00</updated>
    <content>Pakistan Stands Up For Canada Amid Diplomatic Battle With India #canada #india #pakistan  India is warning its citizens traveling to Canada or living in Canada to exercise the utmost caution. They issued this warning in light of what they call “anti-India activities and politically-condoned hate crimes and criminal violence in Canada”. Adding that any Indians who oppose the “anti-India agenda” in Canada face threats. India, who murdered a Canadian citizen, continues to play the victim. The investigation that caught India was initially thought to be headed by the CIA and Canada, but a western intelligence official dropped a not-so-subtle hint that all of 5 eyes has been investigating the murder. Pakistan has something to say about all of this though, saying “India's terrorism in Canada is not a matter of surprise” Adding “If anyone in the world is aware of Indian terrorism, it is us” Yesterday they said India was a “terrorist and rogue state”, and asked "how long will our friends in the West continue to ignore such acts from India?”</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7281038330848922922" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-20T22:27:27+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7281367017364606254</id>
    <title>Saudi Arabia To Built A Nuke If Iran Gets One #usa #saudiarabia  Saudi Arabia said in no uncertain terms that if Iran gets a nuclear weapon then they have to get one too. The U.S.’ biggest fear regarding a nuclear Iran has less to do with Iran having a nu</title>
    <updated>2023-09-21T19:42:58+00:00</updated>
    <content>Saudi Arabia To Built A Nuke If Iran Gets One #usa #saudiarabia  Saudi Arabia said in no uncertain terms that if Iran gets a nuclear weapon then they have to get one too. The U.S.’ biggest fear regarding a nuclear Iran has less to do with Iran having a nuke but the proliferation it’ll bring to the region. As Saudi Arabia is clearly stating here they’ll build nukes, one should expect Turkey to also build nukes if Saudi gets them. A nuclear arms race in the Middle East gives the U.S. all the more reason to strike a deal with Iran.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7281367017364606254" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-21T19:42:58+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7281410415370964270</id>
    <title>India Says Quebec Should Be Free #canada #india  India says it should have a referendum on Quebec’s independence from Canada. Also saying that Canada’s reputation is now being a “safe haven for terror”. This comes as India has suspended visa services for </title>
    <updated>2023-09-21T22:31:22+00:00</updated>
    <content>India Says Quebec Should Be Free #canada #india  India says it should have a referendum on Quebec’s independence from Canada. Also saying that Canada’s reputation is now being a “safe haven for terror”. This comes as India has suspended visa services for Canadians and has demanded that Canada reduce the amount of staff in it’s embassy in India. Saying that Canada has interfered in their domestic affairs… which actually kind of seems like admission of guilt. India continues to deny the accusation but Canada has rejected India’s denial and is urging India to cooperate in the investigation.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7281410415370964270" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-21T22:31:22+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7281426848012061994</id>
    <title>America abandons Canada #usa #canada  American has abandoned Canada. India has reportedly reached out to the US to offer to cooperate with Canada if they release the evidence publicly. It’s unclear why India didn’t just tell Canada this directly but it’s </title>
    <updated>2023-09-21T23:35:06+00:00</updated>
    <content>America abandons Canada #usa #canada  American has abandoned Canada. India has reportedly reached out to the US to offer to cooperate with Canada if they release the evidence publicly. It’s unclear why India didn’t just tell Canada this directly but it’s possible that the Indian government is just lying and is assuming the US won’t involve itself. India is having a full scale meltdown and is throwing gasoline on this fire, making themselves look more guilty in the process as Canada continues to wonder why the US and UK, who helped indict India, are staying silent. As one Canadian in our comments put it “America loves this kind of thing. They love to stick up for the little guy &amp; raise hell but not when it comes to us I guess. Maybe China would be a more dependable ally.”</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7281426848012061994" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-21T23:35:06+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
