<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-10-25T20:06:16+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7291398010318163246</id>
    <title>Hospital In Gaza Hit By Rogue Missile #usa #israel  Yesterday a hospital in Gaza was hit by a rogue missile. Visual evidence from Palestinians, an independent assessment from the Pentagon, and overwhelming evidence released by the IDF suggest this was a P</title>
    <updated>2023-10-18T20:28:19+00:00</updated>
    <content>Hospital In Gaza Hit By Rogue Missile #usa #israel  Yesterday a hospital in Gaza was hit by a rogue missile. Visual evidence from Palestinians, an independent assessment from the Pentagon, and overwhelming evidence released by the IDF suggest this was a PIJ rocket that misfired. The US has also collected “high confidence” signals intelligence that this was caused by the PIJ. President Biden also went as far to say that the Department of Defense concluded that it wasn’t Israel based on their own intelligence. The IDF also released an alleged audio recording between two Hamas members discussing the rocket that misfired. Contrary to initial claims, the hospital wasn't completely destroyed. It's still standing and footage from the ground shows that the worst damage was done in the parking lot. The crater in the ground is consistent with militant missiles, not Israeli JDAMs according to most experts. Hamas claims that nearly 500 were killed. But due to the seeming lack of major damage to any of the nearby buildings or independent verification of those numbers, people are starting to doubt that figure. The facts of what actually happened differ from what mainstream media and several other news creators initially reported yesterday because they ran with Hamas’ narrative. With Al-Jazeera, BBC, MSNBC among several others all saying with certainty that Israel had done this. This misinformation resulted in widespread riots and protests outside of US embassies across the Middle East. As well as regional-wide condemnation of Israel, calls to war by Hezbollah and Iran, and drones launched at US bases in Iraq. Today should serve as a day of reflection for the media and news influencers since they almost started a region-wide war yesterday. Taking a second to make sure what you have is correct is more important than being first because someone’s going to get there before you do anyways.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7291398010318163246" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-18T20:28:19+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7291784553260125486</id>
    <title>US Forces Under Assault Across Middle East #usa #israel  The United States has issued a very rare worldwide caution travel alert due to the risk of terror attacks, protests, and violent actions against Americans. Reuters reports that US officials say that</title>
    <updated>2023-10-19T21:28:26+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Forces Under Assault Across Middle East #usa #israel  The United States has issued a very rare worldwide caution travel alert due to the risk of terror attacks, protests, and violent actions against Americans. Reuters reports that US officials say that a Hezebollah linked terror group used drones to attack a US Military base in Syria today causing minor injuries. Meanwhile the Pentagon says a US Navy warship operating in the Northern Red Sea today intercepted 3 cruise missiles and several drones that were fired from the Houthi militant group in Yemen. The Pentagon says the missiles were potentially headed towards Israel which is why they intercepted them, but that they can’t currently confirm that Israel was the target. Channel 13 in Israel is reporting that Israel believes that the missiles were launched at them. And just now Reuters is reporting that two security sources tell them that yet another US base in Iraq has been hit with drones and missiles, this is reportedly the 5th attack on US forces in Iraq and Syria in the past 36 hours. The US has also ordered Americans to leave Lebanon as soon as possible and has changed its travel advisory to “Do Not Travel”.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7291784553260125486" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-19T21:28:26+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7293279484566850862</id>
    <title>US Fears Region-Wide War #usa #israel  The US fears a widening region-wide war, US officials tell Axios. With the Pentagon now putting even more troops on “prepare to deploy orders” This comes as the US has sent two aircraft carriers to the region, surged</title>
    <updated>2023-10-23T22:09:25+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Fears Region-Wide War #usa #israel  The US fears a widening region-wide war, US officials tell Axios. With the Pentagon now putting even more troops on “prepare to deploy orders” This comes as the US has sent two aircraft carriers to the region, surged aircraft to its bases in the Middle East, and added more air defense systems and all weekend, US bases all over the region were attacked by terror groups. The rhetoric coming out of Israel and Iran has been white hot, with the BBC reporting that Iran warned Israel that if they don’t stop striking Gaza - the region will spiral out of control. Israel and Hezbollah are continuing to exchange fire with each other on the northern border. With the New York Times reporting that the United States has told Israel to not conduct a preemptive strike on Hezbollah. With the outlet also saying the US believes that Israel would struggle in a two front war, and that such a war would drag both them and Iran into it.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7293279484566850862" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-23T22:09:25+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7293296117683604782</id>
    <title>US Moves Carrier Closer To Iran #usa #israel  The USS Eisenhower, the 2nd aircraft carrier the US sent to Israel, will now move to the Persian Gulf according to the Pentagon. This puts the US closer to its bases in the region and closer to Iran. The Guard</title>
    <updated>2023-10-23T23:14:01+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Moves Carrier Closer To Iran #usa #israel  The USS Eisenhower, the 2nd aircraft carrier the US sent to Israel, will now move to the Persian Gulf according to the Pentagon. This puts the US closer to its bases in the region and closer to Iran. The Guardian is reporting that ISIS and Al-Qaeda are calling on their followers to attack Israel and the US. In other parts of the world: The Philippines has accused China of intentionally colliding with their ships on a resupply mission. The US has sided with the Philippines and once again reaffirmed their mutual defense treaty. In an exclusive, Rolling Stone is reporting that Trump is planning on pulling the United States out of NATO if he wins the Presidency again. Russia began an offensive in the past two weeks and it’s gone about as well as the initial invasion did. Only advancing a few hundred meters. Ukraine says Russia has lost over 400 vehicles and 6,000 soldiers. How’s the expression go? If at first you don’t succeed, try, try again.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7293296117683604782" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-23T23:14:01+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7293989871083998507</id>
    <title>Iran Attacks United States, Teetering On War #usa #america  The U.S. &amp; Iran are on the verge of war. Since October 17th, the Pentagon says there have been at least 15 drone and rocket attacks on US forces by Iranian proxies. With US officials telling NBC </title>
    <updated>2023-10-25T20:06:16+00:00</updated>
    <content>Iran Attacks United States, Teetering On War #usa #america  The U.S. &amp; Iran are on the verge of war. Since October 17th, the Pentagon says there have been at least 15 drone and rocket attacks on US forces by Iranian proxies. With US officials telling NBC News that more than two dozen U.S. soldiers were wounded in these attacks. Several of these soldiers have reported symptoms of traumatic brain injuries. Today President Biden said “My warning to the Ayatollah was that if they continued to move against our troops we will respond and he should be prepared.” The Marine Corps top general issued a warning yesterday saying “For those that are in the area, if that Marine Expeditionary Unit has to go in, if you target them, someone else will raise your children.” Yesterday the US delivered a stark warning at the UN to Iran and now The White House says they’re sending even MORE forces to the Middle East. US officials say they have intelligence that Iran is encouraging its terror groups to ramp up attacks on the United States according to Reuters. With one U.S. official saying “there are red lights flashing everywhere.”</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7293989871083998507" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-25T20:06:16+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
