<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-07-26T00:21:34+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7259474763851042091</id>
    <title>UN Trying To Save US Soldier From North Korea #usa #korea  The UN has begun talks with North Korea about Travis King, the U.S. soldier who ran into North Korea. King hasn’t been seen since he ran across the border and was shoved into a van and driven off </title>
    <updated>2023-07-24T19:49:54+00:00</updated>
    <content>UN Trying To Save US Soldier From North Korea #usa #korea  The UN has begun talks with North Korea about Travis King, the U.S. soldier who ran into North Korea. King hasn’t been seen since he ran across the border and was shoved into a van and driven off by North Korean soldiers. The US says they’re not ruling out that he contacted North Korea beforehand but currently they don’t believe he was in prior contact. New reports suggest that there was a 13 hour gap between when he escaped the airport and when he crossed into the North. North Korea has so far refused to talk to the U.S. about the issue.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7259474763851042091" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-24T19:49:54+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7259497585491184938</id>
    <title>China Is Now Supplying Russia In Ukraine #ukraine #russia  China is supplying Russia with enough gear to equip the entire Russian army. China has been supplying Russia with dual use equipment - so things that are civilian but could be used for military pu</title>
    <updated>2023-07-24T21:18:27+00:00</updated>
    <content>China Is Now Supplying Russia In Ukraine #ukraine #russia  China is supplying Russia with enough gear to equip the entire Russian army. China has been supplying Russia with dual use equipment - so things that are civilian but could be used for military purposes. So for example: Russia has imported over 100 million dollars worth of drones from China this year as well as 225 million dollars of Ceramic. This goes right up to the West’s red line.. with both France and the U.S. telling China earlier this month that they rely on the west and that they won’t hesitate to cut them off. While it’s clear that China is not a neutral actor unless they cross the red line of supplying munitions and equipment,. They’re unlikely to face sanctions</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7259497585491184938" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-24T21:18:27+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7259767425774816558</id>
    <title>Russia Attacked US Drone #usa #russia  Russia just attacked a U.S. drone. When a U.S. drone was returning home after it completed its mission of defeating, a Russian jet flew within meters of it and deployed flares on it which hit its propeller, severely </title>
    <updated>2023-07-25T14:45:35+00:00</updated>
    <content>Russia Attacked US Drone #usa #russia  Russia just attacked a U.S. drone. When a U.S. drone was returning home after it completed its mission of defeating, a Russian jet flew within meters of it and deployed flares on it which hit its propeller, severely damaging it. The U.S. says this was an attempt to knock the US drone out of the sky. With the U.S. saying “We call upon the Russian forces in Syria to put an immediate end to this reckless, unprovoked, and unprofessional behavior.” Apparently both sides used the deconfliction hotline but reportedly the line has been very heated lately and just been a place for the two of them to verbally argue instead of deconflict.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7259767425774816558" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-25T14:45:35+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7259866793546714410</id>
    <title>Russia Bombs NATO Ship #russia #ukraine  Russia just hit a NATO ship while it was bombing a Ukrainian port. The civilian ship belonged to Romania and it was struck in the Ukrainian port of Reni. The ship was able to complete its voyage despite minor damag</title>
    <updated>2023-07-25T21:11:11+00:00</updated>
    <content>Russia Bombs NATO Ship #russia #ukraine  Russia just hit a NATO ship while it was bombing a Ukrainian port. The civilian ship belonged to Romania and it was struck in the Ukrainian port of Reni. The ship was able to complete its voyage despite minor damage. No Romanian citizens were injured. If Russia continues to bomb Ukrainian ports, they will only raise the risk of NATO involvement.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7259866793546714410" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-25T21:11:11+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7259915875946450219</id>
    <title>Russian Brain Drain Boosts Neighboring Economies Big Time #russia #ukraine </title>
    <updated>2023-07-26T00:21:34+00:00</updated>
    <content>Russian Brain Drain Boosts Neighboring Economies Big Time #russia #ukraine </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7259915875946450219" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-26T00:21:34+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
