<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-08-10T21:45:52+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7265409212384021806</id>
    <title>Russia Won’t Have A Presidential Election #russia #usa  Russia says they may not hold Presidential elections next year because Putin will obviously win re-election. Putin is expected to announce his run for a 6th presidential term, especially since he cha</title>
    <updated>2023-08-09T19:38:37+00:00</updated>
    <content>Russia Won’t Have A Presidential Election #russia #usa  Russia says they may not hold Presidential elections next year because Putin will obviously win re-election. Putin is expected to announce his run for a 6th presidential term, especially since he changed the constitution to let him be President until 2036. All of this, of course, doesn’t matter though because they don’t have free and fair elections. But it does raise an interesting question - we know the elections are rigged, so why not just have another fake election? Maybe he thinks that the few real votes will reveal just how weak support for him has gotten.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7265409212384021806" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-09T19:38:37+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7265459095942024490</id>
    <title>US &amp; Saudi Near Deal To Normalize Relations With Israel #usa #saudiarabia #israel  The U.S. and Saudi Arabia reportedly have a working plan in place to normalize relations with Israel! The deal would see the US help Saudi develop a civilian nuclear progra</title>
    <updated>2023-08-09T22:52:13+00:00</updated>
    <content>US &amp; Saudi Near Deal To Normalize Relations With Israel #usa #saudiarabia #israel  The U.S. and Saudi Arabia reportedly have a working plan in place to normalize relations with Israel! The deal would see the US help Saudi develop a civilian nuclear program and give them iron-clad security guarantees similar to that of NATO Article 5. It would also see the creation of a Palestinian state. Now in return, Saudi would distance itself from China economically and militarily. Saudi will price oil sales to China in dollas, it’ll also drop Chinese tech, and not allow China to build a base in the country. And lastly, they’ll stop messing with oil prices. But there are some obstacles though. For one, Israel fears that a nuclear program would allow Saudi to develop nukes if Iran does and it also wants a larger US security guarantee that is also similar to NATO’s Article 5. Israel will also have to agree to help forward the Palestinian quest for statehood. And the last obstacle for this deal is at home. Such a deal would require Senate approval and Saudi is toxic. They funded 9/11, they killed a US journalist, they mess with gas prices to swing our elections and they’re ruining golf. The Senate already won’t sell more weapons to Saudi, so to get them to agree to a security guarantee like an Article 5 seems far-fetched. But the Biden Admin is hoping that the history shifting deal will be enough for lawmakers to drop opposition if and when that day comes.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7265459095942024490" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-09T22:52:13+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7265727828107300138</id>
    <title>US Asks Citizens To Shelter In Place In Niger #usa #niger  The U.S. has issued an urgent security alert telling all American citizens in Niger to shelter in place. Niger armed forces are on high alert in order to defend against attacks by the French milit</title>
    <updated>2023-08-10T16:15:08+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Asks Citizens To Shelter In Place In Niger #usa #niger  The U.S. has issued an urgent security alert telling all American citizens in Niger to shelter in place. Niger armed forces are on high alert in order to defend against attacks by the French military. The Junta is accusing France of having violated their airspace and of having released terrorists to the region. But France released the receipts showing that the Junta said they could fly over the country and released the agreement that was signed by the head of the Junta himself. As for the terrorist accusations, there is currently no evidence of such a thing happening. Niger’s ousted political party has called for a nationwide mobilization and is calling on the citizens to save the President and his family. And here’s an interesting side plot to all of this: an Al-Qaeda Affiliate killed two Wagner spies on the border of Niger.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7265727828107300138" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-10T16:15:08+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7265762813769993515</id>
    <title>World War Africa Has Begun #usa #nigeria  World War: Africa has begun. ECOWAS has activated its standby forces to restore democracy and constitutional order in the Republic of Niger. They maintain that all options remain on the table. Earlier today, Niger</title>
    <updated>2023-08-10T18:30:48+00:00</updated>
    <content>World War Africa Has Begun #usa #nigeria  World War: Africa has begun. ECOWAS has activated its standby forces to restore democracy and constitutional order in the Republic of Niger. They maintain that all options remain on the table. Earlier today, Niger told the US that if their neighboring nations intervene they will kill the ousted President that they’re holding hostage. This seems to be what pushed ECOWAS to intervention. Mali and Burkina Faso have said that they will go to war on the side of Niger. In a statement today, the US said it supports “African solutions to African problems”</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7265762813769993515" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-10T18:30:48+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7265813081597725998</id>
    <title>Military Intervention Into Niger To Happen ASAP #usa #nigeria  ECOWAS says military intervention in Niger will happen as soon as possible. With the President of the Ivory Coast saying “The junta in Niger are keeping the President as a hostage. I personall</title>
    <updated>2023-08-10T21:45:52+00:00</updated>
    <content>Military Intervention Into Niger To Happen ASAP #usa #nigeria  ECOWAS says military intervention in Niger will happen as soon as possible. With the President of the Ivory Coast saying “The junta in Niger are keeping the President as a hostage. I personally consider this as a terrorist act. And we cannot let this continue. We have to act”. It’s suspected now that France will in some type of way assist ECOWAS after the Junta said they would kill the President. #france </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7265813081597725998" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-10T21:45:52+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
