<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-08-15T21:26:27+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7265813081597725998</id>
    <title>Military Intervention Into Niger To Happen ASAP #usa #nigeria  ECOWAS says military intervention in Niger will happen as soon as possible. With the President of the Ivory Coast saying “The junta in Niger are keeping the President as a hostage. I personall</title>
    <updated>2023-08-10T21:45:52+00:00</updated>
    <content>Military Intervention Into Niger To Happen ASAP #usa #nigeria  ECOWAS says military intervention in Niger will happen as soon as possible. With the President of the Ivory Coast saying “The junta in Niger are keeping the President as a hostage. I personally consider this as a terrorist act. And we cannot let this continue. We have to act”. It’s suspected now that France will in some type of way assist ECOWAS after the Junta said they would kill the President. #france </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7265813081597725998" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-10T21:45:52+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7266171843969633579</id>
    <title>US Picks A Side In World War Africa #usa #france #nigeria  The U.S. has picked a side in World War Africa. With it now saying it fully backs ECOWAS’s military intervention into Niger. France has also come out in full support &amp; says it will study their req</title>
    <updated>2023-08-11T20:58:02+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Picks A Side In World War Africa #usa #france #nigeria  The U.S. has picked a side in World War Africa. With it now saying it fully backs ECOWAS’s military intervention into Niger. France has also come out in full support &amp; says it will study their requests for military support. 5,000 combat troops have already been moved to staging areas. Mail and Burkina Faso have been radio silent since the intervention was announced, leading many to believe their bluff to defend Niger has been called. The African Union has fully backed ECOWAS and has called on the international community to save the life of the President. Russia says that intervention would destabilize the region meanwhile their mercenaries are in Niger trying to disrupt diplomatic efforts that would prevent a war. Allegedly 3,000 people are protesting in front of the French military base in the country after the Junta called for people to surround it. The Nigerian military is taking the lead on the invasion. Ivory Coast will send between 850 to 1,100 soldiers into Niger. With the President saying that if the Junta leaves tomorrow there will be no war, adding that whether or not there’s a war is up to them.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7266171843969633579" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-11T20:58:02+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7267280227997437227</id>
    <title>US &amp; France Fighting Over World War Africa #usa #france  The US and France are fighting over World War Africa. France reportedly actively favors and wants to support the military intervention into Niger. While the U.S. actively opposes military interventi</title>
    <updated>2023-08-14T20:39:03+00:00</updated>
    <content>US &amp; France Fighting Over World War Africa #usa #france  The US and France are fighting over World War Africa. France reportedly actively favors and wants to support the military intervention into Niger. While the U.S. actively opposes military intervention and wants to seek diplomatic solutions to the crisis. France believes the US is being “unwise” in their attempts at diplomacy, but the US views the consequences of destabilization as counterproductive to its anti-terror mission. The U.S. currently has a massive drone base in Niger that it uses to combat terrorism across all of Western and Northern Africa.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7267280227997437227" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-14T20:39:03+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7267329367859137838</id>
    <title>North Korea Is Preparing For Offensive War #usa #korea  North Korea says it’s preparing for an offensive war against South Korea. This comes after the defense chief hinted at a preemptive nuclear strike. In response, the US and South Korea will strengthen</title>
    <updated>2023-08-14T23:49:46+00:00</updated>
    <content>North Korea Is Preparing For Offensive War #usa #korea  North Korea says it’s preparing for an offensive war against South Korea. This comes after the defense chief hinted at a preemptive nuclear strike. In response, the US and South Korea will strengthen their defense and surveillance posture. They will also be conducting military exercises later this month. North Korea is expected to make more provocations in response.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7267329367859137838" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-14T23:49:46+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7267663518541876526</id>
    <title>Al-Qaeda Calls For Revenge On Sweden &amp; Denmark #sweden #denmark  Al-Qaeda has called for revenge attacks on Sweden and Denmark. This comes after people in the two countries burned Qurans. With Al-Qaeda saying “Denmark and Sweden are two small, despicable </title>
    <updated>2023-08-15T21:26:27+00:00</updated>
    <content>Al-Qaeda Calls For Revenge On Sweden &amp; Denmark #sweden #denmark  Al-Qaeda has called for revenge attacks on Sweden and Denmark. This comes after people in the two countries burned Qurans. With Al-Qaeda saying “Denmark and Sweden are two small, despicable countries that amount to no more than two small spots on the world map” And then it called upon Muslims to take revenge on them.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7267663518541876526" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-15T21:26:27+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
