<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-10-13T19:13:31+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7288442118136302894</id>
    <title>Iran &amp; Israel Take The War To Twitter #israel #usa  The US may conduct a special forces operation to free Americans in Gaza. Yemen’s Houthi group reportedly said if the US intervenes, they’ll attack them with missiles. Trigger fingers are turning into twi</title>
    <updated>2023-10-10T21:18:09+00:00</updated>
    <content>Iran &amp; Israel Take The War To Twitter #israel #usa  The US may conduct a special forces operation to free Americans in Gaza. Yemen’s Houthi group reportedly said if the US intervenes, they’ll attack them with missiles. Trigger fingers are turning into twitter fingers. With Iran’s supreme leader tweeting that Israel will face a larger force if they keep doing, what he called, the mass murder of Gaza. Israel tweeted back saying “It’s easy to be brave when you’re hiding behind a keyboard. You and your Hamas friends will regret your barbaric actions very soon.” Egypt says it’ll bring aid to Gaza but Israel says it’ll airstrike all Egyptian aid convoys. Despite these warnings, Egypt has reportedly still ordered the aid convoy to go into Gaza.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7288442118136302894" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-10T21:18:09+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7288456984376954154</id>
    <title>US To Send Another Aircraft Carrier To Israel #usa #israel  Israel is now getting hit by Mortars from Syria in addition to rockets from Lebanon, and Israel is responding with counter-battery fire. So far 1,000 Israelis have been killed with another 3,400 </title>
    <updated>2023-10-10T22:15:44+00:00</updated>
    <content>US To Send Another Aircraft Carrier To Israel #usa #israel  Israel is now getting hit by Mortars from Syria in addition to rockets from Lebanon, and Israel is responding with counter-battery fire. So far 1,000 Israelis have been killed with another 3,400 injured and 900 Palestinians have been killed with another 4,500 injured. Israel is preparing a months-long ground campaign in Gaza according to Egypt. With Egypt also saying that Israel has dismissed their efforts to mediate any kind of de-escalation according to the Times of Israel. With the Times saying it’s believed that Israel wants to destroy Hamas before entertaining a ceasefire. The United States may deploy a 2nd aircraft carrier strike group to Israel according to the Wall Street Post. The USS Gerald Ford has arrived off the coast of Israel and will likely begin operations tonight. And this has made Erdogan very mad at Israel and the United States. He angrily asked today:  “Why is the US aircraft carrier coming to Israel? For what? What will they do? Will they hit Gaza with their warplanes and commit a massacre?”. Jake Sullivan responded saying: "Let me be clear: we did not move the carrier for Hamas. We moved the carrier to send a clear message of deterrence to other parties who may seek to widen the war”.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7288456984376954154" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-10T22:15:44+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7288859775377624366</id>
    <title>Putin Blames America For Terrorist Attack On Israel #usa #israel  Zelensky will visit Israel in a show of solidarity according to axios. He was among the first leaders to call Israel to offer his support, he is also one of the only Jewish heads of states </title>
    <updated>2023-10-12T00:19:00+00:00</updated>
    <content>Putin Blames America For Terrorist Attack On Israel #usa #israel  Zelensky will visit Israel in a show of solidarity according to axios. He was among the first leaders to call Israel to offer his support, he is also one of the only Jewish heads of states in the world. This comes as Putin blamed the United States for Saturday’s terrorist attack. Hamas is now denying that it killed civilians in Israel, but their attack on Saturday is now the 2nd deadliest terror attack in the history of the West, superseded only by 9/11. The Wall Street Journal says that the IDF killed at least 1,500 terrorists on Saturday while the terror attack was ongoing. Sweden has now cut aid to Palestine.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7288859775377624366" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-12T00:19:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7289210719046831403</id>
    <title>Israel Strikes Syria In Growing War #usa #israel  Israel struck Syria’s two main airports last night to put them out of service according to Al-Jazeera, which is thought to have been done to stop Iranian assistance. https://x.com/IAFsite/status/1712484101</title>
    <updated>2023-10-12T23:00:36+00:00</updated>
    <content>Israel Strikes Syria In Growing War #usa #israel  Israel struck Syria’s two main airports last night to put them out of service according to Al-Jazeera, which is thought to have been done to stop Iranian assistance. https://x.com/IAFsite/status/1712484101763342772?s=20has also dropped over 6,000 bombs on Gaza since Sunday. The IDF also claims that they have a list of everyone who participated in the terror attack and that the air force will reach every one of them. The UK will send part of the Royal navy to Israel as a show of support and to conduct surveillance flights over israel. The US and Qatar have reached a “quiet understanding” to not give Iran any of the 6 Billion that was unfrozen, according to CBS News. 27 Americans have now been killed in the attacks on Israel, 14 are still missing. Secretary Blinken in Israel today said “This is the equivalent of ten 9/11s” - what he means is population scaling. If what happened in Israel happened in America that would mean 48,000 people dead. France has banned Pro-Palestine protests because they are “likely to generate disturbances to the public order”</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7289210719046831403" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-12T23:00:36+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7289523296746360107</id>
    <title>Israel Gives 24 Hours To Evacuate Gaza #usa #israel  Israel has told the United Nations that they have 24 hours to evacuate Northern Gaza to the south. But The UN says that its impossible to evacuate 1.1 million people in less than 24 hours. And Hamas is </title>
    <updated>2023-10-13T19:13:31+00:00</updated>
    <content>Israel Gives 24 Hours To Evacuate Gaza #usa #israel  Israel has told the United Nations that they have 24 hours to evacuate Northern Gaza to the south. But The UN says that its impossible to evacuate 1.1 million people in less than 24 hours. And Hamas is telling people not to evacuate, saying its propaganda according to Al-Jazeera. Israel is expected to begin its ground invasion of Gaza as soon as this weekend. Iran says that there is a real possibility of more fronts opening against Israel. Human rights Watch has accused Israel of using White Phosphorus while others have accused them of flat out revenge bombing.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7289523296746360107" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-13T19:13:31+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
