<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-07-31T20:17:42+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7260956878946143534</id>
    <title>NATO To Escort Ukrainian Ships?! #usa #ukraine  A US Admiral and former Supreme Allied commander of NATO has suggested the US Navy and NATO escort Ukraine’s ships exporting grain in the Black Sea. He says they would bundle merchant ships into three-to-fiv</title>
    <updated>2023-07-28T19:41:17+00:00</updated>
    <content>NATO To Escort Ukrainian Ships?! #usa #ukraine  A US Admiral and former Supreme Allied commander of NATO has suggested the US Navy and NATO escort Ukraine’s ships exporting grain in the Black Sea. He says they would bundle merchant ships into three-to-five ship convoys, each escorted by a couple of guided-missile warships. He cites how the US Navy did the same thing in the Persian Gulf when Iran was sinking Kuwait’s oil vessels. The justification for this action would be that blockades are illegal and that there is no declared state of war between Ukraine and Russia. It may have worked against Iran, but the serious flaw in this plan is that your average Russian sailor is silly and that Biden is too risk averse for such a plan.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7260956878946143534" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-28T19:41:17+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7261677878058749226</id>
    <title>China Hacked US Power Grid #usa #america  China has planted malware inside of networks controlling power grids, communications systems and water supplies that feed US military bases all around the world. And now the U.S. is hunting for it in a panic under</title>
    <updated>2023-07-30T18:19:09+00:00</updated>
    <content>China Hacked US Power Grid #usa #america  China has planted malware inside of networks controlling power grids, communications systems and water supplies that feed US military bases all around the world. And now the U.S. is hunting for it in a panic under the belief that China could activate the code to disrupt the U.S. military in the event of conflict or when China makes a move on Taiwan. One official called it a “ticking time bomb”. If China were to use the malware, it wouldn’t just affect the bases - it would also affect regular Americans as domestic US bases use the same infrastructure.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7261677878058749226" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-30T18:19:09+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7261691797804502314</id>
    <title>Ukraine Using North Korean Rockets To Hit Russia #ukraine #korea  Ukraine is using North Korean rockets to hit Russia. They say that a friendly nation seized them from a Russian ship and gave them to Ukraine. The friendly nation is suspected to either be </title>
    <updated>2023-07-30T19:13:12+00:00</updated>
    <content>Ukraine Using North Korean Rockets To Hit Russia #ukraine #korea  Ukraine is using North Korean rockets to hit Russia. They say that a friendly nation seized them from a Russian ship and gave them to Ukraine. The friendly nation is suspected to either be the United States or South Korea. However, Ukrainians don’t like using the rockets because they have a high dud rate because they’re North Korean and nearly 40 years old. But ammo is ammo.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7261691797804502314" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-30T19:13:12+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7261995787427826990</id>
    <title>France Puts Niger On Notice #france #niger  Protesters in Niger are attacking the French embassy. France has condemned the violence and pledged to react strongly to any attack on its nationals or interests. Since the coup, France has cut off all aid to th</title>
    <updated>2023-07-31T14:52:56+00:00</updated>
    <content>France Puts Niger On Notice #france #niger  Protesters in Niger are attacking the French embassy. France has condemned the violence and pledged to react strongly to any attack on its nationals or interests. Since the coup, France has cut off all aid to the country until the President is reinstated.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7261995787427826990" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-31T14:52:56+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7262079526224547114</id>
    <title>Is Elon Helping Russia Invade Ukraine? #ukraine #russia  Elon Musk may have just helped Russia’s invasion of Ukraine. Musk has explicitly intervened and refused to let Starlink be activated in occupied territories so Ukraine could conduct drone strikes in</title>
    <updated>2023-07-31T20:17:42+00:00</updated>
    <content>Is Elon Helping Russia Invade Ukraine? #ukraine #russia  Elon Musk may have just helped Russia’s invasion of Ukraine. Musk has explicitly intervened and refused to let Starlink be activated in occupied territories so Ukraine could conduct drone strikes in places like Crimea. Musk was concerned that such strikes would escalate the war and loss of life, even though not allowing such strikes just meant more dead Ukrainians and that ultimately such a decision was not his to make. This led to the US having to pay for specific access and control of certain Starlink systems so that Musk could get over himself and quit intervening in the war. #elonmusk #usa </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7262079526224547114" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-31T20:17:42+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
