<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-07-18T17:19:20+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7254676393949269290</id>
    <title>Turkey Has Agreed to Back Sweden’s NATO Bid #Politics  #NATO   #Sweden  #Turkey</title>
    <updated>2023-07-11T21:29:43+00:00</updated>
    <content>Turkey Has Agreed to Back Sweden’s NATO Bid #Politics  #NATO   #Sweden  #Turkey</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7254676393949269290" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-11T21:29:43+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7254969387713695019</id>
    <title>People in Uruguay are accusing Google of stealing precious water needed amid a devastating drought to cool a planned data center. #Google  #Tech  #Uruguay  #Water</title>
    <updated>2023-07-12T19:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <content>People in Uruguay are accusing Google of stealing precious water needed amid a devastating drought to cool a planned data center. #Google  #Tech  #Uruguay  #Water</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7254969387713695019" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-12T19:00:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7256963948082203946</id>
    <title>US Preparing Military Response To Russia #usa #russia  The U.S. is looking at military responses to Russia. For the last two weeks, the Russian Air Force has been harassing US drones, servicemembers, bases, and aircraft. They’ve done everything from locki</title>
    <updated>2023-07-18T01:26:40+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Preparing Military Response To Russia #usa #russia  The U.S. is looking at military responses to Russia. For the last two weeks, the Russian Air Force has been harassing US drones, servicemembers, bases, and aircraft. They’ve done everything from locking on to aircraft to dumping fuel on them. Earlier in the year, the US deployed F-22s to the region to ward off Russia. A new report says that Iran and Russia are colluding to try to force the U.S. out of Syria. They are now deploying F-35s and F-16s to combat the squeeze from the two countries. An interesting side note is that the last time Russia attacked the US in Syria, they were squad wiped.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7256963948082203946" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-18T01:26:40+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7257171915914169646</id>
    <title>US Soldier Detained By North Korea #usa #korea  An American soldier has entered North Korea by crossing the demilitarized line into the country. Travis King has been identified as the soldier and he is currently in North Korean custody. He reportedly let </title>
    <updated>2023-07-18T14:53:37+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Soldier Detained By North Korea #usa #korea  An American soldier has entered North Korea by crossing the demilitarized line into the country. Travis King has been identified as the soldier and he is currently in North Korean custody. He reportedly let out a loud laugh before running across the border. It’s unclear if it’s a defection. The US and UN are currently working on negotiating his release.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7257171915914169646" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-18T14:53:37+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7257209457208364334</id>
    <title>US Soldier Escaped To North Korea #usa #korea  The US soldier who crossed into North Korea had been in U.S. custody for over a month and was being taken to the airport to be sent back to the U.S. when he escaped and joined a tour group and then ran into N</title>
    <updated>2023-07-18T17:19:20+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Soldier Escaped To North Korea #usa #korea  The US soldier who crossed into North Korea had been in U.S. custody for over a month and was being taken to the airport to be sent back to the U.S. when he escaped and joined a tour group and then ran into North Korea. The US Military says it’s working with North Korea to resolve the incident, they say he crossed the line “willfully and without authorization”.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7257209457208364334" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-18T17:19:20+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
