<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-11-21T00:29:57+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7301818652817444127</id>
    <title>Congress Has Turned Into Fight Club #usa #america  Rep. Tim Burchett accused former Speaker of the House Kevin McCarthy of elbowing him in the kidneys intentionally in retaliation for the Tennessee Republican's vote last month to oust McCarthy, sparking a</title>
    <updated>2023-11-15T22:25:57+00:00</updated>
    <content>Congress Has Turned Into Fight Club #usa #america  Rep. Tim Burchett accused former Speaker of the House Kevin McCarthy of elbowing him in the kidneys intentionally in retaliation for the Tennessee Republican's vote last month to oust McCarthy, sparking a conflict on an already tumultuous day at the Capitol. Burchett was talking to NPR reporter Claudia Grisales on Tuesday morning when he says he “got elbowed in the back and it kind of caught me off guard because it was a clean shot to the kidneys.” “I turned back and there was Kevin,” Burchett told CNN. “I chased after him of course. He’s a, as I stated many times, he’s a bully with $17 million and a security detail. He’s the type of guy that when you’re a kid would throw a rock over the fence and run home and hide behind his mama’s skirt." Burchett and Grisales said McCarthy denied it at the time and he later denied elbowing Burchett to other members of the press. He said there was no bad blood over the vote to remove him from the speakership. “I didn’t even know what he was talking about,” McCarthy told CNN. “I did not run and hit the guy. I did not kidney punch him.” “If I hit someone, they would know about it,” he added, mocking Burchett for claiming he was in pain. In audio released by NPR, Burchett can be heard saying "Why'd you elbow me in the back, Kevin? Hey Kevin, you got any guts?” McCarthy can be heard denying the claim and laughing. “What a jerk. You need security Kevin,” Burchett says. McCarthy conceded he may have bumped into Burchett, but the NPR reporter backed up Burchett’s account. “While talking to [Burchett] after the GOP conference meeting, [McCarthy] walked by with his detail and McCarthy shoved Burchett. Burchett lunged towards me,” Grisales wrote on X, the social media platform formerly known as Twitter. “I thought it was a joke, it was not. And a chase ensued.” Speaking to reporters on Tuesday, Burchett brushed off McCarthy's explanation, saying that it shows "exactly why he doesn't need to be speaker."</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7301818652817444127" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-11-15T22:25:57+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7302192727024799007</id>
    <title>Pandas To Return To America! #usa #china  Pandas are coming back to America! During his visit to California, Xi said that China is ready to continue their cooperation on Panda conservation with America. Saying that he was told that a lot of American child</title>
    <updated>2023-11-16T22:37:28+00:00</updated>
    <content>Pandas To Return To America! #usa #china  Pandas are coming back to America! During his visit to California, Xi said that China is ready to continue their cooperation on Panda conservation with America. Saying that he was told that a lot of American children were sad to see them go. Xi also called Pandas “envoys of friendship between the Chinese and American peoples” Biden also wished Xi’s wife a happy early birthday because they share the same birthday. And Xi reportedly said he was embarrassed because he had forgotten that his wife’s birthday was next week. Which I don’t know why you’d admit that.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7302192727024799007" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-11-16T22:37:28+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7302206535692782879</id>
    <title>US Starts Playing Hardball With Israel #usa #israel  The US and Europe are pushing for a plan that would deploy an international peacekeeping force to the Gaza Strip according to Bloomberg. US and European officials believe that this may push Israel to wr</title>
    <updated>2023-11-16T23:31:06+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Starts Playing Hardball With Israel #usa #israel  The US and Europe are pushing for a plan that would deploy an international peacekeeping force to the Gaza Strip according to Bloomberg. US and European officials believe that this may push Israel to wrap up its war and start considering what will come next. This is yet another sign of growing impatience with Israel. Earlier this week, the Times of Israel reported that the US wants Netanyahu out due to him obstructing US efforts to negotiate an end game for Gaza with their Arab Allies. And yesterday the US let a UN Security Council resolution calling for a humanitarian pause in the Gaza strip pass without vetoing it. Also earlier today, the USS Gerald R Ford pulled away from the coast of Israel. Some analysts say this is the US playing hardball after Israel has “gone off the rails” and ignored their pressure.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7302206535692782879" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-11-16T23:31:06+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7303650973589736734</id>
    <title>Houthis Hijack Israeli Ship #usa #israel  Yemen’s Houthi rebels have seized an Israel-linked cargo ship named Galaxy Leader in what most nations would consider an act of piracy. They seized the ship by rappelling down from a helicopter. They have taken 25</title>
    <updated>2023-11-20T20:56:09+00:00</updated>
    <content>Houthis Hijack Israeli Ship #usa #israel  Yemen’s Houthi rebels have seized an Israel-linked cargo ship named Galaxy Leader in what most nations would consider an act of piracy. They seized the ship by rappelling down from a helicopter. They have taken 25 of its crew members hostage, and say they will treat them in accordance to Islamic values but they haven’t elaborated on what that means. The Houthis say they will continue to attack all ships linked to Israel and say that Israel only understands the language of force. The ship is operated by Japan who condemned the hijacking. Israel insists that the ship is British owned but public data says it’s associated with one of the richest men in Israel according to AP.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7303650973589736734" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-11-20T20:56:09+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7303706080247434526</id>
    <title>US Prepares To Sanction Israel #usa #israel  The US is preparing to sanction Israel. President Biden wrote in an Op-Ed that the US is preparing to issue visa bans against extremist settlers in the West Bank who are attacking and displacing Palestinians. W</title>
    <updated>2023-11-21T00:29:57+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Prepares To Sanction Israel #usa #israel  The US is preparing to sanction Israel. President Biden wrote in an Op-Ed that the US is preparing to issue visa bans against extremist settlers in the West Bank who are attacking and displacing Palestinians. While officials backed up that op-ed and told Politico that they are also preparing sanctions. President Biden also said that the Gaza strip and West Bank should be reunited and be governed under a revitalized Palestinian Authority. The US continues to publicly oppose an Israeli occupation of Gaza after the war is over.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7303706080247434526" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-11-21T00:29:57+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
