<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-11-06T23:38:31+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7294737926674582815</id>
    <title>Chinese Jet Almost Hit B-52 Bomber #usa #america  A Chinese fighter jet came within 10 feet of a US B-52 bomber over the South China Sea earlier this week, that’s what you’re seeing on screen right now. The US says the Chinese pilot was “flying at an unco</title>
    <updated>2023-10-27T20:28:55+00:00</updated>
    <content>Chinese Jet Almost Hit B-52 Bomber #usa #america  A Chinese fighter jet came within 10 feet of a US B-52 bomber over the South China Sea earlier this week, that’s what you’re seeing on screen right now. The US says the Chinese pilot was “flying at an uncontrolled excessive speed, flying below, in front of, and within 10 feet of the B-52, putting both aircraft in danger of collision.” In response to this, China released a video showing a US warship doing what they call “close-in harassment” on August 19th, which is what you’re watching right now. China says the US is the real provoker, risk-taker and disrupter. But the US says that China has engaged in risky and aggressive behavior in the skies over 180 times since Fall of 2021. Good lord, which one of them is gonna yell “mom” first?</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7294737926674582815" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-27T20:28:55+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7295884650151546143</id>
    <title>Hamas Wasn’t Expecting America To Join The Battle #usa #israel  Hamas says it didn’t expect such a strong response from the U.S. With a senior member of the group telling the financial times - “An Israeli response? Yes, we expected that but what we’re see</title>
    <updated>2023-10-30T22:38:46+00:00</updated>
    <content>Hamas Wasn’t Expecting America To Join The Battle #usa #israel  Hamas says it didn’t expect such a strong response from the U.S. With a senior member of the group telling the financial times - “An Israeli response? Yes, we expected that but what we’re seeing now is the entrance of the US into the battle, and this we didn’t count on.” This alluding to how the US’ two carriers have restrained Hamas’ allies from fully entering the war with Israel as Hamas expected them to. Jordan has asked the United States to deploy Patriots in its country to bolster its defense. An anti-Semitic mob of hundreds stormed an airport and its tarmac in Russia looking for Jewish people who they claim were on a flight from Tel Aviv. Earlier in the day, the New York Times reports that hundreds gathered outside of a hotel after rumors that it was “filled with Jews”. Russia has blamed Ukraine for its own people forming antisemitic mobs.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7295884650151546143" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-30T22:38:46+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7296251541105675550</id>
    <title>Israel Strikes Refugee Camp #usa #israel  Israel has confirmed that it carried out an airstrike on Gaza’s largest refugee camp to kill a senior Hamas commander. The Wall Street Journal says Doctors estimate scores of civilians were killed in the strike. T</title>
    <updated>2023-10-31T22:22:31+00:00</updated>
    <content>Israel Strikes Refugee Camp #usa #israel  Israel has confirmed that it carried out an airstrike on Gaza’s largest refugee camp to kill a senior Hamas commander. The Wall Street Journal says Doctors estimate scores of civilians were killed in the strike. The IDF was asked by Wolf Blitzer why they would hit the camp if they knew it had  innocent refugees and civilians. And the spokesperson said: “This is the tragedy of war, wolf. We've been saying for days, move south." The Houthis have entered the conflict, according to Reuters. The Houthis, based in Yemen over a thousand miles away from Israel, say they have carried out 3 missile attacks on Israel so far. The first of these attacks was intercepted by the US navy and Saudi Arabia while the 2nd hit Egypt instead of Israel, and initial reports seem to suggest that the third attack hit Jordan by accident today.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7296251541105675550" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-31T22:22:31+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7298462694175214878</id>
    <title>Iran Threatened With Tomahawkalypse As US Reveals Sub Location #usa #america  In a very rare announcement, the US announced the arrival of one of its most secretive assets to the Persian Gulf. A nuclear submarine. The message they’re sending is clear and </title>
    <updated>2023-11-06T21:23:01+00:00</updated>
    <content>Iran Threatened With Tomahawkalypse As US Reveals Sub Location #usa #america  In a very rare announcement, the US announced the arrival of one of its most secretive assets to the Persian Gulf. A nuclear submarine. The message they’re sending is clear and the recipient of that message is Iran and it’s proxies. The USS Florida is one of four Ohio Class Submarines that carries 154 tomahawk missiles that can each carry a 1,000 pound warhead and travel up to 1,500 miles. It also deploys navy seals. These subs are known as the four horsemen of the Tomahawkalypse.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7298462694175214878" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-11-06T21:23:01+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7298497621595917598</id>
    <title>Israel Conducts Space Combat In A Global First #usa #israel  Israel shot down a missile in space in what is the first recorded instance of space combat. With the Telegraph reporting that the missile was fired by Yemen’s Houthis, where it traveled out of t</title>
    <updated>2023-11-06T23:38:31+00:00</updated>
    <content>Israel Conducts Space Combat In A Global First #usa #israel  Israel shot down a missile in space in what is the first recorded instance of space combat. With the Telegraph reporting that the missile was fired by Yemen’s Houthis, where it traveled out of the earth’s atmosphere and was intercepted by Israel’s Arrow. Israel has suspended a cabinet minister after he suggested nuking Gaza. Iran says that the US will be hit hard if it doesn’t implement a ceasefire in Gaza. Iranian proxies have continued to attack US bases. They’ve launched at least 40 attacks on America in the past 20 days with at least 45 US troops being injured according to NBC News. The US has conducted at least two airstrikes in response and is now calling on the Iraqi government to stop Iran’s proxies from further attacks. The King of Jordan says they worked with Israel to airdrop medical supplies to a hospital in Gaza. Israel says that its ground invasion has split Gaza in half and the IDF says that it expects to enter Gaza City within the next 48 hours. In an interview, a senior Hamas leader called North Korea an ally and suggested that one day they could intervene in the conflict. This comes after AP identified Hamas using North Korean supplied weapons in the October 7th attack. France has had more than a thousand anti-Semitic incidents since October 7th according to the French interior minister. Turkish police used tear gas and water cannons to stop pro-Palestinian protesters from storming an Air Force base that houses US troops according to Reuters. </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7298497621595917598" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-11-06T23:38:31+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
