<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-08-28T18:29:56+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7270229825829358890</id>
    <title>Algeria Blocks French Airforce #france #algeria  Algeria says France can’t fly military aircraft over the country in order to conduct a “military operation” in Niger. France responded by saying “cool, we never asked for such a thing”. 12 nigerien soldiers</title>
    <updated>2023-08-22T19:25:07+00:00</updated>
    <content>Algeria Blocks French Airforce #france #algeria  Algeria says France can’t fly military aircraft over the country in order to conduct a “military operation” in Niger. France responded by saying “cool, we never asked for such a thing”. 12 nigerien soldiers, as in soldiers from Niger, were killed in a terrorist ambush, that’s the 8th terrorist attack on the Army since the coup happened. Also the African Union has kicked Niger out of the union due to the coup and the new US ambassador has arrived in the country but they won’t be meeting with the Junta.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7270229825829358890" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-22T19:25:07+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7270604618403548458</id>
    <title>Wagner To Get Revenge On Russia For Leader’s Death #russia #ukraine  Wagner says the Kremlin will now be captured after Russia killed the group’s leader. Shortly after Prigo’s death, Putin was seen joyfully speaking at a public event. Russia has opened a </title>
    <updated>2023-08-23T19:39:36+00:00</updated>
    <content>Wagner To Get Revenge On Russia For Leader’s Death #russia #ukraine  Wagner says the Kremlin will now be captured after Russia killed the group’s leader. Shortly after Prigo’s death, Putin was seen joyfully speaking at a public event. Russia has opened a criminal investigation into the crash. Some Russian officials have blamed Ukraine but Wagner is pinning the blame straight on the Kremlin. The Pentagon says no one should be surprised that Prigo is dead. Biden says that he’s not surprised and that not much happens in Russia that Putin isn’t behind. It’s unclear if Putin will try to claim the $250,000 bounty the FBI had on Prigo</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7270604618403548458" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-23T19:39:36+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7270951365181017387</id>
    <title>Putin Planted Bomb On Wagner Plane #russia #ukraine  US intelligence believes that a Russian anti-air missile shot down Prigo’s plane, killing all of Wagner’s senior leadership but US officials believe a bomb exploded on board. British Intelligence believ</title>
    <updated>2023-08-24T18:05:04+00:00</updated>
    <content>Putin Planted Bomb On Wagner Plane #russia #ukraine  US intelligence believes that a Russian anti-air missile shot down Prigo’s plane, killing all of Wagner’s senior leadership but US officials believe a bomb exploded on board. British Intelligence believes Russia’s FSB took down the plane. Either way it’s believed that yesterday’s assassination was a message to all of Russia’s elite. If Putin is willing to kill Prigo in broad daylight over Moscow.. then absolutely no one is safe. Putin has sent his condolences to Prigo’s family and he says he’s waiting for the results of the investigation.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7270951365181017387" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-24T18:05:04+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7271054071765716267</id>
    <title>Former President Donald Trump turned himself at the Fulton County jail. This is Donald’s Trump mugshot. Trump and 18 co-defendants face a noon ET Friday deadline to voluntarily surrender after being criminally charged in the state’s 2020 election subversi</title>
    <updated>2023-08-25T00:43:29+00:00</updated>
    <content>Former President Donald Trump turned himself at the Fulton County jail. This is Donald’s Trump mugshot. Trump and 18 co-defendants face a noon ET Friday deadline to voluntarily surrender after being criminally charged in the state’s 2020 election subversion case. Trump agreed earlier this week to a $200,000 bond. The order also bars him from using social media to target co-defendants or witnesses. Fulton County District Attorney Fani Willis is asking for the trial of all 19 people to begin on October 23, an extremely ambitious schedule. Trump opposes the proposed trial date, his attorneys said this afternoon. Trump’s former lawyer, Rudy Giuliani, surrendered Wednesday, and former White House chief of staff Mark Meadows surrendered Thursday. Trump is accused in the indictment of being the head of a “criminal enterprise” that was part of a broad conspiracy to overturn his electoral defeat in the state. The former president faces 91 charges across four separate criminal cases. </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7271054071765716267" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-25T00:43:29+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7272442090938797355</id>
    <title>Shooting At University of North Carolina Chapel Hill #usa #unc  There has been a shooting at the University of North Carolina Chapel Hill. There are reports of several injuries. The Shooter is believed to be still at large. The college is asking students </title>
    <updated>2023-08-28T18:29:56+00:00</updated>
    <content>Shooting At University of North Carolina Chapel Hill #usa #unc  There has been a shooting at the University of North Carolina Chapel Hill. There are reports of several injuries. The Shooter is believed to be still at large. The college is asking students to shelter in place.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7272442090938797355" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-28T18:29:56+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
