<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-09-19T20:18:55+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7278802150493408554</id>
    <title>Putin Praises Musk as SpaceX Faces Growing Criticism #usa #elonmusk  Putin called Elon Musk an outstanding person yesterday. This comes after allegations that he blocked Ukraine from taking out Russia’s navy due to his own ego. British reporters hounded M</title>
    <updated>2023-09-14T21:49:58+00:00</updated>
    <content>Putin Praises Musk as SpaceX Faces Growing Criticism #usa #elonmusk  Putin called Elon Musk an outstanding person yesterday. This comes after allegations that he blocked Ukraine from taking out Russia’s navy due to his own ego. British reporters hounded Musk yesterday, asking him repeatedly “Has your ego and ignorance cost Ukrainian lives?”. Musk didn’t respond. And the Washington Post recently pointed out that the government could just nationalize Starlink if Musk’s antics continue. But the press is the least of Musk’s worries right now as SpaceX is growing under increasing scrutiny, not just from the public but from the U.S. military as well. With the Air Force Secretary saying “If we’re going to rely upon commercial architectures or commercial systems for operational use, then we have to have some assurances that they’re going to be available” SpaceX is currently contracted to create a rocket that can deliver supplies to a conflict zone but now the Air Force may be second guessing the contract. With some asking “If Musk will do this to the people who need help the most, what’s stopping him from doing it to America?” And a U.S. general saying “American industry has to be clear-eyed on the full spectrum of what their products could be used for”. On top of all of that, the US awarded Lockheed Martin and Northrop Grumman a 1.5 billion dollar contract to create a competing satellite internet network.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7278802150493408554" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-14T21:49:58+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7279907511808085294</id>
    <title>America Trolls China #usa #america  America is giving China a taste of their own medicine. Right now China is undergoing what appears to be a purge with several top officials being fired and placed on house arrest for unknown reasons. But America’s ambass</title>
    <updated>2023-09-17T21:19:27+00:00</updated>
    <content>America Trolls China #usa #america  America is giving China a taste of their own medicine. Right now China is undergoing what appears to be a purge with several top officials being fired and placed on house arrest for unknown reasons. But America’s ambassador to Japan, who is none other than Rahm Emmanuel, has wasted no time giving China a taste of their wolf warrior diplomacy. Tweeting: “President Xi's cabinet lineup is now resembling Agatha Christie's novel And Then There Were None. Who's going to win this unemployment race? China’s youth or Xi's cabinet?  #MysteryInBeijingBuilding”. And then once US intelligence concluded that the Chinese defense minister was actually under investigation and put on house arrest for unknown reasons, Rahm tweeted: “As Shakespeare wrote in Hamlet, “Something is rotten in the state of Denmark.” 1st: Defense Minister Li hasn’t been seen or heard from in 3 weeks. 2nd: He was a no-show for his trip to Vietnam. Now: He’s absent from his scheduled meeting with the Singaporean Chief of Navy because he was placed on house arrest???...Might be getting crowded in there. Good news is I heard he’s paid off his mortgage with the Country Garden real estate developers.” I can’t say for certain but I think this is China’s first introduction to Chicago style politics. If Rahm keeps tweeting like this, China is gonna have a mental breakdown by the end of the month. #chicago </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7279907511808085294" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-17T21:19:27+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7280173610302491946</id>
    <title>F-35 Goes Missing After Pilot Ejects #usa #america  The U.S. military is asking for the public's help in finding a lost F-35. The 80 million dollar stealth jet went missing when a pilot ejected from it over North Carolina this afternoon. The jet is report</title>
    <updated>2023-09-18T14:32:09+00:00</updated>
    <content>F-35 Goes Missing After Pilot Ejects #usa #america  The U.S. military is asking for the public's help in finding a lost F-35. The 80 million dollar stealth jet went missing when a pilot ejected from it over North Carolina this afternoon. The jet is reportedly on autopilot and hasn’t crashed. If you’ve seen the jet, they’re asking that you call them. 80 million dollars but you don’t air tag it?</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7280173610302491946" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-18T14:32:09+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7280294874832801067</id>
    <title>India Killed Canadian Leader #canada #india  Canada says India is behind the murder of a Canadian Sikh leader. Canadian intelligence says it’s identified a credible link between the fatal shooting and India. Trudeau raised the issue with Modi at the G-20 </title>
    <updated>2023-09-18T22:22:34+00:00</updated>
    <content>India Killed Canadian Leader #canada #india  Canada says India is behind the murder of a Canadian Sikh leader. Canadian intelligence says it’s identified a credible link between the fatal shooting and India. Trudeau raised the issue with Modi at the G-20 which explains their very chilly &amp; awkward greeting here, Trudeau told the House of Commons today: “Any involvement of a foreign government in the killing of a Canadian citizen on Canadian soil is an unacceptable violation of our sovereignty”. Adding “It is contrary to the fundamental rules by which free, open and democratic societies conduct themselves” The murdered leader was very supportive of an Indian separatist state. India has denied the accusation. Canada is looking at severe measures to “punish” India but has reportedly privately ruled out severing diplomatic ties. What’s interesting though is that the Canadian leader was the 3rd Sikh leader to be killed in recent months.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7280294874832801067" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-18T22:22:34+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7280634113508363563</id>
    <title>India and Canada Continue To Fall Out Over Murder Of Sikh Leader #canada #india #usa  Canada has briefed the US, UK, and France over India’s killing of a Canadian Sikh Leader in Canada. Canada has expelled an Indian diplomat they believe is India’s head s</title>
    <updated>2023-09-19T20:18:55+00:00</updated>
    <content>India and Canada Continue To Fall Out Over Murder Of Sikh Leader #canada #india #usa  Canada has briefed the US, UK, and France over India’s killing of a Canadian Sikh Leader in Canada. Canada has expelled an Indian diplomat they believe is India’s head spy over the killing. India has retaliated by kicking out a Canadian diplomat. Canada has halted trade negotiations and postponed its trade mission in response to the killing. In a statement India said the accusation is “absurd and motivated.” And alleged Canada is continuing to give shelter to anti-Indian terrorists and that they refuse to do anything about it. The Canadian ambassador to India was also summoned, he was seen storming out of the building angrily and slamming his car door. Canada is urging its citizens to avoid traveling to India. Meanwhile, Indian TV has labeled their intelligence service “the new Mossad”. Canada has been pressuring 5 eyes to raise the murder with India in recent months, and they allegedly did privately last week. But It also asked them to release a joint statement condemning the action, and its allies, including the United States, have declined. This is in spite of the US helping Canadian intelligence discover India’s action. Yesterday, the U.S. said that it was deeply concerned about the killing and that the perpetrators must be brought to justice. Australia said that they raised the issue with India and expressed their deep concern. This comes at a particularly awkward time. As the US-led West has been courting India to be a strategic counterweight to China and are trying to avoid antagonizing them. Earlier this year, India demanded that the U.S. and UK break up protests outside of their embassies and when the countries said that wasn’t something they could do - they removed the concrete barriers in front of the British embassy in India to punish them. Many have pointed out that India seems to think it can act with impunity &amp; push around everyone in the West except the United States and so for the US to stay quiet as India bullies its allies, it sends the wrong message. The United States would better serve its allies and the values it claims to stand for if it condemned India and backed up its closest ally instead of playing coy.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7280634113508363563" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-19T20:18:55+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
