<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-10-23T22:09:25+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7290707916590550314</id>
    <title>US Warns Iran To Not Escalate With Israel #usa #israel  The US has warned Iran to not escalate the conflict with Israel, this comes as the US has deployed another carrier and is preparing troops for deployment. Israel turned water back on for Gaza after P</title>
    <updated>2023-10-16T23:50:31+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Warns Iran To Not Escalate With Israel #usa #israel  The US has warned Iran to not escalate the conflict with Israel, this comes as the US has deployed another carrier and is preparing troops for deployment. Israel turned water back on for Gaza after President Biden pressured them to do so. Biden is also pushing Israel to demonstrate restraint. Acknowledging that Israel has a right to destroy Hamas but not a right to subject Palestine to collective punishment. He also warned against occupying Gaza. Israel’s ground offensive is still expected, but keeps getting delayed by rain.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7290707916590550314" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-16T23:50:31+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7291002229492878638</id>
    <title>US Gets Israel To Allow Aid To Gaza #usa #israel  After 8 hours of negotiations with Israel, the United States has convinced Israel to agree to develop a plan to let humanitarian aid flow into Gaza as well as create areas to keep civilians out of harm's w</title>
    <updated>2023-10-17T18:52:30+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Gets Israel To Allow Aid To Gaza #usa #israel  After 8 hours of negotiations with Israel, the United States has convinced Israel to agree to develop a plan to let humanitarian aid flow into Gaza as well as create areas to keep civilians out of harm's way. The US warned that if Hamas tries to block or seize the aid, the US will prevent it from happening. President Biden will go to Israel tomorrow, where he will be presented with a plan from Israel on how they plan to conduct their operation in a way that minimizes civilian casualties according to the State Department. They will also present him with a briefing on their war strategy. After this, Biden will fly to Jordan where he will meet with the President of Palestine and Egypt, and the King of Jordan. The King of Jordan says that Egypt and Israel will not accept any refugees or support Israel’s operation to take out Hamas but President Biden seems determined to change that. Secretary Blinken has taken 13 trips in the past 72 hours between 8 different Middle Eastern capitals in an effort to prevent an escalation of this war.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7291002229492878638" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-17T18:52:30+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7291398010318163246</id>
    <title>Hospital In Gaza Hit By Rogue Missile #usa #israel  Yesterday a hospital in Gaza was hit by a rogue missile. Visual evidence from Palestinians, an independent assessment from the Pentagon, and overwhelming evidence released by the IDF suggest this was a P</title>
    <updated>2023-10-18T20:28:19+00:00</updated>
    <content>Hospital In Gaza Hit By Rogue Missile #usa #israel  Yesterday a hospital in Gaza was hit by a rogue missile. Visual evidence from Palestinians, an independent assessment from the Pentagon, and overwhelming evidence released by the IDF suggest this was a PIJ rocket that misfired. The US has also collected “high confidence” signals intelligence that this was caused by the PIJ. President Biden also went as far to say that the Department of Defense concluded that it wasn’t Israel based on their own intelligence. The IDF also released an alleged audio recording between two Hamas members discussing the rocket that misfired. Contrary to initial claims, the hospital wasn't completely destroyed. It's still standing and footage from the ground shows that the worst damage was done in the parking lot. The crater in the ground is consistent with militant missiles, not Israeli JDAMs according to most experts. Hamas claims that nearly 500 were killed. But due to the seeming lack of major damage to any of the nearby buildings or independent verification of those numbers, people are starting to doubt that figure. The facts of what actually happened differ from what mainstream media and several other news creators initially reported yesterday because they ran with Hamas’ narrative. With Al-Jazeera, BBC, MSNBC among several others all saying with certainty that Israel had done this. This misinformation resulted in widespread riots and protests outside of US embassies across the Middle East. As well as regional-wide condemnation of Israel, calls to war by Hezbollah and Iran, and drones launched at US bases in Iraq. Today should serve as a day of reflection for the media and news influencers since they almost started a region-wide war yesterday. Taking a second to make sure what you have is correct is more important than being first because someone’s going to get there before you do anyways.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7291398010318163246" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-18T20:28:19+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7291784553260125486</id>
    <title>US Forces Under Assault Across Middle East #usa #israel  The United States has issued a very rare worldwide caution travel alert due to the risk of terror attacks, protests, and violent actions against Americans. Reuters reports that US officials say that</title>
    <updated>2023-10-19T21:28:26+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Forces Under Assault Across Middle East #usa #israel  The United States has issued a very rare worldwide caution travel alert due to the risk of terror attacks, protests, and violent actions against Americans. Reuters reports that US officials say that a Hezebollah linked terror group used drones to attack a US Military base in Syria today causing minor injuries. Meanwhile the Pentagon says a US Navy warship operating in the Northern Red Sea today intercepted 3 cruise missiles and several drones that were fired from the Houthi militant group in Yemen. The Pentagon says the missiles were potentially headed towards Israel which is why they intercepted them, but that they can’t currently confirm that Israel was the target. Channel 13 in Israel is reporting that Israel believes that the missiles were launched at them. And just now Reuters is reporting that two security sources tell them that yet another US base in Iraq has been hit with drones and missiles, this is reportedly the 5th attack on US forces in Iraq and Syria in the past 36 hours. The US has also ordered Americans to leave Lebanon as soon as possible and has changed its travel advisory to “Do Not Travel”.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7291784553260125486" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-19T21:28:26+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7293279484566850862</id>
    <title>US Fears Region-Wide War #usa #israel  The US fears a widening region-wide war, US officials tell Axios. With the Pentagon now putting even more troops on “prepare to deploy orders” This comes as the US has sent two aircraft carriers to the region, surged</title>
    <updated>2023-10-23T22:09:25+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Fears Region-Wide War #usa #israel  The US fears a widening region-wide war, US officials tell Axios. With the Pentagon now putting even more troops on “prepare to deploy orders” This comes as the US has sent two aircraft carriers to the region, surged aircraft to its bases in the Middle East, and added more air defense systems and all weekend, US bases all over the region were attacked by terror groups. The rhetoric coming out of Israel and Iran has been white hot, with the BBC reporting that Iran warned Israel that if they don’t stop striking Gaza - the region will spiral out of control. Israel and Hezbollah are continuing to exchange fire with each other on the northern border. With the New York Times reporting that the United States has told Israel to not conduct a preemptive strike on Hezbollah. With the outlet also saying the US believes that Israel would struggle in a two front war, and that such a war would drag both them and Iran into it.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7293279484566850862" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-23T22:09:25+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
