<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-09-17T21:19:27+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7278058200476273963</id>
    <title>America &amp; Canada Make China Very Mad #usa #canada  The U.S. and Canada sailed two ships through the Taiwan strait after China claimed it had total ownership over the strait. China sent three ships armed with torpedoes and missiles to flank the Canadian wa</title>
    <updated>2023-09-12T21:43:09+00:00</updated>
    <content>America &amp; Canada Make China Very Mad #usa #canada  The U.S. and Canada sailed two ships through the Taiwan strait after China claimed it had total ownership over the strait. China sent three ships armed with torpedoes and missiles to flank the Canadian warship and they followed them for 17 hours. China also sent fighter jets to intercept the warships but upon realizing that the Canadian vessel wasn’t alone, it changed course. The U.S. frequently takes this route as part of it’s freedom of navigation operations. China accused these two hoodlums of trying to stir up trouble.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7278058200476273963" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-12T21:43:09+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7278417481327217963</id>
    <title>Ukraine Destroys Russian Submarine &amp; Landing Ship #ukraine #russia  Ukraine destroyed a Russian submarine and a landing ship. Using British Storm Shadow missiles, they hit a Russian dry dock in Crimea. Both vessels have been completely destroyed. The subm</title>
    <updated>2023-09-13T20:57:20+00:00</updated>
    <content>Ukraine Destroys Russian Submarine &amp; Landing Ship #ukraine #russia  Ukraine destroyed a Russian submarine and a landing ship. Using British Storm Shadow missiles, they hit a Russian dry dock in Crimea. Both vessels have been completely destroyed. The submarine is only one of 6 that Russia has in the Black Sea, and Russia frequently uses them to fire cruise missiles at Ukraine. Russia has repeatedly said that attacking this area would result in a nuclear response. These missiles hit the same area that Elon Musk blocked Ukraine from hitting earlier in the year by turning off the internet. Ukraine’s attack would have nearly taken out the entire Russian Black Sea fleet, but General Musk blocked it. As a result of the aborted attack, the Russian Black Sea Fleet would proceed to fire hundreds of missiles at Ukrainian cities in the following months, causing widespread destruction and numerous civilian casualties. So far though, it’s been over 12 hours and Russia’s super spooky nuclear threat appears to be yet another bluff. If you’re threatening to use nukes, you’ve already lost and if you actually believe their nuclear threats - you’re a sucker. You know who also doesn’t buy the nuclear threats? The United States. They will be providing Ukraine with the Army Tactical Missile System, which fires ballistic missiles that have a range of 300 kilometers… So more strikes inside of occupied Crimea and Russia are coming.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7278417481327217963" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-13T20:57:20+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7278451597305351470</id>
    <title>Russia Gives North Korea Nuclear Missiles #russia #korea  Kim Jong Un and Putin met in Russia today. Kim vowed “full and unconditional” support for Russia, and called Russia’s war “just”. Russia is seeking stockpiles of aging ammunition and rockets for th</title>
    <updated>2023-09-13T23:09:40+00:00</updated>
    <content>Russia Gives North Korea Nuclear Missiles #russia #korea  Kim Jong Un and Putin met in Russia today. Kim vowed “full and unconditional” support for Russia, and called Russia’s war “just”. Russia is seeking stockpiles of aging ammunition and rockets for their soviet weapons. North Korea is seeking food and missile technology for their nuclear missiles and spy satellites. Earlier this year, experts pointed out that North Korea’s nuclear missiles look an awful lot like Russian nuclear missiles which would put Russia in violation of the Nuclear Non-proliferation treaty if true. If Russia and North Korea do sign a deal though, it’ll violate global sanctions making Russia and North Korea subjected to even more UN-sanctioned sanctions. Kim ended the meeting by saying that “we believe with certainty that the Russian army and people will achieve a great victory in the just fight to punish the evil forces”. Uhh.. Lol.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7278451597305351470" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-13T23:09:40+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7278802150493408554</id>
    <title>Putin Praises Musk as SpaceX Faces Growing Criticism #usa #elonmusk  Putin called Elon Musk an outstanding person yesterday. This comes after allegations that he blocked Ukraine from taking out Russia’s navy due to his own ego. British reporters hounded M</title>
    <updated>2023-09-14T21:49:58+00:00</updated>
    <content>Putin Praises Musk as SpaceX Faces Growing Criticism #usa #elonmusk  Putin called Elon Musk an outstanding person yesterday. This comes after allegations that he blocked Ukraine from taking out Russia’s navy due to his own ego. British reporters hounded Musk yesterday, asking him repeatedly “Has your ego and ignorance cost Ukrainian lives?”. Musk didn’t respond. And the Washington Post recently pointed out that the government could just nationalize Starlink if Musk’s antics continue. But the press is the least of Musk’s worries right now as SpaceX is growing under increasing scrutiny, not just from the public but from the U.S. military as well. With the Air Force Secretary saying “If we’re going to rely upon commercial architectures or commercial systems for operational use, then we have to have some assurances that they’re going to be available” SpaceX is currently contracted to create a rocket that can deliver supplies to a conflict zone but now the Air Force may be second guessing the contract. With some asking “If Musk will do this to the people who need help the most, what’s stopping him from doing it to America?” And a U.S. general saying “American industry has to be clear-eyed on the full spectrum of what their products could be used for”. On top of all of that, the US awarded Lockheed Martin and Northrop Grumman a 1.5 billion dollar contract to create a competing satellite internet network.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7278802150493408554" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-14T21:49:58+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7279907511808085294</id>
    <title>America Trolls China #usa #america  America is giving China a taste of their own medicine. Right now China is undergoing what appears to be a purge with several top officials being fired and placed on house arrest for unknown reasons. But America’s ambass</title>
    <updated>2023-09-17T21:19:27+00:00</updated>
    <content>America Trolls China #usa #america  America is giving China a taste of their own medicine. Right now China is undergoing what appears to be a purge with several top officials being fired and placed on house arrest for unknown reasons. But America’s ambassador to Japan, who is none other than Rahm Emmanuel, has wasted no time giving China a taste of their wolf warrior diplomacy. Tweeting: “President Xi's cabinet lineup is now resembling Agatha Christie's novel And Then There Were None. Who's going to win this unemployment race? China’s youth or Xi's cabinet?  #MysteryInBeijingBuilding”. And then once US intelligence concluded that the Chinese defense minister was actually under investigation and put on house arrest for unknown reasons, Rahm tweeted: “As Shakespeare wrote in Hamlet, “Something is rotten in the state of Denmark.” 1st: Defense Minister Li hasn’t been seen or heard from in 3 weeks. 2nd: He was a no-show for his trip to Vietnam. Now: He’s absent from his scheduled meeting with the Singaporean Chief of Navy because he was placed on house arrest???...Might be getting crowded in there. Good news is I heard he’s paid off his mortgage with the Country Garden real estate developers.” I can’t say for certain but I think this is China’s first introduction to Chicago style politics. If Rahm keeps tweeting like this, China is gonna have a mental breakdown by the end of the month. #chicago </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7279907511808085294" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-17T21:19:27+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
