<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-10-05T21:45:12+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7286145132175346987</id>
    <title>Los Angeles Trolls Saudi Arabia #usa #saudiarabia  Los Angeles has renamed an intersection for Jamal Khashoggi, the intersection is in front of the Saudi Consulate. Last year, DC renamed the street that the Saudi embassy is on to Jamal Khashoggi Way. Jama</title>
    <updated>2023-10-04T16:44:49+00:00</updated>
    <content>Los Angeles Trolls Saudi Arabia #usa #saudiarabia  Los Angeles has renamed an intersection for Jamal Khashoggi, the intersection is in front of the Saudi Consulate. Last year, DC renamed the street that the Saudi embassy is on to Jamal Khashoggi Way. Jamal Khashoggi was a very prevalent journalist who worked for the Washington Post, was a permanent US resident, and whose children were US citizens. Saudi Arabia murdered him inside of an embassy in Turkey at the direct order of the Saudi Crown Prince. They cut off his limbs while he was still alive and tortured him on Skype while MBS’s staff watched. After the murder, MBS reportedly was given Khashoggi’s fingers. And this is the country Joe Biden wants to name a “non-NATO major ally”.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7286145132175346987" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-04T16:44:49+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7286175246548258090</id>
    <title>Mexico Says US Doesn’t Do Anything For Them #usa #mexico  The President of Mexico says the U.S. should send the money it’s giving to Ukraine to Latin America instead. Saying that the US doesn’t do anything for them. He also called on the US to lift sancti</title>
    <updated>2023-10-04T18:41:28+00:00</updated>
    <content>Mexico Says US Doesn’t Do Anything For Them #usa #mexico  The President of Mexico says the U.S. should send the money it’s giving to Ukraine to Latin America instead. Saying that the US doesn’t do anything for them. He also called on the US to lift sanctions on Cuba and Venezuela, adding that the sanctions are why there’s a migrant crisis. But experts say that economic mismanagement and political repression are why people are leaving, not sanctions.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7286175246548258090" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-04T18:41:28+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7286191953404841259</id>
    <title>Israel &amp; Saudi Arabia Mad At US For Trying To Protect Palestine #usa #israel #saudiarabia  Israel and Saudi Arabia are reportedly frustrated with the United States over its insistence on Palestine. The US and Saudi are negotiating a defense pact that in o</title>
    <updated>2023-10-04T19:46:22+00:00</updated>
    <content>Israel &amp; Saudi Arabia Mad At US For Trying To Protect Palestine #usa #israel #saudiarabia  Israel and Saudi Arabia are reportedly frustrated with the United States over its insistence on Palestine. The US and Saudi are negotiating a defense pact that in order to go through requires Israel and Saudi to normalize relations with each other; but the US requires that Palestine be given a pathway to statehood in that normalization deal. This has made the two other countries rather annoyed. Saudi wants a NATO-like pledge from the US to defend the Kingdom but the US isn’t so sure given Saudi’s rampant history of human rights abuses &amp; 9/11. The US would rather just make Saudi a Major Non-NATO ally instead.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7286191953404841259" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-04T19:46:22+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7286535008242748715</id>
    <title>US F-16 Shoots Down Turkish Drone #usa #turkey  A US Fighter Jet just shot down a Turkish drone in Syria after it was deemed a threat to US forces today in a very rare NATO-on-NATO clash. Turkey denies that it was their drone but the US says it was an arm</title>
    <updated>2023-10-05T17:57:50+00:00</updated>
    <content>US F-16 Shoots Down Turkish Drone #usa #turkey  A US Fighter Jet just shot down a Turkish drone in Syria after it was deemed a threat to US forces today in a very rare NATO-on-NATO clash. Turkey denies that it was their drone but the US says it was an armed Turkish drone, and that it was aware of that before it acted. The drone came too close to US Forces who were conducting operations in the area and the US acted in self-defense after Turkey failed to answer their calls.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7286535008242748715" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-05T17:57:50+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7286593689713954090</id>
    <title>Turkey Unfazed By America’s Warning #usa #america  Turkey says its unfazed by the US shooting down its drone, and will continue its bombings of Kurdish infrastructure in Iraq and Syria. Turkey was conducting airstrikes a half kilometer away from US forces</title>
    <updated>2023-10-05T21:45:12+00:00</updated>
    <content>Turkey Unfazed By America’s Warning #usa #america  Turkey says its unfazed by the US shooting down its drone, and will continue its bombings of Kurdish infrastructure in Iraq and Syria. Turkey was conducting airstrikes a half kilometer away from US forces in a US restricted zone when the US acted in self-defense and shot down their drone. The US says it was a regrettable incident but some analysts say.. Look it’s not everyday the US shoots down a NATO drone, so they’re also sending a message to Turkey to quit. But Turkey is clearly not receiving that message. However, the US and Turkey seem to have worked it out with the Pentagon saying that the Turkish drone wasn’t being threatening, it was just where it shouldn’t have been. Adding that Turkey is one of America’s favorite allies.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7286593689713954090" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-05T21:45:12+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
