<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-10-04T19:46:22+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7285839716237200682</id>
    <title>US Speaker Removed For First Time In History #usa #america  For the first time in American history, the speaker of the house has been removed. Needing only 5 votes to can him, McCarthy’s fellow Republicans cannibalized him after he worked with Democrats t</title>
    <updated>2023-10-03T20:59:36+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Speaker Removed For First Time In History #usa #america  For the first time in American history, the speaker of the house has been removed. Needing only 5 votes to can him, McCarthy’s fellow Republicans cannibalized him after he worked with Democrats to prevent the government from shutting down. Democrats said McCarthy wasn't a man of his word, and refused to save his speakership. Kevin was speaker for 270 days, which is about 25 Scaramuccis.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7285839716237200682" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-03T20:59:36+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7285868658608409899</id>
    <title>Test Of Emergency Alert System Tomorrow #usa #america  Tomorrow, Wednesday the 4th, all phones, TVs, and radios in America are going to broadcast an emergency message from the President. The message will be broadcast at 2:20pm eastern time and will say “T</title>
    <updated>2023-10-03T22:51:43+00:00</updated>
    <content>Test Of Emergency Alert System Tomorrow #usa #america  Tomorrow, Wednesday the 4th, all phones, TVs, and radios in America are going to broadcast an emergency message from the President. The message will be broadcast at 2:20pm eastern time and will say “THIS IS A TEST of the National Wireless Emergency Alert System. No action is needed.” Your phone will vibrate and set off an emergency tone, you’ll also get a text message as well. They’re testing the national alert system so you know it exists and also so they know it works. If, god forbid, anything happens tomorrow like an alien invasion or nuclear war - the test will be delayed to the 11th.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7285868658608409899" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-03T22:51:43+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7286145132175346987</id>
    <title>Los Angeles Trolls Saudi Arabia #usa #saudiarabia  Los Angeles has renamed an intersection for Jamal Khashoggi, the intersection is in front of the Saudi Consulate. Last year, DC renamed the street that the Saudi embassy is on to Jamal Khashoggi Way. Jama</title>
    <updated>2023-10-04T16:44:49+00:00</updated>
    <content>Los Angeles Trolls Saudi Arabia #usa #saudiarabia  Los Angeles has renamed an intersection for Jamal Khashoggi, the intersection is in front of the Saudi Consulate. Last year, DC renamed the street that the Saudi embassy is on to Jamal Khashoggi Way. Jamal Khashoggi was a very prevalent journalist who worked for the Washington Post, was a permanent US resident, and whose children were US citizens. Saudi Arabia murdered him inside of an embassy in Turkey at the direct order of the Saudi Crown Prince. They cut off his limbs while he was still alive and tortured him on Skype while MBS’s staff watched. After the murder, MBS reportedly was given Khashoggi’s fingers. And this is the country Joe Biden wants to name a “non-NATO major ally”.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7286145132175346987" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-04T16:44:49+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7286175246548258090</id>
    <title>Mexico Says US Doesn’t Do Anything For Them #usa #mexico  The President of Mexico says the U.S. should send the money it’s giving to Ukraine to Latin America instead. Saying that the US doesn’t do anything for them. He also called on the US to lift sancti</title>
    <updated>2023-10-04T18:41:28+00:00</updated>
    <content>Mexico Says US Doesn’t Do Anything For Them #usa #mexico  The President of Mexico says the U.S. should send the money it’s giving to Ukraine to Latin America instead. Saying that the US doesn’t do anything for them. He also called on the US to lift sanctions on Cuba and Venezuela, adding that the sanctions are why there’s a migrant crisis. But experts say that economic mismanagement and political repression are why people are leaving, not sanctions.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7286175246548258090" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-04T18:41:28+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7286191953404841259</id>
    <title>Israel &amp; Saudi Arabia Mad At US For Trying To Protect Palestine #usa #israel #saudiarabia  Israel and Saudi Arabia are reportedly frustrated with the United States over its insistence on Palestine. The US and Saudi are negotiating a defense pact that in o</title>
    <updated>2023-10-04T19:46:22+00:00</updated>
    <content>Israel &amp; Saudi Arabia Mad At US For Trying To Protect Palestine #usa #israel #saudiarabia  Israel and Saudi Arabia are reportedly frustrated with the United States over its insistence on Palestine. The US and Saudi are negotiating a defense pact that in order to go through requires Israel and Saudi to normalize relations with each other; but the US requires that Palestine be given a pathway to statehood in that normalization deal. This has made the two other countries rather annoyed. Saudi wants a NATO-like pledge from the US to defend the Kingdom but the US isn’t so sure given Saudi’s rampant history of human rights abuses &amp; 9/11. The US would rather just make Saudi a Major Non-NATO ally instead.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7286191953404841259" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-10-04T19:46:22+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
