<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-12-05T23:42:09+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7306700013411831071</id>
    <title>India rescues workers trapped for over a week after breaking through debris #india #rescue  With how the world has been going lately, I know it feels like we never have any good news. But this time I do have some: Officials in India announced that they’ve</title>
    <updated>2023-11-29T02:08:01+00:00</updated>
    <content>India rescues workers trapped for over a week after breaking through debris #india #rescue  With how the world has been going lately, I know it feels like we never have any good news. But this time I do have some: Officials in India announced that they’ve rescued 41 construction workers who were trapped for over a week underground. The 41 men were working on the $1.5 billion Char Dam highway, which is meant to connect four Hindu pilgrimage sites and is one of Prime Minister Narendra Modi’s prized projects. However, while digging through the Himalayas, the tunnel collapsed and trapped the men for 17 days. It’s unclear what exactly caused the collapse, but the mountainous region is well-known for earthquakes, floods, and landslides. The 41 managed to stay alive for so long because rescue crews drilled little passageways into the chamber and pumped in oxygen, water, and food. At the same time, crews were working around the clock to open up a passage big enough to get the men out. They tried various methods, but the one that proved to be the most effective -- despite many snags along the way -- was to just drill through the debris that was blocking the tunnel. Eventually a 3-foot-wide pipe connected the workers to the outside. Initial reports indicated that a wheeled stretcher was sent to them to help them out, But according to the chief minister of the local state, the workers preferred to crawl out on their own. That was a good indication of their health, as the minister added they were all healthy. Crews and locals celebrated each time a man came out of the tunnel, although the rescued workers didn’t get to stay long as they were sent away on ambulances to make sure they were fine. Reportedly, the workers are getting $1,200 for their ordeal. Which isn’t a lot, but at the same time these workers are from India’s poorest states and working a low-paying job. It ends up that the $1,200 is about equal to 6-months of the average salary in the state. So that $1,200 is actually quite a bit for them. (I vote they get more). The real kicker though is that the local chief minister had to ask that “the company that these 41 workers be allowed to go home and spend time with their family for 15 days, 20 days, or 1 month.” So there’s a chance they may only get a little time off for their troubles. But what if that was you? Would you be going back to that tunnel?</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7306700013411831071" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-11-29T02:08:01+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7306990804239764766</id>
    <title>Saudi Offers Iran A Deal They Can’t Refuse #usa #saudiarabia  Saudi Arabia has approached Iran with a deal that they might not be able to refuse. Saudi, according to Bloomberg, has approached Iran with an offer to boost cooperation and investments to its </title>
    <updated>2023-11-29T20:56:32+00:00</updated>
    <content>Saudi Offers Iran A Deal They Can’t Refuse #usa #saudiarabia  Saudi Arabia has approached Iran with a deal that they might not be able to refuse. Saudi, according to Bloomberg, has approached Iran with an offer to boost cooperation and investments to its sanctioned economy if they stop their proxies from turning the Israel-Hamas war into a wider conflict. At the same time though, Saudi Arabia is also pursuing another path with the US. With US Assistant Secretary of State Barbara Leaf saying the US is working with them and their Arab allies to stop Iran from weaponizing the Israel-Hamas war to strengthen its axis of resistance. This is a continuation of Saudi’s two-pronged approach to foreign affairs - they’re trying to deepen ties with Iran and deescalate with them while trying to normalize ties with Israel, achieve a two state solution, and get a defense alliance with the US. Bloomberg writes that it’s unclear how serious Iran is taking Saudi’s offer but that a regional war has been averted so far. Saudi’s main fear is that once this ceasefire ends - Israel will once again ignite the region in anger, making its goal of normalizing with Israel harder to achieve.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7306990804239764766" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-11-29T20:56:32+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7308846810636881182</id>
    <title>US Navy &amp; Cargo Ships Under Attack In Red Sea #usa #navy  The US Navy and several commercial vessels came under attack yesterday. US Central Command says that there were four attacks against three separate cargo ships in the Red Sea. Over the course of ei</title>
    <updated>2023-12-04T20:58:50+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Navy &amp; Cargo Ships Under Attack In Red Sea #usa #navy  The US Navy and several commercial vessels came under attack yesterday. US Central Command says that there were four attacks against three separate cargo ships in the Red Sea. Over the course of eight hours, the USS Carney detected several ballistic missile and drone launches. A ship named the Unity Explorer was reportedly hit by a ballistic missile, along with two other ships. When the USS Carney was responding to the distress calls, Central Command says they shot down several drones headed for the ships. In addition to that, the Carney also shot down a drone that was headed towards itself - However, Central Command says it’s unsure if the Carney was the intended target. The US says that Iran is enabling these attacks and that they will consider all appropriate responses in full coordination with its allies and partners.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7308846810636881182" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-12-04T20:58:50+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7308862546776198430</id>
    <title>India Hires Hitman Who Was Undercover Agent #usa #india  India accidentally hired a DEA agent to kill American citizens, federal prosecutors allege. The DOJ filed charges against a man they allege was working with the Indian government to assassinate two </title>
    <updated>2023-12-04T21:59:46+00:00</updated>
    <content>India Hires Hitman Who Was Undercover Agent #usa #india  India accidentally hired a DEA agent to kill American citizens, federal prosecutors allege. The DOJ filed charges against a man they allege was working with the Indian government to assassinate two Americans and four Canadians. One of the Americans was in California while another was in New York. It’s alleged that the man, after being recruited by the Indian government, paid a 15,000 dollar advance to a hitman to carry out the murder. But.. record scratch, that hitman was an undercover agent for the Drug Enforcement Administration. The indictment alleges that the Indian government would dismiss this man’s criminal charges in exchange for hiring a hitman. The man who has been indicted was in India during the planning of the plots but when he went on a trip to the Czech Republic this summer, he was arrested when he landed by Czech police at the request of the United States. It’s believed that he was lured there by the US in order to arrest him and terminate the plots. The investigation has uncovered what seems to be very solid evidence of India having a transnational assassination campaign. With the Indictment alleging that Indian officials said in texts that they have lots of targets that they still needed to hit. And that they took responsibility for the assassination of the Canadian Sikh leader that happened earlier this year.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7308862546776198430" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-12-04T21:59:46+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7309260014097632542</id>
    <title>Israel To Flood Hamas Tunnels #usa #israel  Israel is weighing a plan to flood Hamas tunnels with seawater according to the Wall Street Journal. Israel has assembled at least 5 large seawater pumps that can pump thousands of cubic meters of water per hour</title>
    <updated>2023-12-05T23:42:09+00:00</updated>
    <content>Israel To Flood Hamas Tunnels #usa #israel  Israel is weighing a plan to flood Hamas tunnels with seawater according to the Wall Street Journal. Israel has assembled at least 5 large seawater pumps that can pump thousands of cubic meters of water per hour. The Wall Street Journal reports that Israel informed the US of the option early last month. This reportedly prompted a discussion on the feasibility and the effect on the environment it may have. The general problem, according to US officials, is that nobody knows how successful pumping will be because nobody knows the exact details of the tunnels. Some experts believe that flooding could affect Gaza’s already polluted soil and cause hazardous substances in the tunnels to seep into the ground while others say that it could impact the stability of buildings. There is also concern about making Gaza’s aquifer even more salty than it already is. Former officials acknowledged to the Wall Street Journal that such an operation could put the Biden Administration in a tough position and potentially bring global condemnation, but that it remains one of the few effective options to disable the tunnel system that spans 300 miles. Egypt has flooded Hamas tunnels in the past. In 2015, they used seawater to flood tunnels operated by smugglers, and it worked - however it did cause damage to nearby farmers’ crops.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7309260014097632542" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-12-05T23:42:09+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
