<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-08-30T20:30:30+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7272442090938797355</id>
    <title>Shooting At University of North Carolina Chapel Hill #usa #unc  There has been a shooting at the University of North Carolina Chapel Hill. There are reports of several injuries. The Shooter is believed to be still at large. The college is asking students </title>
    <updated>2023-08-28T18:29:56+00:00</updated>
    <content>Shooting At University of North Carolina Chapel Hill #usa #unc  There has been a shooting at the University of North Carolina Chapel Hill. There are reports of several injuries. The Shooter is believed to be still at large. The college is asking students to shelter in place.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7272442090938797355" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-28T18:29:56+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7272519143495126315</id>
    <title>Pope Is Beefing With Americans Again #usa #catholic  The Pope is popping off about Americans. He said: “The situation in the United States is not easy” - ya you’re telling me Frank. Adding that conservative Catholics are very reactionary and backwards, an</title>
    <updated>2023-08-28T23:28:47+00:00</updated>
    <content>Pope Is Beefing With Americans Again #usa #catholic  The Pope is popping off about Americans. He said: “The situation in the United States is not easy” - ya you’re telling me Frank. Adding that conservative Catholics are very reactionary and backwards, and that LGBTQ are welcome to the Church &amp; they must accept this. He finished his remarks with “Those American groups of which you speak, so closed, are isolating themselves. And instead of living by doctrine, by the true doctrine that always develops and bears fruit, they live by ideologies”. As long as I can remember the American Catholic Church has been beefing with the Pope. Whether it’s Northeastern Catholics thinking the Church isn’t liberal enough or Southern Catholics thinking the Church isn’t cruel enough.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7272519143495126315" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-28T23:28:47+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7272823440342682926</id>
    <title>China Demands Britain Return Stole Relics #UK #british  China has demanded that the British Museum return all of its Chinese cultural relics that it stole. Adding that the British Museum should return all of their stolen relics to their home countries lik</title>
    <updated>2023-08-29T19:09:39+00:00</updated>
    <content>China Demands Britain Return Stole Relics #UK #british  China has demanded that the British Museum return all of its Chinese cultural relics that it stole. Adding that the British Museum should return all of their stolen relics to their home countries like Egypt, Greece, India, and Nigeria, not just China. They say that the vast majority of their 8 million relics are stolen from other countries, and that the UK has a “bloody, ugly, shameful colonial history”. Damn they kind of ate, not gonna lie. As someone who has been to the British museum, no amount of jokes or memes can prepare you for the amount of theft inside. I was inside for not even 2 minutes when I saw the inside of a pyramid!!! They took part of the inside of one of the pyramids and brought it back to London. What they’ve done to other countries is the equivalent of them stealing our Statue of Liberty, putting it in a museum, and when we ask for it back - they say “hmm no but you can come here and see it”.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7272823440342682926" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-29T19:09:39+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7272901083880607019</id>
    <title>China Having Meltdown Over Japan #japan #korea  China is having an absolute meltdown over Japan. Japan released treated water from Fukushima with the approval of the IAEA into the ocean with many scientists agreeing that it would have a negligible impact </title>
    <updated>2023-08-30T00:10:52+00:00</updated>
    <content>China Having Meltdown Over Japan #japan #korea  China is having an absolute meltdown over Japan. Japan released treated water from Fukushima with the approval of the IAEA into the ocean with many scientists agreeing that it would have a negligible impact on the environment. This is a process that will take 30 years as they slowly release it. But China is acting like Japan unleashed a toxic plague into Asia. With China’s wolf warrior artist releasing this image depicting Japan. First China called them selfish and irresponsible. Now China says it’s blocked all seafood imports from Japan despite all testing of the water and fish showing it to be very safe. So Japan is taking China to the WTO over the seafood ban. Scientists have pointed out that China releases untreated water from its nuclear plants every day that is more radioactive than what Japan is releasing. But that has not stopped Chinese citizens from harassing Japanese businesses and schools with phone calls and throwing rocks at their embassy in China. Japan has asked China to tell its citizens to chill out &amp; China said it has no idea what Japan was talking about. Now as for Japan’s other neighbors - South Korea said that if Japan is following the regulations and doing it safely then who cares. Taiwan and the Philippines basically said whatever. But in Hong Kong, they declared Japan an enemy of the whole world.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7272901083880607019" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-30T00:10:52+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7273215368611532078</id>
    <title>China Drops New Map Claiming India, Japan, Vietnam, Malaysia, Philippines, Russia, and Bhutan #russia #philippines #japan  China dropped it’s new map and it’s neighbors are upset. China’s new map shows them claiming part of India. India says the map is ab</title>
    <updated>2023-08-30T20:30:30+00:00</updated>
    <content>China Drops New Map Claiming India, Japan, Vietnam, Malaysia, Philippines, Russia, and Bhutan #russia #philippines #japan  China dropped it’s new map and it’s neighbors are upset. China’s new map shows them claiming part of India. India says the map is absurd and that their claims have no basis. The map also shows them infringing on Malaysia’s maritime border so Malaysia has rejected their unilateral claims. China’s map also claims part of Russia, Japan, Vietnam, Bhutan, Indonesia, Philippines, and all of Taiwan. It may seem silly for these countries to get very upset over what are essentially just lines on a piece of paper. But lines on a map represent people’s identities, their validation, things they’ve fought thousands of years for. It’s never just a line on a piece of paper.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7273215368611532078" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-30T20:30:30+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
