<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-11-16T22:37:28+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7301079848355630367</id>
    <title>US Upset With Israel As It Strikes Back At Iran &amp; Warns Hezbollah #usa #israel  The US is at least mildly pissed at Israel according to Axios. Yesterday the Pentagon’s chief called his Israeli counterpart to issue a warning about trying to provoke a war w</title>
    <updated>2023-11-13T22:38:54+00:00</updated>
    <content>US Upset With Israel As It Strikes Back At Iran &amp; Warns Hezbollah #usa #israel  The US is at least mildly pissed at Israel according to Axios. Yesterday the Pentagon’s chief called his Israeli counterpart to issue a warning about trying to provoke a war with Hezbollah because the US believes that this will cause a regional war that will draw the US and several other countries into the conflict. Israel flatly denies that this conversation happened but Axios says their sources in both countries claim the call was very direct and frank. The US conducted another round of airstrikes in Eastern Syria on bases used by Iranian proxies and the http://IRGC.US Forces have been attacked 4 times by Iranian proxies since the airstrikes yesterday. There have now been at least 50 attacks on US forces since October 17th according to the Pentagon. The New York Times reported that President Biden has rejected more aggressive bombing options proposed by the Pentagon in hopes of not escalating into a war with Iran. With some now saying his hands are looking to be increasingly tied after today’s attacks. The Biden administration sent an advisor to Lebanon last week to deliver a warning to Hezbollah via Lebanon's parliament according to VOA. The warning was to not escalate the conflict. The advisor reportedly returned to America with the impression that Hezbollah wasn’t interested in an actual war, Axios alleges. Despite this, Israel and Hezbollah keep climbing the escalation ladder with each other, hoping one will give up. The White House was reportedly alarmed by two incidents that looked like they could escalate the conflict. If the Fish continues to plagiarize us, he will be struck down.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7301079848355630367" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-11-13T22:38:54+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7301388553676655903</id>
    <title>Bernie Sanders Breaks Up Fight In US Senate #usa #america  Sen. Markwayne Mullin (R-OK) challenges Teamsters leader Sean O’Brien to a physical fight, standing up midway through a Senate HELP Committee hearing. Chair Bernie Sanders (I-VT) repeatedly attemp</title>
    <updated>2023-11-14T18:36:59+00:00</updated>
    <content>Bernie Sanders Breaks Up Fight In US Senate #usa #america  Sen. Markwayne Mullin (R-OK) challenges Teamsters leader Sean O’Brien to a physical fight, standing up midway through a Senate HELP Committee hearing. Chair Bernie Sanders (I-VT) repeatedly attempts to break them up: “You’re a United States senator.” Mullin and O’Brien, the leader of the major union International Brotherhood of Teamsters, have a history of combative moments — Mullin, a hard-right conservative, has repeatedly challenged O’Brien to physical fights.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7301388553676655903" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-11-14T18:36:59+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7301692282800000286</id>
    <title>Senator Challenges Witness To Charity Boxing Match #usa #america  A congressional hearing devolved into an angry confrontation between a senator and a witness on Tuesday after Republican Sen. Markwayne Mullin of Oklahoma challenged Sean O’Brien, the presi</title>
    <updated>2023-11-15T14:15:29+00:00</updated>
    <content>Senator Challenges Witness To Charity Boxing Match #usa #america  A congressional hearing devolved into an angry confrontation between a senator and a witness on Tuesday after Republican Sen. Markwayne Mullin of Oklahoma challenged Sean O’Brien, the president of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters, to “stand your butt up” and settle longstanding differences right there in the room. Vermont Sen. Bernie Sanders, the chairman of the Senate panel that was holding the hearing, yelled at Mullin to sit down after he challenged O’Brien to a fight. Mullin had stood up from his seat at the dais and appeared to start taking his ring off. “This is the time, this is the place,” Mullin told O’Brien after reading a series of critical tweets O’Brien had sent about him in the past. “If you want to run your mouth, we can be two consenting adults. We can finish it here.” The two men never came face to face in the hearing room. But they hurled insults at each other for around six minutes as Sanders repeatedly banged his gavel and tried to cut them off. Sanders, a longtime union ally, pleaded with them to focus on the economic issues that were the focus of the Senate Health, Education, Labor and Pensions Committee hearing, which Sanders was holding to review how unions help working families.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7301692282800000286" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-11-15T14:15:29+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7301818652817444127</id>
    <title>Congress Has Turned Into Fight Club #usa #america  Rep. Tim Burchett accused former Speaker of the House Kevin McCarthy of elbowing him in the kidneys intentionally in retaliation for the Tennessee Republican's vote last month to oust McCarthy, sparking a</title>
    <updated>2023-11-15T22:25:57+00:00</updated>
    <content>Congress Has Turned Into Fight Club #usa #america  Rep. Tim Burchett accused former Speaker of the House Kevin McCarthy of elbowing him in the kidneys intentionally in retaliation for the Tennessee Republican's vote last month to oust McCarthy, sparking a conflict on an already tumultuous day at the Capitol. Burchett was talking to NPR reporter Claudia Grisales on Tuesday morning when he says he “got elbowed in the back and it kind of caught me off guard because it was a clean shot to the kidneys.” “I turned back and there was Kevin,” Burchett told CNN. “I chased after him of course. He’s a, as I stated many times, he’s a bully with $17 million and a security detail. He’s the type of guy that when you’re a kid would throw a rock over the fence and run home and hide behind his mama’s skirt." Burchett and Grisales said McCarthy denied it at the time and he later denied elbowing Burchett to other members of the press. He said there was no bad blood over the vote to remove him from the speakership. “I didn’t even know what he was talking about,” McCarthy told CNN. “I did not run and hit the guy. I did not kidney punch him.” “If I hit someone, they would know about it,” he added, mocking Burchett for claiming he was in pain. In audio released by NPR, Burchett can be heard saying "Why'd you elbow me in the back, Kevin? Hey Kevin, you got any guts?” McCarthy can be heard denying the claim and laughing. “What a jerk. You need security Kevin,” Burchett says. McCarthy conceded he may have bumped into Burchett, but the NPR reporter backed up Burchett’s account. “While talking to [Burchett] after the GOP conference meeting, [McCarthy] walked by with his detail and McCarthy shoved Burchett. Burchett lunged towards me,” Grisales wrote on X, the social media platform formerly known as Twitter. “I thought it was a joke, it was not. And a chase ensued.” Speaking to reporters on Tuesday, Burchett brushed off McCarthy's explanation, saying that it shows "exactly why he doesn't need to be speaker."</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7301818652817444127" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-11-15T22:25:57+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7302192727024799007</id>
    <title>Pandas To Return To America! #usa #china  Pandas are coming back to America! During his visit to California, Xi said that China is ready to continue their cooperation on Panda conservation with America. Saying that he was told that a lot of American child</title>
    <updated>2023-11-16T22:37:28+00:00</updated>
    <content>Pandas To Return To America! #usa #china  Pandas are coming back to America! During his visit to California, Xi said that China is ready to continue their cooperation on Panda conservation with America. Saying that he was told that a lot of American children were sad to see them go. Xi also called Pandas “envoys of friendship between the Chinese and American peoples” Biden also wished Xi’s wife a happy early birthday because they share the same birthday. And Xi reportedly said he was embarrassed because he had forgotten that his wife’s birthday was next week. Which I don’t know why you’d admit that.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7302192727024799007" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-11-16T22:37:28+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
