<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-08-08T02:39:49+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7263612031952211246</id>
    <title>Niger Asks For American Intervention #usa #france  Niger’s President has called upon the United States to restore constitutional order in the country and to stop the military Junta from overthrowing their democracy. Saying that if they’re not stopped the </title>
    <updated>2023-08-04T23:24:37+00:00</updated>
    <content>Niger Asks For American Intervention #usa #france  Niger’s President has called upon the United States to restore constitutional order in the country and to stop the military Junta from overthrowing their democracy. Saying that if they’re not stopped the region will fall to Russian influence and become a breeding ground for terrorism. The Junta is currently holding the President hostage and they have ended diplomatic relations with the US, France, Nigeria, and Togo. ECOWAS made a plan for military intervention today, including how and when to deploy forces. France will reportedly give logistical and intelligence support for the invasion. Nigeria’s President has asked the senate to approve a full scale military intervention. They also have called for a blockade of Niger and for a no-fly-zone.  The Junta has cut off military cooperation with France and is now trying to expel French troops from the country. And they have reportedly entered talks with Wagner, presumably about exchanging protection for resources. There are disturbing videos and reports emerging of the Junta shooting protesters who support the President. They say they’ll fight any invasion to the death. There is a lot of misinformation going around suggesting that this was a popular revolution, that is false. This is a military coup that was started due to one man’s desire to stay in power. It was never about resources or the will of the people. The people of Niger certainly don’t back them and the US, France, and ECOWAS have a clear mandate to restore democracy here. There are two days left on the deadline to war.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7263612031952211246" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-04T23:24:37+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7264663850971155755</id>
    <title>China &amp; Russia Sail Off Coast Of America #usa #america  China and Russia sent a huge Naval patrol near Alaska. At least 11 Chinese and Russian ships came very close to Alaska but never entered US waters. 4 US destroyers and P-8 aircraft were dispatched to</title>
    <updated>2023-08-07T19:26:12+00:00</updated>
    <content>China &amp; Russia Sail Off Coast Of America #usa #america  China and Russia sent a huge Naval patrol near Alaska. At least 11 Chinese and Russian ships came very close to Alaska but never entered US waters. 4 US destroyers and P-8 aircraft were dispatched to shadow their patrol. It was reportedly a historic first as this was the largest flotilla to ever approach the United States. The U.S. says this was highly provocative</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7264663850971155755" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-07T19:26:12+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7264685315024080171</id>
    <title>Calm Before World War: Africa #usa #france #nigeria  It’s the calm before the storm for World War: Africa. The U.S. is reportedly going to send a special emissary to try to reason with the Junta. The Junta has closed the airspace and has called on the peo</title>
    <updated>2023-08-07T20:49:34+00:00</updated>
    <content>Calm Before World War: Africa #usa #france #nigeria  It’s the calm before the storm for World War: Africa. The U.S. is reportedly going to send a special emissary to try to reason with the Junta. The Junta has closed the airspace and has called on the people to be ready to “defend the homeland”. Wagner has deployed advisors to Niger to reportedly defend the capital; they'll also open an office there. France has issued a Do-Not-Travel advisory for Niger, Mail, and Burkina Faso. They’ve also canceled all flights going to these places and those that fly over them. ECOWAS’s deadline for military intervention is over but they say that the militaries need more time to amass troops so they’ve extended it a week to align with the African Union’s deadline, likely in an attempt to gain more manpower. They will hold an extraordinary summit on Thursday to seek one last attempt at diplomacy. #africa </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7264685315024080171" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-07T20:49:34+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7264708088266116395</id>
    <title>Kenya To Intervene In Haiti #usa #kenya  Kenya is ready to lead a multinational force into Haiti. Gangs in Haiti are causing a humanitarian crisis leading to the Prime Minister sending out a request to the world for help last year. The UN has backed the c</title>
    <updated>2023-08-07T22:17:57+00:00</updated>
    <content>Kenya To Intervene In Haiti #usa #kenya  Kenya is ready to lead a multinational force into Haiti. Gangs in Haiti are causing a humanitarian crisis leading to the Prime Minister sending out a request to the world for help last year. The UN has backed the calls for a security force but no country has been willing to do it because.. to keep it brief, it’s anarchy. But Kenya has answered the call and has offered to deploy a thousand police officers to the island to train and assist Haitian police. The U.S. has offered to propose it to the security council for Kenya as it mulls how it can support them by potentially forming a coalition of countries to support the UN action by giving personnel, financing, and equipment.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7264708088266116395" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-07T22:17:57+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7264775611598540074</id>
    <title>China Attacks Philippines In South China Sea #philippines #usa  China attacked the Philippines in the South China Sea. A Chinese coast guard ship fired a water cannon at a Philippine ship attempting to resupply a marine garrison. The Philippines condemned</title>
    <updated>2023-08-08T02:39:49+00:00</updated>
    <content>China Attacks Philippines In South China Sea #philippines #usa  China attacked the Philippines in the South China Sea. A Chinese coast guard ship fired a water cannon at a Philippine ship attempting to resupply a marine garrison. The Philippines condemned the action and the U.S. reminded China that it has a treaty obligation to defend the Philippines and that extends to its ships in the South China Sea. Australia, Germany, Canada, and Japan have condemned China.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7264775611598540074" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-08T02:39:49+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
