<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco</id>
  <title>philipdefranco TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-07-28T19:41:17+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/philipdefranco.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from philipdefranco</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7259866793546714410</id>
    <title>Russia Bombs NATO Ship #russia #ukraine  Russia just hit a NATO ship while it was bombing a Ukrainian port. The civilian ship belonged to Romania and it was struck in the Ukrainian port of Reni. The ship was able to complete its voyage despite minor damag</title>
    <updated>2023-07-25T21:11:11+00:00</updated>
    <content>Russia Bombs NATO Ship #russia #ukraine  Russia just hit a NATO ship while it was bombing a Ukrainian port. The civilian ship belonged to Romania and it was struck in the Ukrainian port of Reni. The ship was able to complete its voyage despite minor damage. No Romanian citizens were injured. If Russia continues to bomb Ukrainian ports, they will only raise the risk of NATO involvement.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7259866793546714410" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-25T21:11:11+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7259915875946450219</id>
    <title>Russian Brain Drain Boosts Neighboring Economies Big Time #russia #ukraine </title>
    <updated>2023-07-26T00:21:34+00:00</updated>
    <content>Russian Brain Drain Boosts Neighboring Economies Big Time #russia #ukraine </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7259915875946450219" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-26T00:21:34+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7260185946157567275</id>
    <title>America Has Alien Bodies?! #usa #ufo  A former intelligence officer testified in front of the United States Congress today that the US is in possession of alien bodies and UFOs. The officer claims that non-human technologies have injured humans and that t</title>
    <updated>2023-07-26T17:49:36+00:00</updated>
    <content>America Has Alien Bodies?! #usa #ufo  A former intelligence officer testified in front of the United States Congress today that the US is in possession of alien bodies and UFOs. The officer claims that non-human technologies have injured humans and that the US government became aware of Aliens in the 1930s. He also says he’s seen a video of a UFO being shot down and that the US government has a program to retrieve crashed UFOs and to reverse engineer them. He refused to say publicly if the US has communicated with aliens. He said that since coming forward about UFOs, he’s had to fear for his life. The officer also alleges that the US government is conducting a disinformation campaign targeted towards Americans about UFOs. Extraordinary claims require extraordinary amounts of evidence.. And he’s provided nothing.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7260185946157567275" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-26T17:49:36+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7260588859367394602</id>
    <title>Russia Attacks 6th US Drone #usa #russia  For the 6th time this month and the 2nd time in 24 hours, a Russian jet has attacked a U.S. drone. The Russian jet fired flares at the drone which struck the main body of the drone, severely damaging it. Russia cl</title>
    <updated>2023-07-27T19:53:07+00:00</updated>
    <content>Russia Attacks 6th US Drone #usa #russia  For the 6th time this month and the 2nd time in 24 hours, a Russian jet has attacked a U.S. drone. The Russian jet fired flares at the drone which struck the main body of the drone, severely damaging it. Russia claims the drone was being highly provocative. And the US statement is the same as last time which is essentially “Russia needs to grow up”. Commanders reportedly exchanged angry threats over the deconfliction hotline afterwards. The U.S. has now deployed even more F-35s to the region as their patience begins to run thin.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7260588859367394602" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-27T19:53:07+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7260956878946143534</id>
    <title>NATO To Escort Ukrainian Ships?! #usa #ukraine  A US Admiral and former Supreme Allied commander of NATO has suggested the US Navy and NATO escort Ukraine’s ships exporting grain in the Black Sea. He says they would bundle merchant ships into three-to-fiv</title>
    <updated>2023-07-28T19:41:17+00:00</updated>
    <content>NATO To Escort Ukrainian Ships?! #usa #ukraine  A US Admiral and former Supreme Allied commander of NATO has suggested the US Navy and NATO escort Ukraine’s ships exporting grain in the Black Sea. He says they would bundle merchant ships into three-to-five ship convoys, each escorted by a couple of guided-missile warships. He cites how the US Navy did the same thing in the Persian Gulf when Iran was sinking Kuwait’s oil vessels. The justification for this action would be that blockades are illegal and that there is no declared state of war between Ukraine and Russia. It may have worked against Iran, but the serious flaw in this plan is that your average Russian sailor is silly and that Biden is too risk averse for such a plan.</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@philipdefranco/video/7260956878946143534" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-28T19:41:17+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
