<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@theausinstitute</id>
  <title>theausinstitute TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-09-06T07:20:00+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/theausinstitute.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from theausinstitute</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@theausinstitute/video/7269984162067631368</id>
    <title>"If we say Yes now, we can listen to their priorities and needs, and we as a nation can begin to come together after decades of growing apart."  In less than a minute, Richard Denniss, executive director of the Australia Institute explains the simple reas</title>
    <updated>2023-08-22T03:32:23+00:00</updated>
    <content>"If we say Yes now, we can listen to their priorities and needs, and we as a nation can begin to come together after decades of growing apart."  In less than a minute, Richard Denniss, executive director of the Australia Institute explains the simple reasons why we are supporting the Voice to Parliament. Here's the facts: The polling shows more than 80% of Indigenous Australians support the Voice.   It was first proposed in the Uluru Statement from the Heart. The Uluru Statement from the Heart is the culmination of over a decade of work and extensive First Nations consultation which arrived at a consensus about what constitutional recognition should look like. Twelve deliberative dialogues were conducted involving a total of 1,200 First Nations people drawn from local traditional owners, First Nations community-based organisations and Aboriginal and Torres Strait Islander leaders. These regional dialogues then selected their own representatives to attend the First Nations Constitutional Convention at Uluru in 2017, where First Nations forged a historic consensus on what constitution recognition should look like, adopting the Uluru Statement from the Heart. The Statement is an invitation from First Nations people to all Australians. One of its key features is to ask Australians to support meaningful constitutional recognition by providing a First Nations Voice. We're proud to support the Yes vote in the upcoming Voice referendum. #WriteYes #auspol #yes23 #fyp</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@theausinstitute/video/7269984162067631368" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-22T03:32:23+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@theausinstitute/video/7272625721812552968</id>
    <title>"The fact that you've got two whistleblowers on trial right now in Australia... sends a really chilling effect to other whistleblowers who might be thinking about speaking up." - Kieran Pender, senior lawyer at the Human Rights Law Centre Watch the full w</title>
    <updated>2023-08-29T06:24:03+00:00</updated>
    <content>"The fact that you've got two whistleblowers on trial right now in Australia... sends a really chilling effect to other whistleblowers who might be thinking about speaking up." - Kieran Pender, senior lawyer at the Human Rights Law Centre Watch the full webinar on Whistleblowing in Australia, link in bio. #auspol</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@theausinstitute/video/7272625721812552968" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-29T06:24:03+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@theausinstitute/video/7273006430414703879</id>
    <title>[Pacific Island leaders] have been very clear in what they expect from Australia...when it comes to partnering to host a COP.  "Is Australia really a credible host? Why should we host an event when they've ignored our requests for years?" Listen to the la</title>
    <updated>2023-08-30T07:01:05+00:00</updated>
    <content>[Pacific Island leaders] have been very clear in what they expect from Australia...when it comes to partnering to host a COP.  "Is Australia really a credible host? Why should we host an event when they've ignored our requests for years?" Listen to the latest episode of our Follow the Money podcast, link in bio. #auspol #climate</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@theausinstitute/video/7273006430414703879" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-30T07:01:05+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@theausinstitute/video/7275571761998056712</id>
    <title>"If they were fluffy koalas piled up, I think people would be a lot more outraged. But unfortunately, because they're fish, we think it's not quite as bad." On this episode of Follow the Money, Ebony is chatting with Australia Institute researcher and Men</title>
    <updated>2023-09-06T04:55:22+00:00</updated>
    <content>"If they were fluffy koalas piled up, I think people would be a lot more outraged. But unfortunately, because they're fish, we think it's not quite as bad." On this episode of Follow the Money, Ebony is chatting with Australia Institute researcher and Menindee local Kate McBride about fish kills, and the Murray-Darling Basin Plan. Listen via link in bio. #auspol</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@theausinstitute/video/7275571761998056712" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-06T04:55:22+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@theausinstitute/video/7275573021203614984</id>
    <title>"One of the most frustrating things to hear, particularly during those first fish kills, was politicians in particular saying that they're natural." "These fish kills are not natural and they should not happen." - Kate McBride, researcher and Menindee loc</title>
    <updated>2023-09-06T07:20:00+00:00</updated>
    <content>"One of the most frustrating things to hear, particularly during those first fish kills, was politicians in particular saying that they're natural." "These fish kills are not natural and they should not happen." - Kate McBride, researcher and Menindee local Listen to the latest episode of Follow the Money via link in bio #auspol</content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@theausinstitute/video/7275573021203614984" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-09-06T07:20:00+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
