<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://tiktok.com/@viceautoday</id>
  <title>viceautoday TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-12-07T05:31:36+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="http://tiktok.com" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/viceautoday.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://awirthy.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>OK Boomer, all the latest TikToks from viceautoday</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@viceautoday/video/7307496172103535879</id>
    <title>Victoria could be on its way to decriminalising 🍃 after a new drug law bill, introduced in the state’s parliament this week, spurred discussions from politicians about criminal possession laws. Several senior MPs shared their opinions of and experiences w</title>
    <updated>2023-12-01T05:37:21+00:00</updated>
    <content>Victoria could be on its way to decriminalising 🍃 after a new drug law bill, introduced in the state’s parliament this week, spurred discussions from politicians about criminal possession laws. Several senior MPs shared their opinions of and experiences with the substance and some came out in support of law reform. #australia #news #law #legal #health #healthtok #herb #politics #auspol #medicine #victoria #parliament #todayilearned #learnontiktok </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@viceautoday/video/7307496172103535879" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-12-01T05:37:21+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@viceautoday/video/7308619310614777096</id>
    <title>Independent Senator Jacqui Lambie says Coles and Woolworths supermarkets operate “like a cartel” and have “ripped [people] off for years” one day after the Greens launched a Senate inquiry into the major chains’ pricing and claims of price gouging and pro</title>
    <updated>2023-12-04T06:15:44+00:00</updated>
    <content>Independent Senator Jacqui Lambie says Coles and Woolworths supermarkets operate “like a cartel” and have “ripped [people] off for years” one day after the Greens launched a Senate inquiry into the major chains’ pricing and claims of price gouging and profiteering. #australia #news #supermarket #shopping #groceryshopping #groceries #food #politics #auspol #costofliving #bills #money #coles #woolworths #todayilearned #learnontiktok </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@viceautoday/video/7308619310614777096" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-12-04T06:15:44+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@viceautoday/video/7308982887842450696</id>
    <title>Lead No campaigner Jacinta Nampijinpa Price declined 52 requests for interviews from the ABC ahead of the Indigenous Voice to Parliament referendum. An internal report from the broadcaster found voices on the No side were “significantly more difficult” to</title>
    <updated>2023-12-05T05:46:35+00:00</updated>
    <content>Lead No campaigner Jacinta Nampijinpa Price declined 52 requests for interviews from the ABC ahead of the Indigenous Voice to Parliament referendum. An internal report from the broadcaster found voices on the No side were “significantly more difficult” to get on the record across all of the ABC’s platforms, which led to more coverage of Yes perspectives. #australia #news #referendum #indigenous #firstnations #voicetoparliament #jacintaprice #abc #media #auspol #politics #todayilearned #learnontiktok </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@viceautoday/video/7308982887842450696" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-12-05T05:46:35+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@viceautoday/video/7309350772905364738</id>
    <title>Victoria’s police union says n3o-N@zi protests should be banned in the state after a small group of people in black clothes and balaclavas marched through Ballarat chanting “Australia is for the white man” over the weekend. This push for expanded police p</title>
    <updated>2023-12-06T05:34:10+00:00</updated>
    <content>Victoria’s police union says n3o-N@zi protests should be banned in the state after a small group of people in black clothes and balaclavas marched through Ballarat chanting “Australia is for the white man” over the weekend. This push for expanded police powers at protests comes after Victoria Police announced it would bolster its presence at pro-Palestine and pro-Israel demonstrations. #police #vicpol #protest #melbourne #australia #policepowers #learnontiktok #todayilearned #news #newsaustralia </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@viceautoday/video/7309350772905364738" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-12-06T05:34:10+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://tiktok.com/@viceautoday/video/7309721202627497223</id>
    <title>The landmark report found that crucial fixes need to be made in order for the NDIS to remain sustainable. The government will be making a full response to the review in 2024. #australia #news #ndis #disability #disabilitysupport #health #aunews #edutok #l</title>
    <updated>2023-12-07T05:31:36+00:00</updated>
    <content>The landmark report found that crucial fixes need to be made in order for the NDIS to remain sustainable. The government will be making a full response to the review in 2024. #australia #news #ndis #disability #disabilitysupport #health #aunews #edutok #learnontiktok #todayilearned </content>
    <link href="https://tiktok.com/@viceautoday/video/7309721202627497223" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-12-07T05:31:36+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
